Language: English Deutsche Español (España) Français (Canada) Français (Francaise) Italiano Nederlands Polski Português (Portugal) Română

PLUGSHARE PRIVACY POLICY
========================

EFFECTIVE DATE: July 10, 2023
-----------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (“PlugShare” “we”, “us”, or “our”) has the goals of creating a supportive community of Electric Vehicle (“EV”) users and delivering industry-leading charging information and a broad range of innovative products and services to help make the EV driving experience as easy and rewarding as possible. This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies on the collection, use, disclosure, retention, and transfer of the Personal Information (defined below) that we collect about you (“you” or “your”) through our interactions with you through our Websites ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); or [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); collectively, “Websites”), corresponding services and our mobile applications (collectively “Services”), as well as through interactions with unaffiliated parties such as our vendors who work with us to provide our Services to you.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you do not want us to process your Personal Information, please do not provide any to us; however, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features of our Services.

Your use of the Website and our Services is at all times also subject to our Terms of Use (available at [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) and as updated from time to time (the “Terms”)).

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any unaffiliated site or service linked to or from our Websites or Services other than to those of our Service Providers, to our social media channels or platforms that host them, or to any site or service recommended or referred to by our Websites or Services or by our staff.

California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah, and Connecticut Residents: Please review our [Supplemental Privacy Notice for Residents of Certain U.S. States](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) regarding additional information about our processing of your Personal Information.

Residents of Other Countries: If you are a resident of a country other than the United States, please review our Supplemental Privacy Notices for Certain Non-US Countries Website page for additional information about our processing of your Personal Information.

We are constantly working to improve our Services, and we may need to change this Privacy Policy from time to time as well. Our current Privacy Policy will always be on our Websites. Please notice the effective date on this Privacy Policy and make sure to periodically check back for updates.

1\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
========================================

1.1 WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION
--------------------------------

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of your personally identifiable information. “Personal Information” generally means any unencrypted information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked with a particular person such as, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.

Personal Information does not include your Personal Information that has been de-identified, anonymized, or aggregated in ways required under applicable laws so that the information can no longer directly or through other reasonably available means be used to identify an individual (collectively, “De-Identified Personal Information”).

1.2 CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND PROCESS
-------------------------------------------------------------

We collect several categories of Personal Information from and about you as summarized in the following table:

| Category | Specific Items of Personal Information |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | * first and last name<br>* user name (which may include first and last name)<br>* email address<br>* zip/postal code<br>* sex, gender<br>* unique personal identifier, e.g., customer or account name or number, phone number, mobile device identifier |
| Demographic | * country of residence |
| Commercial information | * products/services purchasing history and tendencies |
| Internet or other electronic network activity; device information | * type and manufacturer of device and its ID/UDID or similar device-specific code<br>* operating system and platform<br>* screen resolution<br>* internet service provider or mobile carrier’s name, connection speed, and connection type<br>* Internet Protocol (or IP) address, protocol, and sequence information<br>* cookies<br>* pixel tags<br>* Media Access Control (MAC) address of pages you have visited<br>* mobile device advertising identifier<br>* browser type, language, and version<br>* Website browsing, session, interaction, and search history, material and pages viewed, time and date of access to the Websites, number of bytes transferred, number of clicks per visit, time spent on a page, click-through and clickstream data, queries made, search results selected, comments made<br>* date stamp and URL of the last webpage visited before visiting our Websites, and URL of the first page visited after leaving our Websites<br>* type of Service requested<br>* hypertext transfer protocol headers, application client and server banners |
| Geolocation | * physical location and/or movements |
| Other | * EV charging data, vehicle make, model, and year<br>* Information volunteered by you as part of a feedback response or other general query made via our Websites<br>* Inferences drawn from any of the information listed to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, or aptitude |

1.3 WHERE WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------

We may collect Personal Information directly from you through our Services when you:

* Provide Personal Information to us by filling out webforms on our Websites or transacting in stores (parent, subsidiary and affiliate brands). This includes information provided when creating an online account, purchasing our Services, subscribing to our e-newsletters or other communications, requesting information from us, submitting or posting material (where permitted) on our forums, or interacting with customer support or service, report a problem with our Websites, mobile applications or Services, or otherwise communicating with us.
* Contact us. This includes all records and copies of your correspondence with us, such as with our offices or customer service/support or mailing in a check.
* Register for an event or inform us of any accessibility or other accommodation requests.
* Respond to surveys that we or our Service Providers might ask you to complete for research purposes.
* Make search queries on the Websites.
* Participate in loyalty/rewards programs.
* Apply for employment.
* Use devices and networks to access our Services, such as synching your EV with our Services.
* Use certain features on our Websites and mobile applications. Although users can access limited features without disclosing their Personal Information, such as browsing public charging stations without an account, we collect Personal Information when users sign up an account. Users can choose to use only their e-mail and password in order to browse home chargers. Users can also choose to take advantage of the enhanced capabilities by posting, commenting, publishing, or sharing additional Personal Information with the community. Generally speaking, Users choose how much information they wish to display about themselves, and can opt-out at any time.

We may also collect Personal Information from unaffiliated parties, including:

* Data suppliers (e.g., companies that provide demographics and other information regarding consumers)
* On mobile applications (parent, subsidiary and affiliate brands)
* Joint marketing partners
* Online advertising companies or platforms (such as if you voluntarily link or connect your social media profile with our Services)
* Fulfillment and delivery Service Providers
* Social media companies
* Other Service Providers
* Responding to employment opportunities
* User website/webform or app actions
* Employment verification or background check vendors
* Allow, through your device settings or third-party services, us to receive geolocation data in order to show local information (for example, a local charging station) on our mobile applications.

1.4 INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH AUTOMATED TECHNOLOGIES
--------------------------------------------------------

As you navigate through and interact with our Services, we may also use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information from your device, browser, or other network activities as described in our Cookie Policy, available at [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Website Visit and Device Information. We collect details of your visits to our Websites and use of our Mobile Apps, including, but not limited to, traffic data, geolocation data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Websites. We collect information about your computer, mobile device, and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, browser type, clickstream patterns (i.e., what you click on in a website), the URL of the most recent website you visited before coming to our Websites, the amount of time you spent on our Websites, and the pages you viewed while on our Websites. We may derive a rough estimate of your location from your IP address when you visit our Websites. For users of our Mobile Apps, we may also collect and maintain a history of your precise location information using Wi-Fi and/or Bluetooth technologies, as well as your device identifiers and GPS coordinates (e.g., latitude/longitude). If you want to prevent the collection of your location information, please adjust your settings in your mobile device to limit the Mobile App’s access to your location information.

When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our identity partners/service providers. These partners return an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online, in-app, and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please click here ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/))

Behavioral Tracking. We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services, or associate Personal Information with other information collected in this manner.

Location Analytics: Our Mobile Apps and mobile browser Websites include functionality (e.g., for submission of a driver review of a charging facility) which allows us to identify a driver’s location and the charging facility location at which a user is currently located. We collect information such as IP address, device ID, and geolocation. Mobile App users can choose to use the Mobile Apps anonymously or to login as an identified user, in which case the personal data provided upon registration may be used.

For users of the Mobile Apps, we may ask permission to access certain information from your mobile device, including your contact list, photos and videos, and microphone and camera. It is optional for you to provide us with access to this information. However, certain features of the Mobile Apps may not function optimally if you decide to not provide us with permission. 

Web Beacons. Pages of our Websites and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

Pixel Tracking. In addition to using cookies, the Websites may employ “pixel tracking.” Pixel tracking involves the use of pixel tags that are not visible to the user and consist of a few lines of computer code. Pixel tracking measures the effectiveness of advertisements and compiles aggregate and specific usage statistics. We may access these pixel tags to identify activity and interests that may allow us to better match our Products, Services, and offers with your interests and needs. For example, if you visit our Websites from an advertisement on another website, the pixel tag will allow the advertiser to track that its advertisement brought you to the Websites. If you visit our Websites, and we link you to another website, we also may be able to determine that you were sent to and/or transacted with a third-party website.

GIF. We may use tiny images known as clear GIFs to track behavior of users, including statistics on who opens our emails.

IP Address. Our servers (or those of our service providers) automatically record certain log file information reported from your browser when you access the Websites. These server logs may include information such as which pages of the Websites you visited, your internet protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, and other information on how you interact with the Websites. These log files are generally deleted periodically.

Third-Party Metrics and Analytics. Third-party metrics and analytics, on certain pages or features of the Services to help us understand and analyze visitor traffic, measure the promotional effectiveness and efficacy of our features, offerings, and marketing campaigns. We also use these tools to identify pitfalls, shortcomings, and areas of our operations in need of improvement, and to view the overall performance and ranking of our online presence. These tools might store cookies on your device at their discretion.

COOKIE NOTICE AND POLICY

The technologies we use for automatic data collection also include cookies, as described below.

Browser Cookies

Browser cookies are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. They may contain certain data, including, but not limited to, the name of the server that has placed it there, an identifier in the form of a unique number, and, an expiration date (some cookies only). Browser cookies are managed by the web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) on your computer or mobile device. Different types of cookies which have different purposes are used on our Websites.

Essential Cookies

Essential cookies are essential to allow you to browse our Websites and use its functions. Without them, services such as shopping baskets and electronic invoicing would not be able to work.

Performance Cookies

Performance cookies collect information on the use of our Websites, such as which pages are consulted most often. This information enables us to optimize our Websites and simplify browsing. Performance cookies also enable our affiliates and partners to find out whether you have accessed one of our Website pages from their site and whether your visit has led to the use or purchase of a Product or Service from our Websites, including the references for the Product or Service purchased. All the information collected by performance cookies is aggregated, and therefore anonymous.

Functionality Cookies

Functionality cookies enable our Websites to remember the choices you have made when browsing. For example, we can store your geographical location in a cookie so that the Websites corresponding to your area is shown. We can also remember your preferences, such as the text size, font and other customizable aspects of the Websites. Functionality cookies also may be able to keep track of the products or videos consulted to avoid repetition. The information collected by these cookies cannot be used to identify you and cannot monitor your browsing activity on websites which do not belong to us. Functionality cookies allow us to display advertising that is tailored to you on our Websites, to understand which parts of our content interest you the most, and which Product or Service categories you request. Some of our service providers are allowed to place cookies on our Websites. Those companies also may provide you with the option of preventing the use of cookies in the future.

At any time, you can prevent or opt out of the future use of certain cookies by activating the appropriate setting in your browser to refuse to accept browser cookies. However, if you do, your experience on our Websites may be affected; e.g., you may be unable to access certain parts of our Websites. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Websites.

Local Storage Cookies

Certain features of our Websites may use local stored objects (to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Websites. Local storage cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.

We may also combine the Personal Information we collect from you outside of our Websites or Services with Personal Information that is collected through our Websites or Services or by another means as described above.

1.5 DEVICE, NETWORK, GEOLOCATION, AND EV INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------------

When you visit or leave our Websites or Services by clicking a hyperlink or view a plugin on a third-party website, we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came or the one to which you are directed. Also, advertisers receive the URL of the page that you are on when you click on any ad that may appear on our Services. We also receive the internet protocol (“IP”) address of your computer or the proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your computer operating system details, your type of web browser, your mobile device (including your mobile device identifier provided by your mobile device operating system), your mobile operating system (if you are accessing our websites or services using a mobile device), and the name of your ISP or your mobile carrier.

1.6 SURVEYS
-----------

We or unaffiliated parties may conduct user surveys regarding on our Services. Some unaffiliated parties may target advertisements or promotions to you based on your answers to the survey. We or unaffiliated parties develop new programs or products based on the information you share in the surveys. We may use unaffiliated parties to deliver financial or other incentives to you to participate in surveys. If the delivery of incentives requires your contact information, you may be asked to provide Personal Information to the unaffiliated party fulfilling the incentive offer, which will be used only for the purpose of delivering the promised incentives and verifying your contact information. It is up to you whether you provide this information, or whether you desire to take advantage of an incentive offer. Your consent to the use of any Personal Information for the purposes set forth in the survey will be explicitly requested by the unaffiliated party conducting it. To opt-out of our surveys, you can send your request to us using the contact information below.

2\. NATURE AND PURPOSE OF PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION
=========================================================

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information, for one or more of the following purposes:

* To present our Websites and mobile applications and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information and respond to your questions on Products or Services that you request from us and information on new products and services, discounts, special promotions or upcoming events, and features or offers that we believe will be of interest to you or regarding a promotion, contest, or sweepstakes in which you have participated
* To process account information and transaction payments, including, but not limited to, Product and/or Service fees, and payments and refunds for any purchased Products or Services (though we do not receive your full credit or debit card number).
* To process discounts, offers, loyalty rewards, and/or rebate requests, forms, and applications and coordinate with the manufacturer, retailer and/or wholesaler.
* To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
* To notify you about information regarding or changes to our Websites, our policies, terms, or any Products or Services we offer or provide, or regarding your account.
* To process Personal Information or other information that you submit through to us.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Websites.
* To enhance and improve our Products and Services and develop new ones, for example, by analyzing user trends, and measuring demographics and interests.
* For internal Website, Service and system operation, administration, maintenance, internal audits and reviews, diagnosing technical problems, and maintaining security.
* To investigate any breach of our Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy.
* To track potential problems and trends with Users’ use of our Websites and Services and customize our support to better serve you.
* To provide statistics about the usage levels of the Websites and other related information to our Service Providers.
* To notify you of data privacy incidents or provide you with legally required information.
* To request your participation in ratings, reviews, surveys, focus groups, or other initiatives which help us to gather information used to develop and enhance our Products and Services.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide Personal Information.
* In any other way we may describe and for which we obtain your consent when you provide the information.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Websites; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Services; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; and/or, (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in.

Statistical data we collect automatically helps us to improve our Websites and deliver better and more personalized Products and Services, including, but not limited to, by enabling us to: estimate our audience/visitor size and usage patterns, store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize and improve our Websites, speed up your searches, and/or, recognize you when you return to our Websites.

We may collect and use your EV charging session information (e.g., charging time, energy consumption, station ownership and data, etc.) and the make, model, and year of your vehicle to administer your account, such as to distinguish between multiple vehicles or users sharing a single account, and for analytical purposes.

To the extent you do not consent to the information handling practices set out herein, you may have the right to opt-out of such practices. All opt-out requests should be directed to [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). To the extent opt-out requests are honored, they will have effect to future processing and not on processing that has occurred based on prior consent.

2.1 AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING
-----------------------------

We may use your Personal Information you provide us and which we obtain from other sources to better understand your interests so we can try to predict what other Products, Services and information in which you might be most interested. This practice involves making automated decisions about you based on this information in order to better enable us to tailor our interactions with you to make them more relevant and interesting. You may object to our doing this at any time or ask us for more information about the methodology applied in our automated decision-making processes by contacting us (see Section 12 below).

2.2 TEXT MESSAGES
-----------------

Our Services may include sending you Short Message Service (“SMS”) messages, which may deliver up to two messages per day to your wireless device (unless you communicate further with us), but message frequency may vary.  When you expressly consent to receive text messages from us and provide a cell phone number, you are expressly consenting to receive recurring informational and transactional texts from or on behalf of us to the number you provided. By expressly consenting to receive SMS messages from us and providing a cell phone number, you warrant and represent that you are the owner of the cell phone number you provide to us. We may use your information to contact you about your usage, purchases, returns (if available), Website updates, conduct surveys, or informational and service-related communications, including important security updates. After you send the SMS message “STOP” to us, we will send you an SMS message to confirm that you have been unsubscribed. Alternatively, you may submit your request by email to us, including the email address and phone number you registered with us, or by any reasonable means. After this, you will no longer receive SMS messages from us. If you want to join again, just sign up as you did the first time and we will start sending SMS messages to you again. For help, please reply to a text with HELP. Message and data rates may apply, depending on your cell phone plan. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.

2.3 SOCIAL MEDIA PLUGINS
------------------------

We integrate social media application program interfaces or plug-ins (“Plug-ins”) from social networks, including Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest and/or possibly other companies, into the Websites. In order to register as a user with us, you may have the option to sign in using your Facebook or other social media site login.

For example, when you visit our Websites, the plugin creates a direct connection between your browser and the Facebook server. This allows Facebook to receive information about your visit to our Websites with your IP address. If you click the Facebook “Like” button while you are logged on to your Facebook account, you can link the contents of our Websites to your Facebook profile. This allows Facebook to assign your visit to our Websites to your user account. Please note that as provider of the Websites, we receive no notification about the contents of the transmitted data or their use by Facebook. If you do not want Facebook to assign your visit to our Websites to your Facebook user account, please log out of your Facebook user account.

If you sign in via a social media Plug-in, you authorize us to access certain account information from that social media site, such as your public social media profile (consistent with your privacy settings in the social media site), your email address, interests, likes, gender, birthday, education history, relationships, interests, current city, photos, personal description, friend list, and information about and photos of your social media site friends who might be common social media site friends with other users. Plug-ins may transfer information about you to the Plug-in’s respective platform without action by you. This information may include your platform user identification number, which website you are on, and more. Interacting with a Plug-in will transmit information directly to that Plug-in’s social network and that information may be visible by others on that platform. Plug-ins are controlled by the respective social media site’s privacy policy (available on their website), and not by our Privacy Policy.

3\. HOW WE DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO UNAFFILIATED PARTIES
================================================================

3.1 TYPES OF UNAFFILIATED PARTIES
---------------------------------

We may or do disclose your Personal Information, in whole or in part, to the following types of unaffiliated parties, and for one or more of the following purposes:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Type of Unaffiliated Party | Purpose |
| Data storage or hosting providers | secure storage and transmission of your data |
| Database and software Service Providers | management and tracking of your data |
| Legal and compliance consultants, such as external counsel, external auditors, or tax consultants | Providing professional services to us |
| Identity management providers | authentication purposes |
| Payment solution providers | secure processing of payments you provide to us |
| Manufacturers, retailers, and wholesalers | submission, processing, and management of rebates, discounts, offers, loyalty rewards, and the like |
| Fulfillment and shipping vendors | fulfillment and delivery of Products, Services, and merchandise |
| Survey and research providers | performing studies on our behalf |
| Advertising partners, including social media providers | delivering targeted advertisements |

For any transfer of Personal Information that is not reasonably necessary to achieve the purposes for which you are engaging with PlugShare (such as for marketing or survey purposes) you have the right to opt out of such processing. To exercise your right to opt out, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 SERVICE PROVIDERS, BUSINESS PARTNERS AND SUBCONTRACTORS
-----------------------------------------------------------

 We may share your Personal Information with Service Providers which perform services on our behalf, as discussed above. These Service Providers may have access to your Personal Information in order to provide these services to us or on our behalf. If we engage Service Providers for any of the foregoing, use of your Personal Information will be bound by obligations of confidentiality and their use of Personal Information will be restricted to providing their services to us. We may store Personal Information in locations outside our direct control (for instance, on servers or databases located or co-located with data hosting Service Providers).  

3.3 CROSS-CONTEXT BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING
----------------------------------------

We are required to disclose whether we share Personal Information with a third party that is engaged in cross-context behavioral (targeted) advertising. In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have or may have disclosed the following categories of Personal Information in a context that may, under certain laws (e.g., California’s CPRA, GDPR, or UK GDPR) may be considered a sale:

* Identifiers
* Internet or other similar network activity
* Geolocation data

You have the ability to opt-out of this sharing by clicking on the opt-out prompts that will appear on the notice you are served when first visiting our mobile applications or Websites.

3.4 BUSINESS TRANSFERS
----------------------

You acknowledge (and shall not object to) to our disclosure or transfer of your Personal Information, De-Identified Personal Information, and other information you provide to us, as well as the rights you have granted or acknowledged in this Privacy Policy  (collectively, “Transferred Information”) to a potential or actual buyer or acquirer of our company or other successor for the purpose of considering or undergoing a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, change in control, or transfer of some or all of our assets (each of the foregoing referred to as a “Transfer”), whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or other court proceeding, in which Personal Information held by us is among the assets transferred, and you agree not to object to such disclosure and/or transfer. We cannot make any representations regarding the use or transfer of Transferred Information that we may have in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership, or an assignment for the benefit of creditors. Furthermore, except as required by law, we are not and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any unaffiliated parties or for any actions of any unaffiliated parties that receive any of the Transferred Information that is disclosed to us.

3.5 REQUIRED DISCLOSURES; PROTECTION OF RIGHTS; SAFETY
------------------------------------------------------

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information to any unaffiliated party unless required to do so by law, court order, legal process (e.g., subpoena), including, but not limited to, in order to respond to any government, regulatory, or licensing request, or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, subsidiaries, contracted vendors, or affinity partners, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) enforce our Terms or customer agreement (including for billing and collection purposes); (c) take precautions against liability; (d) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; (e) assist government enforcement agencies or to meet national or other government security requirements; (f) to protect the security or integrity of our Websites, our, Services, and mobile applications; or, (g) exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of us, our users or others. 

We will attempt to notify you, where practicable, about these requests unless: (i) providing notice is prohibited by the legal process itself, by court order we receive, or by applicable law, or (ii) we believe that providing notice would be futile, ineffective, create a risk of injury or bodily or other harm to an individual or group, or create or increase a risk of fraud upon us, our users, our Websites, Services, or mobile applications. In instances where we comply with legal requests without notice for these reasons, we will attempt to notify that user about the request after the fact if we determine in good faith that we are no longer legally prohibited from doing so and that no risk scenarios described in this paragraph apply.

3.6 DISCLOSURE OF DE-IDENTIFIED PERSONAL INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------------

We may share De-Identified Personal Information (including, but not limited to, anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, IP address, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with unaffiliated parties in any way we choose and for any purpose, such as for system administration and to monitor usage of the Websites; for measuring the number of visits to our Websites, average time spent, number of pages viewed; and monitoring various other Website statistics to improve the content.

4\.  “DO NOT TRACK” REQUESTS
============================

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Chrome) incorporate a “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) or similar feature that signals to websites that a user does not want to have his or her online activity and behavior tracked. If a website that responds to a particular DNT signal receives the DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser’s user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many website operators, including PlugShare, do not respond to DNT signals.

5\. PLUGSHARE COMMUNICATIONS, PREFERENCES, AND OPTING OUT
=========================================================

By providing us with your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices by email, including, but not limited to, any notices required by law (e.g., notice of data privacy or security incidents), in lieu of communication by postal mail. You also agree that we may send you notifications of activity regarding our Products, Services, the Websites, the mobile applications, your Personal Information, or any aspect of our relationship, to the email address you give us, in accordance with any applicable privacy settings. We may use your email address to send you other messages or content, such as, but not limited to, newsletters, additions or changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by clicking on Unsubscribe where available. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, special features, announcements, or offers. You may not opt out of Service-related emails. If you have elected not to provide us with an email or other address you may not receive our Service-related emails.

Through your user account settings page, you may access and, in some cases, edit, or delete certain information you have provided to us, such as name and password, email address, address, user profile information, etc. The information that you can view, update, and delete may change as the Products, Websites, Services or our practices change. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by emailing us. It is your responsibility to maintain your current email address with us. Depending on which state or country you reside in you may have additional rights. Please see below for further information.

6\. DEVELOPERS USING PLUGSHARE PLATFORM SERVICES
================================================

We collaborate with and allow third parties to use PlugShare’s developer platform to offer services and functionality in conjunction with PlugShare. These third party developers have either negotiated an agreement to use the PlugShare platform technology or have agreed to our self-service Application Programming Interfaces (“API”) and Plug-In terms in order to build software platform applications (“Platform Applications”). Both the negotiated agreements and our API and Plug-In terms of use contain restrictions on how third parties may access, store, and use the Personal Information you provide to PlugShare. If you choose to use a Platform Application, you will be asked to confirm acceptance of the privacy policy and user agreement of the third party developer. To revoke permission granted to a Platform Application, please visit your settings. Note, however, that even if you revoke the permission granted to a Platform Application, your connections may still be using the Platform Application, so the Platform Application may still have access to certain information about you, just as your connections do.

7\. RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
=====================================

The time period for which we retain your Personal Information depends on the purposes for which we use it. We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active, or as long as you are a registered account holder or user of our Services or for as long as we have another business purpose to do so (such as, but not limited to, for business, tax, or legal purposes) and, thereafter, for no longer than is required or permitted by law, or our records retention policy, reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes, or to provide you with feedback or information you might request. This period of retention is subject to our review and alteration. We may retain De-Identified Personal Information for as long as we deem appropriate.

Following termination or deactivation of your user account, we may retain your profile information and all information posted to public areas of the Websites. Following termination or deactivation of your user account, we may retain your Personal Information and other data, but will maintain it as confidential according to the Terms, this Privacy Policy, and as required by applicable law. We have the right to delete all of your Personal Information and other data after termination of your user account without notice to you.

8\. NO INTENTIONAL COLLECTION OF CHILDREN’S DATA
================================================

We do not knowingly collect, solicit, or maintain Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18 or knowingly allow such persons to register for or use our Services. If you are under 18, please do not send any Personal Information to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under age 18 without verification of parental consent, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from our database.

9\. WHERE PERSONAL INFORMATION IS PROCESSED AND STORED; APPLICABLE GOVERNING LAW
================================================================================

We have our headquarters in the United States. The Personal Information we or our Service Providers collect may be stored and processed in servers within or outside of the United States and wherever we and our Service Providers have facilities around the globe, and certain information may be accessible by persons or companies outside of the United States who provide services for us. You consent to our and our Service Providers’ transmission and/or transfer of your Personal Information to, or access it in, jurisdictions that may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information receives an adequate level of protection in the jurisdictions in which we process it.

US laws apply insofar as the you are a resident of the United States. Otherwise, this Privacy Policy and all other matters shall be interpreted and construed in accordance with the province/state and federal laws of the jurisdiction in which you reside. Jurisdictions outside of your residence may have privacy laws different than those in your including the right of law enforcement and government authorities to access the Personal Information.  To the extent that we process data outside of your country, we undertake a privacy impact assessment to determine that our Service Providers can offer substantially the same level of protection as required in your jurisdiction and enter into contracts to further bolster the obligations to appropriately process your Personal Information.

10\. SECURITY
=============

We have implemented technical and organizational security safeguards designed to protect your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, destruction, alteration and disclosure. However, please keep in mind that the Internet is not a 100% secure environment. It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information, be cautious when transmitting any Personal Information through e-mails, instant messaging, and similar means of communication, and maintain good internet security practices. We will never email you to ask for your password or other account login information. If you receive such an email, please send it to us so we can investigate.

11\. ADDITIONAL DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS FOR RESIDENTS IN CERTAIN JURISDICTIONS DESCRIBED IN THE SUPPLEMENTAL PRIVACY NOTICES
========================================================================================================================

The following explains each data subject right described in the Supplemental Privacy Notices:

* Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices: You have the right to receive certain legally required information at or before the point of Collection or in response to your request.
* Right to Deletion: You may request that we delete any Personal Information about you that we Collected from you, subject to certain exceptions.
* Right to Correction: You may request that we correct any inaccurate Personal Information we maintain about you.
* Right to Know: You may request that we provide you with specific information about how we have handled your Personal Information, including providing you with a copy of the specific pieces of Personal Information we have Collected about you in a portable format.
* Right to Non-Discrimination: You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising your data subject rights. That means not denying goods or services to you, charging you different prices or rates, or providing a different level of quality for products or services as a result of you exercising your data subject rights.
* Rights to Opt-Out: You may request to opt-out of the Sale and Sharing of your Personal Information, cross-context behavioral or targeted advertising, automated decision making or profiling, to the extent such activities are defined and restricted under applicable laws.
* Right to Restrict or Object to Processing: You may request us to suppress or cease the processing of some of your Personal Information but we may still store your Personal Information.  
* Right to Limit the Use of Your Sensitive Personal Information: You may request to limit the use of your Sensitive Personal Information to only the purposes authorized by applicable laws.
* Right to Lodge a Complaint: You have the right to file a complaint with your local data protection authority if you consider that the processing of Personal Information relating to you infringes upon your rights.
* Right to Withdraw Consent: To the extent that our processing of your Personal Information is solely based on your consent, you may withdraw that consent at any time.

12\. CONTACT INFORMATION
========================

PlugShare has designated a Data Protection Officer as the individual who will oversee compliance with privacy requirements. PlugShare’s Data Protection Officer can be contacted at the address below regarding any privacy policy issues.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 USA; Attn: Data Protection Officer; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

PRIVACY NOTICE FOR RESIDENTS OF CERTAIN U.S. STATES
===================================================

If you are a resident in California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah, or Connecticut (occasionally referred herein to as “Consumer”), state laws provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your Personal Information.

CALIFORNIA SHINE THE LIGHT LAW
------------------------------

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits any users who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what Personal Information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge.

CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (“CALOPPA”; CALIF. BUS. & PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, AVAILABLE [HERE](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D-R))
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA applies only to companies which collect Personal Information of California residents.

### a. HOW WE RESPOND TO DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS.

Some web browsers transmit “do not track” (DNT/GPC) signals to the websites and other online services with which your web browser communicates. There is currently no standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals; however, we currently have measures in place to take action in response to these signals.

### b. THIRD-PARTY BEHAVIORAL TRACKING

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services, or associate Personal Information with other information collected in this manner. We may use Personal Information to track users’ click and browsing patterns.

CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT OF 2018 (“CCPA”, AVAILABLE [HERE](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) AND ITS SUCCESSOR, THE CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT OF 2020 (“CPRA”, AVAILABLE [HERE](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-KP0k437UHioMg_6N)).
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

The table below details how we disclose personal information we have collected about you:

| Category | Categories of Unaffiliated Third Parties to Whom We Disclose Personal Information | Categories of Unaffiliated Third Parties to Whom we Sell or Share Personal Information |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | Data storage or hosting providers<br><br>Identity management providers<br><br>Payment solution providers<br><br>Survey and research providers<br><br>Advertising partners, including social media providers | n/a |
| Demographic | Survey and research providers | n/a |
| Commercial information | n/a | n/a |
| Internet or other electronic network activity; device information | Data storage or hosting providers<br><br>Database and software Service Providers<br><br>Identity management providers<br><br>Advertising partners, including social media providers | n/a |
| Geolocation | Data storage or hosting providers<br><br>Database and software Service Providers<br><br>Advertising partners, including social media providers | n/a |
| Other | Data storage or hosting providers<br><br>Database and software Service Providers<br><br>Survey and research providers<br><br>Advertising partners, including social media providers | Manufacturers, retailers, and wholesalers |

You may contact us to exercise the following rights under the CCPA and CPRA (please see section 11 of our main Privacy Policy for descriptions of these rights):

### a. Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices.

### b. Right to Know the following:

* The categories of Personal Information we collected about you.
* The categories of sources for the Personal Information we collected about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting that Personal Information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share that Personal Information.
* The specific pieces of Personal Information we collected about you (also called a data portability request) and provide a copy to you in an electronic or paper format.
* If we disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, a list disclosing disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the Personal Information categories that each category of recipient obtained.

### c. Right to Deletion.

### d. Right to Correction.

### e. Right to Opt-Out of cross-context behavioral advertising, the sale or sharing of Personal Information, the processing of Personal Information for profiling, and automated decision making.

### f. Right to Limit the Use of Your Sensitive Personal Information. Please note that we do not use Sensitive Personal Information about you for purposes not authorized by the CCPA and CPRA.

VIRGINIA CONSUMER DATA PROTECTION ACT (VCDPA), COLORADO PRIVACY ACT (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), UTAH CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2), AND CONNECTICUT DATA PRIVACY ACT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

You may contact us to exercise the following rights under these state-specific laws:

1. Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices.
2. Right to Know.
3. Right to Deletion.
4. Right to Correction.
5. Right to Opt-Out of targeted advertising or the sale of Personal Information.
6. Right to Opt-Out of Profiling (automated processing of personal information for purposes of analyzing or predicting an individual’s characteristics or future behavior, resulting in decisions that affect a person’s substantive rights).  
7. Virginia, Colorado, and Connecticut consumers also have the right to appeal our decisions on their data subject requests by contacting us through the same method for submitting a request. Please enclose a copy of or otherwise specifically reference our decision on your data subject request, so that we may adequately address your appeal. We will respond to your appeal in accordance with applicable law.

NEVADA
------

As described above, we may sell your identifiers or other identifying information that we collect from our Websites and online Services to unaffiliated parties for cross-contextual behavior tracking purposes within the meaning of Nevada law. You have the Right to Opt-Out of selling or licensing those categories of personal information about you to unaffiliated parties.

EXERCISING RIGHTS
-----------------

To exercise the access, correction, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a request to us by using our webform available [here](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Only you or a person you have authorized to act on your behalf may make a request related to your Personal Information. You also may make a request on behalf of your minor child. If we receive a request from a person to exercise right on your behalf, we will ask for a copy of your signed permission giving authorization to submit such requests on your behalf and we will contact you to directly confirm such authorization. You may only make a request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable Consumer request must:

* Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected Personal Information or that an authorized representative has made the request.
* Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the Personal Information relates to you. Making a request does not require you to create an account with us. We will only use Personal Information provided in a request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.

To exercise the rights to opt out of cross-context behavioral advertising, targeted advertising, or the sharing of Personal Information as described above, you will need to opt out based on what platform you are on.  Note that your request to opt out is specific to the device and platform where you submit that request, so you may need to submit multiple requests if you intend to opt out of these specific processing activities for multiple devices and platforms. Please click:

* here to opt out from Plugshare.com (Web platform)
* here to opt out from Plugshare iOS app
* here to opt out from Plugshare Android app

### Verification Process

Upon receiving a data access, correction, data portability, or deletion request from you we will send an email within 10 business days to you at the email address we have for you on file. The email will ask you to respond to verify you as the Consumer making the request. Upon receipt of your verification we will match your information to that which is in our file. Upon verification of your identity we will proceed to process your request and respond within 45 calendar days, unless (a) we are unable to verify your request, (b) if we are unable to match you with information in our database, or (c) if an exception under the law exists exempting us from complying with your request. If we require more time (up to an additional forty-five (45) calendar days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.

If we are unable to comply with your request, the response we provide will explain the reasons for this. For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your Personal Information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable Consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request.

* * *

PRIVACY NOTICES FOR CERTAIN NON-US COUNTRIES
============================================

GENERAL INFORMATION
-------------------

### a. YOUR SPECIFIC CONSENT TO PROCESSING OF “SENSITIVE” OR “SPECIAL” CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Under the privacy laws of some countries, certain types of Personal Information are considered to be “sensitive” or “special” categories of information. We rarely process sensitive or special categories of data unless it is in your vital interests or those of another person that we do so. For all other circumstances, you specifically consent to our collection, processing, and retention of sensitive or special categories of Personal Information as described in Section 1.2 of our main Privacy Policy and otherwise consent to the processing of Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.  

### b. OUR LEGAL BASES FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our legal bases for collecting and using the Personal Information described above will depend on the Personal Information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. Generally speaking, we will collect and process your Personal Information only where we need the Personal Information to perform Services for you for which you have contracted with us, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms, we will rely upon your consent where we are legally required to do so. In some cases, we also may have a legal obligation to collect Personal Information from you or may otherwise need the Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

LEGITIMATE INTEREST BASIS FOR COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION: The collection and processing of your Personal Information may be necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests. Such legitimate interest purposes may include:

* fraud prevention
* ensuring network and information security
* indicating possible criminal acts or threats to public security, including enhancing protection of our community against spam, harassment, intellectual property infringement, crime, and security risks of all kind, and enforcing legal claims, including investigation of potential violations of our Terms of Use
* when we are complying with legal obligations
* processing employee or visitor, member, attendee, or registrant data
* performing the function or service you requested of us
* providing our Services and their functionality to you where such processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by our service providers related to the Services
* direct marketing
* the relevant and appropriate relationship we have with you
* analytics, e.g., assess the number of visitors, page views, use of the Websites, etc., in order to understand how our Websites, Products and Services are being used, to optimize the Websites and/or future communications, and to develop new services and Website features
* updating your information and preferences
* offering and improving our Websites, Products, and Services
* enforcing legal claims, including investigation of potential violations of our Terms

In addition to the information provided above, the following sections apply only to the residents or citizens of the country or region discussed. For the purposes of the following sections, unless specifically mentioned, the definition of “Personal Information” as used above shall have the definition of personal information, personal data, or similar term as applicable under that country’s or region’s data privacy laws. In the event of and to the extent of a conflict between the sections below and the sections above, the sections below shall control.

GDPR – PRIVACY NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA (EEA), UNITED KINGDOM, AND SWITZERLAND
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

### a. OVERVIEW

The following provisions apply only if you are a resident of the EEA, UK, or Switzerland (referred to in this Section for convenience as the “EU Region”).

For such residents, all processing of your Personal Information is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations, in particular, (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, known as the General Data Protection Regulation or the UK General Data Protection Regulation for UK residents (collectively, “GDPR”), and our processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR. For purposes of the GDPR, we will be the “data controller” of Personal Information (referred to and defined in the GDPR (available [here](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/-oP4E51K04lXv)) as “personal data”) we collect, unless we collect such information on behalf of a “data controller” in which case we will be a “data processor.” This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites, applications or services that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that display or link to a different privacy policy. For EU Region residents and citizens only, to the extent any definition in this Privacy Policy conflicts with a definition under the GDPR, the GDPR definition shall control.

We provide adequate protection for the transfer of Personal Information to countries outside of the EU Region through one or more of the following methods: (a) a series of intercompany agreements based on or incorporating the Standard Contractual Clauses, (b) we may rely on the European Commission’s adequacy decisions about certain countries, as applicable, (c) we may obtain your consent for these data transfers from the EU Region to the United States to other countries, (d) we may adopt binding corporate rules, or (e) to the extent applicable, we may rely on derogations as set forth in GDPR Article 49 for the transfer and onward transfer of Personal Information collected from individuals in the EU Region to the United States and other countries that the EU Region views as not providing adequate data protection. Regarding method (e), we may transfer Personal Information to a third party to perform a contract with you, with your explicit consent or in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and freedoms. If this Personal Information is not processed and transferred, we will not be able to execute the contract with you or you will not have access to any or all the benefits and features associated with your transaction.

We also may need to transfer your information to other group companies or service providers in countries outside the EU Region. This may happen if our servers or suppliers and service providers are based outside the EU Region, or if you use our Products and/or Services while visiting countries outside these areas.

Our legal bases for collecting your Personal Information are discussed .

### b. YOUR DATA RIGHTS UNDER GDPR.

If you are subject to GDPR, your rights include the right to:

* Right to Know.
* Right to Correction.
* Right to Deletion.
* Right to Restrict or Object to Processing. You have the right to object to your Personal Information used in the following manners: (a) processing based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority (including profiling); (b) direct marketing (including profiling); and, (c) processing for purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics. See below for more information.
* Right to Opt Out. You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affects you, except for the exceptions applicable under relevant data protection laws.
* Right to Lodge a Complaint. If you reside within the EEA, a list of National Data Protection Authorities can be found [here](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm-pNojSX). If you reside in the United Kingdom you can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office [here.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/-HSqXKKA_MiHPV3)
* Right to Withdraw Consent.

NOTICES TO RESIDENTS OF CERTAIN OTHER (NON-U.S.) COUNTRIES
----------------------------------------------------------

The following in this Section is in addition to the information discussed in our main Privacy Policy.

We will honor the following data subject rights for all residents outside of the U.S.:

* Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices:

* Our identity and contact information,
* The specific purpose of our processing of your Personal Information,
* The form and duration of our processing of your Personal Information,
* Information about our sharing and purpose for sharing your Personal Information,
* The responsibilities of any third parties processing your Personal Information, and,
* Information regarding any public and private legal entities with which we have shared your Personal Information.

* Right to Know:

* Decisions made exclusively on the basis of automated processing of Personal Information.
* Access information about the Personal Information we collect.

* Right to Correction.
* Right to Restrict or Object to Processing.
* Right to Withdraw Consent.

Any translation of this Privacy Policy into a language other than English is provided solely for information purposes. In the event of any discrepancies, the only legally valid and binding version shall be the English version of this document.

### a. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF ARGENTINA

The technical and organizational security measures implemented by PlugShare would also support rules in Argentina’s Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) 25.326, such as the prohibition of any secondary use of a data subject’s personal data and the prohibition against the transfer of personal data to countries that do not offer an adequate level of protection. PlugShare uses a data transfer/processing agreement to help with compliance with PDPA Provision 60-E/2016, which regulates the cross-border transfer of personal data.

Argentina residents have (a) the Right to Know information about the existence and purpose of such Personal Information, and (b) Right to Correction and Right to Restrict or Object to Processing of your Personal Information if it is false, inaccurate, or discriminatory.

### b. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF AUSTRALIA

We may use and disclose your Personal Information (as defined under Australia law) to third parties based outside of Australia, primarily in the United States, as described in Section 9 of our main Privacy Policy. You agree and acknowledge that the overseas recipients will be subject to the privacy law of their local jurisdiction and may not be subject to any privacy obligations or to any principles similar to the Australian Privacy Principles. They will also be subject to a foreign law that could compel the disclosure of Personal Information to a third party, such as an overseas authority. Unless you notify us in writing to the contrary, you will be taken to have consented to the disclosure by us of Personal Information to overseas recipients. You have the option to remain anonymous when dealing with us, or not to disclose certain Personal Information to us. However, this may mean that we may be prevented from being able to provide our Services to you.

For residents of Australia updates to this Privacy Policy are effective if we obtain your express consent or if we provide an option to opt out when material changes are announced (e.g., on our Websites or via email).

### c. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF BRAZIL

Residents of Brazil have the Right to Know the following information: whether your provision to us of your Personal Information is a contractual requirement, or if there is any consequence to not providing such data (the answer is no to both), information regarding any automated decision making (including profiling) that we do (see Section 2.1 of our main Privacy Policy), you have the right to withdraw consent to the processing of your Personal Information, and, your data subject access rights (see below).

Residents of Brazil also have the right to: (a) Right to Know, including to obtain a copy of such information;; (b) Right to Correction; (c) Right to Restrict or Object to Processing; (d) Right to Deletion; (e) Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices about the public and private entities with whom your Personal Information has been shared; and, (f) Right to Lodge a Complaint with the Brazilian data supervisory authority (the ANPD).

### d. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF CANADA (INCLUDING QUEBEC)

Our Privacy Policy and our general practices are designed to comply with Canadian privacy laws including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), and, where applicable, Quebec’s private sector privacy act, the Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector (RSQ, c. P-39.1). For any information handling practices that are not reasonably connected to the purposes for which you reached out PlugShare, you have a Right to Opt Out of such information handling practices (including marketing, profiling, behavioral advertising, sharing with a third party who is not a service provider).  

Canadian residents have the Right to Opt Out to our use of Personal Information for direct marketing purposes and other processing which is not reasonably necessary to respond to what you have engaged us for.

### e. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF HONG KONG

We use your Personal Information for the following direct marketing purposes: (a) to communicate with you about our and our affiliates’ products and services; and, (b) to send you further notices, promotions or other marketing materials regarding our Websites, Products, and Services, and those of our affiliates. Your consent for this purpose will be requested at the time of your submission of Personal Information (e.g., at account creation, event registration, etc.) to us.

### f. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF MEXICO

In addition to the information presented above residents of Mexico have the Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices, including (a) whether your provision to us of your Personal Information is a contractual requirement or if there is any consequence to not providing such data (the answer is no to both), (b) information regarding any automated decision making (including profiling) that we do (which is discussed in Section 2.1 of our main Privacy Policy), (c) how long it is held (see Section 7 of our main Privacy Policy), (d) the right to withdraw consent to the processing of your Personal Information, and, (e) your data subject access rights (see below). You also have the right to know the express indication of the sensitive Personal Information to be processed.

Residents of Mexico also have: (a) Right to Know the Personal Information we collect, including being informed about the public and private entities with whom your Personal Information has been shared and obtaining a copy of such information; (b) Right to Correction; (c) Right to Restrict or Object to Processing; and (d) Right to Deletion.

### g. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF SINGAPORE

Among other rights, if we have a presence in Singapore, you have the right to have your Personal Information we possess transmitted to another organization.

The persons or companies to whom we disclose and transfer your Personal Information may be located outside of Singapore. We shall ensure that the recipients of the transferred Personal Information are able to provide the transferred Personal Information a standard of protection that is comparable to the standards of protection set forth under Singapore privacy law through the use of written data transfer agreements (for transfers to third parties) or binding corporate rules (for transfers to our affiliates and other entities related to us).

### h. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF TAIWAN

Residents of Taiwan have the Right to Receive Information on Privacy Practices.

Residents of Taiwan also have: (a) Right to Know about the Personal Information we collect, including being informed about the public and private entities with whom your Personal Information has been shared and obtaining a copy of such information; (b) Right to Correction; (c) Right to Restrict or Object to Processing; and (d) Right to Deletion.

In addition to the information presented above, residents of Taiwan have the Right to Know certain information about the Personal Information we collect, including (a) whether your provision to us of your Personal Information is a contractual requirement or if there is any consequence to not providing such data (the answer is no to both), (b) information regarding any automated decision making (including profiling) that we do (which is discussed in Section 2.1 of our main Privacy Policy), (c) how long it is held (see Section 7 of our main Privacy Policy), (d) the right to withdraw consent to the processing of your Personal Information, and, (e) your data subject access rights (see below). You also have the Right to Know the express indication of the sensitive Personal Information to be processed (we collect no “sensitive” information).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) The Colorado Privacy Act goes into effect on July 1, 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) The Utah Consumer Privacy Act goes into effect on December 31, 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) The Connecticut Data Privacy Act goes into effect on July 1, 2023.

DATENSCHUTZRICHTLINIE VON PLUGSHARE
===================================

DATUM DES INKRAFTTRETENS: 10. Juli 2023
---------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC („PlugShare“, „wir“, „uns“ oder „unser“) hat sich zum Ziel gesetzt, eine unterstützende Gemeinschaft von Nutzern von Elektrofahrzeugen („EV“) zu schaffen und branchenführende Ladeinformationen und eine breite Palette innovativer Produkte und Dienste bereitzustellen, um das Fahrerlebnis für Elektrofahrzeuge so einfach und lohnend wie möglich zu gestalten. Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie legt unsere Richtlinien für die Erhebung, Verwendung, Offenlegung, Aufbewahrung und Übertragung der personenbezogenen Daten (wie unten definiert) fest, die wir über Sie („Sie“ oder „Ihr“) durch unsere Interaktionen mit Ihnen über unsere Websites ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); oder [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); zusammen „Websites“), entsprechende Dienste und unsere mobilen Anwendungen (zusammen „Dienste“) sowie durch Interaktionen mit nicht angeschlossenen Parteien wie unseren Anbietern, die mit uns zusammenarbeiten, um Ihnen unsere Dienste zur Verfügung zu stellen.

Bitte lesen Sie diese Datenschutzrichtlinie sorgfältig durch. Wenn Sie nicht möchten, dass wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verarbeiten, stellen Sie uns bitte keine zur Verfügung; Sie können jedoch möglicherweise bestimmte Funktionen unserer Dienste nicht nutzen.

Ihre Nutzung der Website und unserer Dienste unterliegt jederzeit auch unseren Nutzungsbedingungen (verfügbar unter [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) und in der jeweils gültigen Fassung (die „Bedingungen“)).

Die vorliegende Datenschutzrichtlinie gilt nicht für nicht verbundene Websites oder Dienste, die mit oder von unseren Websites oder Diensten verknüpft sind, außer denen unserer Dienstleister, auf unsere Social-Media-Kanäle oder -Plattformen, auf denen sie gehostet werden, oder auf Websites oder Dienste, die von unseren Websites oder Diensten oder von unseren Mitarbeitern empfohlen oder empfohlen werden.

Einwohner von Kalifornien, Virginia, Colorado, Utah und Connecticut: Bitte lesen Sie unsere [ergänzende Datenschutzerklärung für Personen mit Wohnsitz in bestimmten US-Bundesstaaten](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) bezüglich zusätzlicher Informationen über unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten.

Einwohner anderer Länder: Wenn Sie Ihren Wohnsitz in einem anderen Land als den Vereinigten Staaten haben, lesen Sie bitte unsere Seite Ergänzende Datenschutzerklärung für bestimmte Nicht-US-Länder Website für zusätzliche Informationen über unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten.

Wir arbeiten ständig daran, unsere Dienste zu verbessern, und müssen diese Datenschutzrichtlinie möglicherweise von Zeit zu Zeit auch ändern. Unsere aktuelle Datenschutzrichtlinie ist immer auf unseren Websites verfügbar. Bitte beachten Sie das Datum des Inkrafttretens dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie und überprüfen Sie regelmäßig, ob Aktualisierungen vorliegen.

1\. WELCHE PERSONENBEZOGENEN DATEN WIR ERHEBEN
==============================================

1.1 WAS SIND PERSONENBEZOGENE DATEN?
------------------------------------

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie deckt unsere Behandlung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten ab. „Personenbezogene Daten“ bezeichnet im Allgemeinen alle unverschlüsselten Informationen, die eine bestimmte Person identifizieren, sich auf diese beziehen, diese beschreiben, mit ihr in Verbindung gebracht werden können oder vernünftigerweise mit ihr in Verbindung gebracht werden könnten, wie z. B., aber nicht beschränkt auf Ihren Namen, Ihre Postanschrift, E-Mail-Adresse, Telefonnummer usw.

Zu den personenbezogenen Daten gehören nicht Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, die gemäß den geltenden Gesetzen de-identifiziert, anonymisiert oder aggregiert wurden, sodass die Daten nicht mehr direkt oder durch andere vernünftigerweise verfügbare Mittel zur Identifizierung einer Person verwendet werden können (zusammen „anonymisierte personenbezogene Daten“).

1.2 KATEGORIEN PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN, DIE WIR ERHEBEN UND VERARBEITEN
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

Wir erheben mehrere Kategorien personenbezogener Daten von Ihnen und über Sie, wie in der folgenden Tabelle zusammengefasst:

| Kategorie | Spezifische Elemente personenbezogener Daten |
| --- | --- |
| Identifikatoren | * Vor- und Nachname<br>* Benutzername (einschließlich Vor- und Nachnamens)<br>* E-Mail-Adresse<br>* Postleitzahl<br>* Geschlecht<br>* eindeutige persönliche Kennung, z. B. Name oder Nummer des Kunden oder Kontos, Telefonnummer, Mobilgerätekennung |
| Demografische Daten | * Wohnsitzland |
| Kommerzielle Informationen | * Kaufhistorie und Tendenzen von Produkten/Diensten |
| Internet- oder andere elektronische Netzwerkaktivitäten; Geräteinformationen | * Typ und Hersteller des Geräts und dessen ID/UDID oder ähnlicher gerätespezifischer Code<br>* Betriebssystem und Plattform<br>* Bildschirmauflösung<br>* Name, Verbindungsgeschwindigkeit und Verbindungstyp des Internetdienstanbieters oder Mobilfunkanbieters<br>* Internetprotokoll (oder IP) Adresse, Protokoll und Sequenzinformationen<br>* Cookies<br>* Pixel-Tags<br>* Media Access Control (MAC) Adresse der von Ihnen besuchten Seiten<br>* Werbekennung für Mobilgeräte<br>* Browsertyp, Sprache und Version<br>* Website-Browsing, Sitzungs-, Interaktions- und Suchverlauf, Material und aufgerufene Seiten, Uhrzeit und Datum des Zugriffs auf die Websites, Anzahl der übermittelten Bytes, Anzahl der Klicks pro Besuch, Zeit, die auf einer Seite verbracht wird, Click-Through- und Clickstream-Daten, gestellte Anfragen, ausgewählte Suchergebnisse, gemachte Kommentare<br>* Datumsstempel und URL der zuletzt besuchten Webseite vor dem Besuch unserer Websites sowie URL der ersten besuchten Seite nach dem Verlassen unserer Websites<br>* Art der angeforderten Dienste<br>* Hypertext-Transfer-Protokoll-Kopfzeilen, Anwendungsclient- und Server-Banner |
| Geolokalisierung | * physischer Standort und/oder Bewegungen |
| Sonstiges | * EV-Ladedaten, Fahrzeugmarke, Modell und Jahr<br>* Informationen, die Sie freiwillig im Rahmen einer Feedback-Antwort oder einer anderen allgemeinen Anfrage über unsere Websites bereitstellen<br>* Schlussfolgerungen, die aus einer der aufgeführten Informationen gezogen werden, um ein Profil über einen Verbraucher zu erstellen, das die Präferenzen, Merkmale, psychologischen Trends, Veranlagungen, Verhaltensweisen, Einstellungen, Intelligenz, Fähigkeiten oder Eignung des Verbrauchers widerspiegelt |

1.3 WO WIR PERSONENBEZOGENE DATEN ERHEBEN
-----------------------------------------

Wir können personenbezogene Daten direkt von Ihnen über unsere Dienste erheben, wenn Sie:

* Uns personenbezogener Daten an uns durch das Ausfüllen von Webformularen auf unseren Websites oder Transaktionen in Geschäften (Mutter-, Tochter- und Partnermarken) bereitstellen. Dazu gehören Informationen, die bei der Erstellung eines Online-Kontos, beim Kauf unserer Dienste, beim Abonnieren unserer E-Newsletter oder anderer Kommunikationen, bei der Anforderung von Informationen von uns, bei der Einreichung oder Veröffentlichung von Material (sofern zulässig) in unseren Foren oder bei der Interaktion mit dem Kundendienst oder Service, bei der Meldung eines Problems mit unseren Websites, mobilen Anwendungen oder Diensten oder bei der anderweitigen Kommunikation mit uns bereitgestellt werden.
* Kontaktieren Sie uns. Dazu gehören alle Aufzeichnungen und Kopien Ihrer Korrespondenz mit uns, wie z. B. mit unseren Büros oder unserem Kundenservice/Support oder dem Versand eines Schecks.
* Melden Sie sich für eine Veranstaltung an oder informieren Sie uns über Barrierefreiheit oder andere Unterkunftswünsche.
* Beantwortung von Umfragen, die wir oder unsere Dienstleister Sie möglicherweise zu Forschungszwecken ausfüllen möchten.
* Stellen Sie Suchanfragen auf den Websites.
* Nehmen Sie an Treue-/Belohnungsprogrammen teil.
* Bewerben Sie sich auf eine Beschäftigung.
* Verwenden Sie Geräte und Netzwerke, um auf unsere Dienste zuzugreifen, wie z. B. die Synchronisierung Ihres Elektrofahrzeugs mit unseren Diensten.
* Nutzen Sie bestimmte Funktionen auf unseren Websites und mobilen Anwendungen. Obwohl Benutzer auf begrenzte Funktionen zugreifen können, ohne ihre personenbezogenen Daten offenzulegen, wie z. B. das Durchsuchen öffentlicher Ladestationen ohne Konto, erheben wir personenbezogene Daten, wenn Benutzer ein Konto anmelden. Benutzer können wählen, nur ihre E-Mail-Adresse und ihr Passwort zu verwenden, um nach Ladegeräten zu suchen. Nutzer können auch die erweiterten Funktionen nutzen, indem sie zusätzliche personenbezogene Daten veröffentlichen, kommentieren, veröffentlichen oder an die Community weitergeben. Im Allgemeinen wählen Nutzer aus, wie viele Informationen sie über sich selbst anzeigen möchten, und können sich jederzeit abmelden.

Wir können auch personenbezogene Daten von nicht verbundenen Parteien erheben, einschließlich:

* Datenlieferanten (z. B. Unternehmen, die demografische Daten und andere Informationen über Verbraucher bereitstellen)
* Auf mobilen Anwendungen (Marken von Muttergesellschaften, Tochtergesellschaften und verbundenen Unternehmen)
* Gemeinsame Marketingpartner
* Online-Werbeunternehmen oder -plattformen (z. B., wenn Sie Ihr Social-Media-Profil freiwillig mit unseren Diensten verknüpfen oder verbinden)
* Abwicklungs- und Lieferdienstleister
* Social-Media-Unternehmen
* Andere Dienstleister
* Reaktion auf Beschäftigungsmöglichkeiten
* Aktionen auf der Website/im Webformular oder in der App
* Anbieter von Beschäftigungsüberprüfungen oder Hintergrundüberprüfungen
* Erlauben Sie uns über Ihre Geräteeinstellungen oder Dienste von Drittanbietern, Geolokalisierungsdaten zu erhalten, um lokale Informationen (z. B. eine lokale Ladestation) auf unseren mobilen Anwendungen anzuzeigen.

1.4 INFORMATIONEN, DIE DURCH AUTOMATISIERTE TECHNOLOGIEN ERHOBEN WERDEN
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

Wenn Sie durch unsere Dienste navigieren und mit ihnen interagieren, können wir auch automatische Datenerhebungstechnologien verwenden, um bestimmte Informationen von Ihrem Gerät, Browser oder anderen Netzwerkaktivitäten zu erheben, wie in unserer Cookie-Richtlinie beschrieben, die Sie unter [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html) finden.

Website-Besuch und Geräteinformationen. Wir erheben Einzelheiten zu Ihren Besuchen auf unseren Websites und zur Nutzung unserer mobilen Apps, einschließlich, aber nicht beschränkt auf Verkehrsdaten, Geolokalisierungsdaten, Protokolle und andere Kommunikationsdaten sowie die Ressourcen, auf die Sie auf den Websites zugreifen und die Sie auf diesen nutzen. Wir erheben Informationen über Ihren Computer, Ihr Mobilgerät und Ihre Internetverbindung, einschließlich Ihrer IP-Adresse, Ihres Betriebssystems, Ihres Browsertyps, Ihrer Clickstream-Muster (d. h., worauf Sie auf einer Website klicken), der URL der neuesten Website, die Sie besucht haben, bevor Sie zu unseren Websites gekommen sind, der Zeit, die Sie auf unseren Websites verbracht haben, und der Seiten, die Sie auf unseren Websites angesehen haben. Wir können eine grobe Schätzung Ihres Standorts von Ihrer IP-Adresse ableiten, wenn Sie unsere Websites besuchen. Für Benutzer unserer mobilen Apps können wir auch eine Historie Ihrer genauen Standortinformationen mithilfe von WLAN- und/oder Bluetooth-Technologien sowie Ihrer Gerätekennungen und GPS-Koordinaten (z. B. Breitengrad/Längengrad) erhobenen und pflegen. Wenn Sie die Erhebung Ihrer Standortinformationen verhindern möchten, passen Sie bitte Ihre Einstellungen auf Ihrem Mobilgerät an, um den Zugriff der mobilen App auf Ihre Standortinformationen zu beschränken.

Wenn Sie unsere Website nutzen, geben wir Informationen, die wir von Ihnen sammeln, wie Ihre E-Mail-Adresse (in gehashter Form), Ihre IP-Adresse oder Informationen über Ihren Browser oder Ihr Betriebssystem, an unsere Identitätspartner/Dienstleister weiter. Diese Partner geben einen Online-Identifikationscode zurück, den wir möglicherweise in unserem Erstanbieter-Cookie für unsere Verwendung in Online-, In-App- und Cross-Channel-Werbung speichern und der möglicherweise an Werbeunternehmen weitergegeben wird, um interessenbasierte und zielgerichtete Werbung zu ermöglichen. Um diese Nutzung zu deaktivieren, klicken Sie bitte hier ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Verhaltenstracking. Wir können diese Technologien auch verwenden, um Informationen über Ihre Online-Aktivitäten im Laufe der Zeit und über Websites Dritter oder andere Online-Dienste hinweg zu erheben oder personenbezogene Daten mit anderen auf diese Weise erhobenen Informationen zu verknüpfen.

Standortanalyse: Unsere mobilen Apps und mobilen Browser-Websites beinhalten Funktionen (z. B. zur Einreichung einer Fahrerbewertung einer Ladeeinrichtung), die es uns ermöglichen, den Standort eines Fahrers und den Standort der Ladeeinrichtung zu identifizieren, an dem sich ein Benutzer derzeit befindet. Wir erheben Informationen wie IP-Adresse, Geräte-ID und Geostandort. Benutzer der mobilen App können die mobilen Apps anonym nutzen oder sich als identifizierter Benutzer anmelden. In diesem Fall können die bei der Registrierung bereitgestellten personenbezogenen Daten verwendet werden.

Für Benutzer der mobilen Apps können wir um Erlaubnis bitten, auf bestimmte Informationen von Ihrem mobilen Gerät zuzugreifen, einschließlich Ihrer Kontaktliste, Fotos und Videos sowie Mikrofon und Kamera. Es ist Ihnen freigestellt, uns Zugang zu diesen Informationen zu gewähren. Es kann jedoch sein, dass bestimmte Funktionen der mobilen Apps nicht optimal funktionieren, wenn Sie uns keine Erlaubnis erteilen. 

Web-Beacons. Die Seiten unserer Websites und unsere E-Mails können kleine elektronische Dateien enthalten, die als Web-Beacons (auch als Clear Gifs, Pixel-Tags und Single-Pixel-Gifs bezeichnet) bekannt sind und die es uns beispielsweise ermöglichen, die Benutzer zu zählen, die diese Seiten besucht oder eine E-Mail geöffnet haben, sowie andere damit zusammenhängende Website-Statistiken zu erstellen (z. B. Aufzeichnung der Beliebtheit bestimmter Website-Inhalte und Überprüfung der System- und Serverintegrität).

Pixel-Tracking. Zusätzlich zur Verwendung von Cookies können die Websites „Pixel-Tracking“ verwenden. Pixel-Tracking umfasst die Verwendung von Pixel-Tags, die für den Benutzer nicht sichtbar sind und aus einigen Zeilen Computercode bestehen. Pixel-Tracking misst die Effektivität von Werbeanzeigen und stellt aggregierte und spezifische Nutzungsstatistiken zusammen. Wir können auf diese Pixel-Tags zugreifen, um Aktivitäten und Interessen zu identifizieren, die es uns ermöglichen, unsere Produkte, Dienste und Angebote besser auf Ihre Interessen und Bedürfnisse abzustimmen. Wenn Sie beispielsweise unsere Websites von einer Werbung auf einer anderen Website besuchen, ermöglicht das Pixel-Tag dem Werbetreibenden, zu verfolgen, dass seine Werbung Sie zu den Websites geführt hat. Wenn Sie unsere Websites besuchen und wir Sie mit einer anderen Website verlinken, können wir möglicherweise auch feststellen, dass Sie auf eine Website eines Drittanbieters gesendet wurden und/oder mit ihr Geschäfte getätigt haben.

GIF. Wir können winzige Bilder verwenden, die als Clear-Gifs bekannt sind, um das Verhalten von Benutzern zu verfolgen, einschließlich Statistiken darüber, wer unsere E-Mails öffnet.

IP-Adresse. Unsere Server (oder die unserer Dienstanbieter) erheben automatisch bestimmte Protokolldateiinformationen, die von Ihrem Browser gemeldet werden, wenn Sie auf die Websites zugreifen. Diese Serverprotokolle können Informationen enthalten, wie z. B. welche Seiten der Websites Sie besucht haben, Ihre Internetprotokolladresse („IP“), Ihren Browsertyp und andere Informationen darüber, wie Sie mit den Websites interagieren. Diese Protokolldateien werden in der Regel regelmäßig gelöscht.

Metriken und Analysen von Drittanbietern. Metriken und Analysen von Drittanbietern auf bestimmten Seiten oder Funktionen der Dienste, um uns dabei zu helfen, den Besucherverkehr zu verstehen und zu analysieren sowie die Werbewirksamkeit und Effektivität unserer Funktionen, Angebote und Marketingkampagnen zu messen. Wir nutzen diese Tools auch, um Fallstricke, Mängel und verbesserungsbedürftige Bereiche unseres Betriebs zu identifizieren und um die Gesamtleistung und das Ranking unserer Online-Präsenz zu überprüfen. Diese Tools können Cookies nach eigenem Ermessen auf Ihrem Gerät speichern.

COOKIE-HINWEIS UND RICHTLINIE

Die Technologien, die wir für die automatische Datenerhebung verwenden, umfassen auch Cookies, wie unten beschrieben.

Browser-Cookies

Browser-Cookies sind kleine Dateien, die auf der Festplatte Ihres Computers oder Mobilgeräts abgelegt werden. Sie können bestimmte Daten enthalten, unter anderem den Namen des Servers, der sie platziert hat, eine Kennung in Form einer eindeutigen Nummer und ein Verfallsdatum (nur bei einigen Cookies). Browser-Cookies werden vom Webbrowser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome usw.) auf Ihrem Computer oder Mobilgerät verwaltet. Auf unseren Websites werden verschiedene Arten von Cookies verwendet, die unterschiedliche Zwecke haben.

Wesentliche Cookies

Wesentliche Cookies sind unerlässlich, damit Sie unsere Websites durchsuchen und ihre Funktionen nutzen können. Ohne sie würden Dienste wie Warenkörbe und die elektronische Rechnungsstellung nicht funktionieren.

Leistungs-Cookies

Performance-Cookies erhobenen Informationen über die Nutzung unserer Websites, wie z. B. welche Seiten am häufigsten aufgerufen werden. Diese Informationen ermöglichen es uns, unsere Websites zu optimieren und das Browsen zu vereinfachen. Performance-Cookies ermöglichen es unseren verbundenen Unternehmen und Partnern auch, herauszufinden, ob Sie von ihrer Website aus auf eine unserer Website-Seiten zugegriffen haben und ob Ihr Besuch zur Nutzung oder zum Kauf eines Produkts oder eines Dienstes von unseren Websites geführt hat, einschließlich der Referenzen für das gekaufte Produkt oder die erworbenen Dienste. Alle von Performance-Cookies erhobenen Informationen werden aggregiert und daher anonymisiert.

Funktions-Cookies

Funktions-Cookies ermöglichen es unseren Websites, sich an die Entscheidungen zu erinnern, die Sie beim Surfen getroffen haben. So können wir beispielsweise Ihren geografischen Standort in einem Cookie speichern, sodass die Websites angezeigt werden, die Ihrem Gebiet entsprechen. Wir können uns auch an Ihre Präferenzen erinnern, wie z. B. die Textgröße, Schriftart und andere anpassbare Aspekte der Websites. Funktions-Cookies können auch in der Lage sein, die Produkte oder Videos zu verfolgen, die konsultiert wurden, um Wiederholungen zu vermeiden. Die durch diese Cookies erheben Informationen können nicht verwendet werden, um Sie zu identifizieren, und können Ihre Browseraktivitäten auf Websites, die nicht zu uns gehören, nicht überwachen. Funktions-Cookies ermöglichen es uns, Werbung anzuzeigen, die auf Sie auf unseren Websites zugeschnitten ist, um zu verstehen, welche Teile unserer Inhalte Sie am meisten interessieren und welche Produkt- oder Dienstkategorien Sie anfordern. Einige unserer Dienstleister dürfen Cookies auf unseren Websites platzieren. Diese Unternehmen können Ihnen auch die Möglichkeit geben, die Verwendung von Cookies in Zukunft zu verhindern.

Sie können die zukünftige Verwendung bestimmter Cookies jederzeit verhindern oder ablehnen, indem Sie die entsprechende Einstellung in Ihrem Browser aktivieren, um die Annahme von Browser-Cookies zu verweigern. Wenn Sie dies jedoch tun, kann Ihre Erfahrung auf unseren Websites beeinträchtigt werden; z. B. können Sie möglicherweise nicht auf bestimmte Teile unserer Websites zugreifen. Sofern Sie Ihre Browsereinstellungen nicht so angepasst haben, dass Cookies abgelehnt werden, wird unser System Cookies ausgeben, wenn Sie Ihren Browser auf unsere Websites verweisen.

Lokale Speicher-Cookies

Bestimmte Funktionen unserer Websites können lokal gespeicherte Objekte verwenden (um Informationen über Ihre Präferenzen und Navigation zu, von und auf unseren Websites zu erheben und zu speichern. Lokale Speicher-Cookies werden nicht durch dieselben Browsereinstellungen verwaltet, die für Browser-Cookies verwendet werden.

Wir können die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir von Ihnen außerhalb unserer Websites oder Dienste erheben, auch mit personenbezogenen Daten kombinieren, die über unsere Websites oder Dienste oder auf andere Weise, wie oben beschrieben, erhoben werden.

1.5 GERÄTE-, NETZWERK-, GEOLOKALISIERUNGS- UND EV-INFORMATIONEN
---------------------------------------------------------------

Wenn Sie unsere Websites oder Dienste besuchen oder verlassen, indem Sie auf einen Hyperlink klicken oder ein Plug-in auf einer Website eines Drittanbieters anzeigen, erhalten wir automatisch die URL der Website, von der Sie gekommen sind, oder der Website, zu der Sie weitergeleitet werden. Außerdem erhalten Werbetreibende die URL der Seite, auf der Sie sich befinden, wenn Sie auf eine Anzeige klicken, die in unseren Diensten erscheint. Wir erhalten auch die Internetprotokoll-Adresse („IP“) Ihres Computers oder des Proxy-Servers, den Sie für den Zugriff auf das Internet verwenden, Ihre Computerbetriebssystemdaten, Ihren Webbrowsertyp, Ihr Mobilgerät (einschließlich Ihrer Mobilgerätekennung, die von dem Betriebssystem Ihres Mobilgeräts bereitgestellt wird), Ihr mobiles Betriebssystem (wenn Sie über ein Mobilgerät auf unsere Websites oder Dienste zugreifen) und den Namen Ihres Internetdienstanbieters oder Ihres Mobilfunkanbieters.

1.6 UMFRAGEN
------------

Wir oder nicht verbundene Parteien können Nutzerumfragen zu unseren Diensten durchführen. Einige nicht verbundene Parteien können basierend auf Ihren Antworten auf die Umfrage Werbung oder Werbemaßnahmen an Sie richten. Wir oder nicht verbundene Parteien entwickeln neue Programme oder Produkte basierend auf den Informationen, die Sie in den Umfragen teilen. Wir können nicht verbundene Parteien einsetzen, um Ihnen finanzielle oder andere Anreize zur Teilnahme an Umfragen zu bieten. Wenn für die Bereitstellung von Anreizen Ihre Kontaktinformationen erforderlich sind, werden Sie möglicherweise gebeten, der nicht angeschlossenen Partei, die das Anreizangebot durchführt, personenbezogene Daten zur Verfügung zu stellen, die nur zum Zweck der Bereitstellung der versprochenen Anreize und zur Überprüfung Ihrer Kontaktinformationen verwendet werden. Es liegt an Ihnen, ob Sie diese Informationen zur Verfügung stellen oder ob Sie ein Anreizangebot nutzen möchten. Ihre Einwilligung zur Verwendung personenbezogener Daten für die in der Umfrage dargelegten Zwecke wird ausdrücklich von der nicht verbundenen Partei, die sie durchführt, angefordert. Wenn Sie sich von unseren Umfragen abmelden möchten, können Sie uns Ihre Anfrage über die Kontaktinformationen weiter unten zukommen lassen.

2\. ART UND ZWECK DER VERARBEITUNG PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN
==========================================================

Wir verwenden Daten, die wir über Sie erheben oder die Sie uns zur Verfügung stellen, einschließlich personenbezogener Daten, für einen oder mehrere der folgenden Zwecke:

* Um Ihnen unsere Websites und mobilen Anwendungen und deren Inhalte zu präsentieren.
* Um Sie mit Informationen zu versorgen und Ihre Fragen zu Produkten oder Dienste zu beantworten, die Sie von uns anfordern, sowie Informationen über neue Produkte und Dienste, Rabatte, Sonderaktionen oder bevorstehende Veranstaltungen und Funktionen oder Angebote, von denen wir glauben, dass sie für Sie von Interesse sind, oder über eine Werbeaktion, einen Wettbewerb oder eine Verlosung, an der Sie teilgenommen haben.
* Um Kontoinformationen und Transaktionszahlungen zu verarbeiten, einschließlich, aber nicht beschränkt auf Produkt- und/oder Dienstleistungsgebühren sowie Zahlungen und Rückerstattungen für gekaufte Produkte oder Dienste (obwohl wir nicht Ihre vollständige Kredit- oder Debitkartennummer erhalten).
* Um Rabatte, Angebote, Treueprämien und/oder Rabattanfragen, Formulare und Anwendungen zu bearbeiten und mit dem Hersteller, Einzelhändler und/oder Großhändler zu koordinieren.
* Um Ihnen Mitteilungen über Ihr Konto zukommen zu lassen, einschließlich Ablauf- und Verlängerungsmitteilungen.
* Um Sie über Informationen oder Änderungen an unseren Websites, unseren Richtlinien, Bedingungen oder Produkten oder Dienste, die wir anbieten oder bereitstellen, oder über Ihr Konto zu informieren.
* Um personenbezogene Daten oder andere Informationen, die Sie uns übermitteln, zu verarbeiten.
* Um Ihnen die Teilnahme an interaktiven Funktionen auf unseren Websites zu ermöglichen.
* Um unsere Produkte und Dienste zu verbessern und zu verbessern und neue zu entwickeln, z. B. durch Analyse von Benutzertrends und Messung der Demografie und Interessen.
* Für den internen Website-, Service- und Systembetrieb, die Verwaltung, Wartung, interne Audits und Überprüfungen, die Diagnose technischer Probleme und die Aufrechterhaltung der Sicherheit.
* Zur Untersuchung von Verstößen gegen unsere Nutzungsbedingungen oder diese Datenschutzrichtlinie.
* Um potenzielle Probleme und Trends bei der Nutzung unserer Websites und Dienste durch die Benutzer zu verfolgen und unseren Support anzupassen, um Ihnen besser zu dienen.
* Um unseren Dienstleistern Statistiken über die Nutzung der Websites und andere damit zusammenhängende Informationen zur Verfügung zu stellen.
* Um Sie über Datenschutzvorfälle zu informieren oder Ihnen gesetzlich vorgeschriebene Informationen zur Verfügung zu stellen.
* Um Ihre Teilnahme an Bewertungen, Rezensionen, Umfragen, Fokusgruppen oder anderen Initiativen anzufordern, die uns helfen, Informationen zu erheben, die zur Entwicklung und Verbesserung unserer Produkte und Dienste verwendet werden.
* Um andere Zwecke zu erfüllen, für die Sie personenbezogene Daten bereitstellen.
* Auf andere Weise können wir beschreiben und für die wir Ihre Einwilligung einholen, wenn Sie die Informationen bereitstellen.

Wir verwenden Cookies, Clear-Gifs und Protokolldateidaten, um: (a) Informationen zu speichern, damit Sie diese während Ihres Besuchs oder beim nächsten Besuch der Websites nicht erneut eingeben müssen; (b) kundenspezifische, personalisierte Inhalte und Informationen bereitzustellen; (c) die Effektivität unserer Dienste zu überwachen; (d) Gesamtkennzahlen wie die Gesamtzahl der Besucher, den Datenverkehr und demografische Muster zu überwachen; (e) von unseren Nutzern oder Technikern gemeldete technische Probleme zu diagnostizieren oder zu beheben, die mit bestimmten IP-Adressen verbunden sind; und/oder (f) Ihnen zu helfen, effizient auf Ihre Informationen zuzugreifen, nachdem Sie sich angemeldet haben.

Statistische Daten, die wir automatisch erheben, helfen uns, unsere Websites zu verbessern und bessere und personalisierte Produkte und Dienste zu liefern, einschließlich, aber nicht beschränkt auf, indem sie uns ermöglichen: die Größe und Nutzungsmuster unserer Zielgruppe/Besucher zu schätzen, Informationen über Ihre Präferenzen zu speichern, uns zu ermöglichen, unsere Websites anzupassen und zu verbessern, Ihre Suche zu beschleunigen und/oder Sie zu erkennen, wenn Sie zu unseren Websites zurückkehren.

Wir können Ihre EV-Ladesitzungsinformationen (z. B. Ladezeit, Energieverbrauch, Stationseigentum und -daten usw.) sowie die Marke, das Modell und das Jahr Ihres Fahrzeugs erheben und verwenden, um Ihr Konto zu verwalten, z. B., um zwischen mehreren Fahrzeugen oder Benutzern zu unterscheiden, die ein einziges Konto teilen, und zu Analysezwecken.

Sofern Sie nicht in die hierin dargelegten Praktiken zur Informationsverarbeitung einwilligen, haben Sie möglicherweise das Recht, diese Praktiken abzulehnen. Alle Anfragen zur Abmeldung (Opt-Out) sollten an [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) gerichtet werden. Soweit Anfragen zur Abmeldung (Opt-Out) berücksichtigt werden, wirken sie sich auf zukünftige Verarbeitungen aus und nicht auf Verarbeitungen, die aufgrund einer vorherigen Einwilligung erfolgt sind.

2.1 AUTOMATISIERTE ENTSCHEIDUNGSFINDUNG
---------------------------------------

Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, die Sie uns zur Verfügung stellen und die wir aus anderen Quellen erhalten, verwenden, um Ihre Interessen besser zu verstehen, damit wir versuchen können, vorherzusagen, an welchen anderen Produkten, Dienste und Informationen Sie am meisten interessiert sind. Bei dieser Praxis werden auf der Grundlage dieser Informationen automatisierte Entscheidungen über Sie getroffen, damit wir unsere Interaktionen mit Ihnen besser auf Sie zuschneiden können, um sie relevanter und interessanter zu gestalten. Sie können dem jederzeit widersprechen oder uns um weitere Informationen über die Methodik unserer automatisierten Entscheidungsprozesse bitten, indem Sie uns kontaktieren (siehe Abschnitt 12 unten).

2.2 TEXTNACHRICHTEN
-------------------

Unsere Dienste können das Senden von Nachrichten an Sie mit dem Short Message Service („SMS“) umfassen, die bis zu zwei Nachrichten pro Tag an Ihr drahtloses Gerät senden können (es sei denn, dass Sie weiter mit uns kommunizieren), aber die Nachrichtenhäufigkeit kann variieren. Wenn Sie ausdrücklich darin einwilligen, Textnachrichten von uns zu erhalten und eine Mobiltelefonnummer anzugeben, willigen Sie ein zu, wiederkehrende Informations- und Transaktionstexte von oder im Namen von uns an die von Ihnen angegebene Nummer zu erhalten. Indem Sie ausdrücklich in den Erhalt von SMS-Nachrichten von uns einwilligen und eine Mobiltelefonnummer angeben, garantieren und sichern Sie zu, dass Sie der Eigentümer der Mobiltelefonnummer sind, die Sie uns zur Verfügung stellen. Wir können Ihre Daten verwenden, um Sie bezüglich Ihrer Nutzung, Einkäufe, Rücksendungen (falls verfügbar), Website-Updates, Durchführung von Umfragen oder informations- und servicebezogener Kommunikation, einschließlich wichtiger Sicherheitsupdates, zu kontaktieren. Nachdem Sie die SMS-Nachricht „STOP“ an uns gesendet haben, senden wir Ihnen eine SMS-Nachricht, um zu bestätigen, dass Sie abgemeldet wurden. Alternativ können Sie Ihre Anfrage per E-Mail an uns senden, einschließlich der E-Mail-Adresse und Telefonnummer, die Sie bei uns registriert haben, oder auf angemessene Weise. Danach erhalten Sie keine SMS-Nachrichten mehr von uns. Wenn Sie erneut beitreten möchten, melden Sie sich einfach wie beim ersten Mal an und wir werden wieder SMS-Nachrichten an Sie senden. Wenn Sie Hilfe benötigen, antworten Sie bitte auf einen Text mit HELP (HILFE). Abhängig von Ihrem Mobilfunkplan können Nachrichten- und Datentarife gelten. Spediteure haften nicht für verspätete oder nicht zugestellte Nachrichten.

2.3 SOCIAL-MEDIA-PLUG-INS
-------------------------

Wir integrieren Social-Media-Anwendungsprogrammschnittstellen oder Plug-ins („Plug-ins“) aus sozialen Netzwerken, einschließlich Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest und/oder möglicherweise anderen Unternehmen, in die Websites. Um sich bei uns als Benutzer zu registrieren, haben Sie möglicherweise die Möglichkeit, sich mit Ihrer Anmeldedaten für Facebook oder anderen Social-Media-Websites anzumelden.

Wenn Sie beispielsweise unsere Websites besuchen, stellt das Plug-in eine direkte Verbindung zwischen Ihrem Browser und dem Facebook-Server her. Facebook erhält damit Informationen über Ihren Besuch auf unseren Websites mit Ihrer IP-Adresse. Wenn Sie auf der Benutzeroberfläche von Facebook „Gefällt mir“ klicken, während Sie bei Ihrem Facebook-Konto angemeldet sind, können Sie die Inhalte unserer Websites mit Ihrem Facebook-Profil verknüpfen. Dadurch kann Facebook Ihren Besuch auf unseren Websites Ihrem Benutzerkonto zuweisen. Bitte beachten Sie, dass wir als Anbieter der Websites keine Benachrichtigung über den Inhalt der übermittelten Daten oder deren Nutzung durch Facebook erhalten. Wenn Sie nicht möchten, dass Facebook Ihren Besuch auf unseren Websites Ihrem Facebook-Benutzerkonto zuweist, melden Sie sich bitte von Ihrem Facebook-Benutzerkonto ab.

Wenn Sie sich über ein Social-Media-Plug-in anmelden, Sie autorisieren uns, auf bestimmte Kontoinformationen von dieser Social-Media-Website zuzugreifen, wie z. B. Ihr öffentliches Social-Media-Profil (in Übereinstimmung mit Ihren Datenschutzeinstellungen auf der Social-Media-Website), Ihre E-Mail-Adresse, Interessen, gefällt, Geschlecht, Geburtstag, Bildungsgeschichte, Beziehungen, Interessen, aktuelle Stadt, Fotos, persönliche Beschreibung, Freundesliste und Informationen über und Fotos Ihrer Freunde auf der Social-Media-Website, die gemeinsame Freunde auf der Social-Media-Website mit anderen Benutzern sein könnten. Plug-ins können Informationen über Sie auf die jeweilige Plattform des Plug-ins übermitteln, ohne dass Sie dies tun. Diese Informationen können Ihre Plattform-Benutzeridentifikationsnummer, die Website, auf der Sie sich befinden, und mehr beinhalten. Durch die Interaktion mit einem Plug-in werden Informationen direkt an das soziale Netzwerk dieses Plug-ins übermitteln, und diese Informationen können für andere auf dieser Plattform sichtbar sein. Plug-ins werden durch die Datenschutzrichtlinie der jeweiligen Social-Media-Website (verfügbar auf ihrer Website) und nicht durch unsere Datenschutzrichtlinie kontrolliert.

3\. WIE WIR PERSONENBEZOGENE DATEN AN NICHT VERBUNDENE PARTEIEN OFFENLEGEN
==========================================================================

3.1 TYPEN VON NICHT VERBUNDENEN PARTEIEN
----------------------------------------

Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten ganz oder teilweise an die folgenden Arten von nicht verbundenen Parteien und für einen oder mehrere der folgenden Zwecke weitergeben:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Art der nicht verbundenen Partei | Zweck |
| Anbieter von Datenspeicherung oder Hosting | sichere Speicherung und Übertragung Ihrer Daten |
| Datenbank- und Software-Dienstleister | Verwaltung und Verfolgung Ihrer Daten |
| Rechts- und Compliance-Berater, wie z. B. externe Rechtsberater, externe Wirtschaftsprüfer oder Steuerberater | Bereitstellung professioneller Dienstleistungen für uns |
| Anbieter von Identitätsmanagement | Authentifizierungszwecke |
| Anbieter von Zahlungslösungen | sichere Abwicklung von Zahlungen, die Sie uns leisten |
| Hersteller, Einzelhändler und Großhändler | Einreichung, Bearbeitung und Verwaltung von Rabatten, Preisnachlässen, Angeboten, Treueprämien und dergleichen |
| Erfüllungs- und Versandanbieter | Erfüllung und Lieferung von Produkten, Dienste und Waren |
| Anbieter von Umfragen und Forschung | Durchführung von Studien in unserem Auftrag |
| Werbepartner, einschließlich Social-Media-Anbieter | Bereitstellung gezielter Werbung |

Für jede Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten, die nach vernünftigen Gesichtspunkten nicht erforderlich ist, um die Zwecke zu erreichen, für die Sie mit PlugShare interagieren (z. B. für Marketing- oder Umfragezwecke), haben Sie das Recht, diese Verarbeitung abzulehnen. Um Ihr Recht auf Abmeldung auszuüben, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 DIENSTLEISTER, GESCHÄFTSPARTNER UND UNTERAUFTRAGNEHMER
----------------------------------------------------------

 Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten an Dienstleister weitergeben, die Dienste in unserem Auftrag erbringen, wie oben erörtert. Diese Dienstleister haben möglicherweise Zugriff auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, um diese Dienste für uns oder in unserem Auftrag zu erbringen. Wenn wir Dienstleister für eines der Vorstehenden beauftragen, ist die Verwendung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an Vertraulichkeitsverpflichtungen gebunden und ihre Verwendung personenbezogener Daten ist auf die Erbringung ihrer Dienste für uns beschränkt. Wir können personenbezogene Daten an Orten außerhalb unserer direkten Kontrolle speichern (z. B. auf Servern oder Datenbanken, die sich mit Datenhosting-Dienstleistern befinden oder sich dort befinden).

3.3 KONTEXTÜBERGREIFENDE VERHALTENSBEZOGENE WERBUNG
---------------------------------------------------

Wir müssen offenlegen, ob wir personenbezogene Daten an Dritte weitergeben, die an kontextübergreifender (zielgerichteter) Werbung beteiligt sind. In den vorangegangenen zwölf (12) Monaten haben wir die folgenden Kategorien personenbezogener Daten in einem Kontext offengelegt oder könnten dies tun, der gemäß bestimmten Gesetzen (z. B. CPRA, DSGVO oder britische DSGVO) als Verkauf betrachtet werden kann:

* Identifikatoren
* Internet- oder andere ähnliche Netzwerkaktivitäten
* Geolokalisierungsdaten

Sie haben die Möglichkeit, sich von dieser Weitergabe abzumelden, indem Sie auf die Abmeldeaufforderungen klicken, die auf der Mitteilung erscheinen, die Ihnen beim ersten Besuch unserer mobilen Anwendungen oder Websites zugestellt wird.

3.4 GESCHÄFTSÜBERTRAGUNGEN
--------------------------

Sie erklären sich damit einverstanden (und werden dem nicht widersprechen), dass wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, anonymisierte personenbezogenen Daten und andere Informationen, die Sie uns zur Verfügung stellen, sowie die Rechte, die Sie in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie gewährt oder anerkannt haben (zusammen „übermittelte Informationen“), an einen potenziellen oder tatsächlichen Käufer oder Erwerber unseres Unternehmens oder einen anderen Nachfolger übermitteln, um eine Fusion zu erwägen oder durchzuführen, Veräußerung, Umstrukturierung, Reorganisation, Auflösung, Kontrollwechsel oder Übertragung einiger oder aller unserer Vermögenswerte (jeweils als „Übermittlung“ bezeichnet), sei es als laufender Betrieb oder im Rahmen des Eintritts eines Konkurses, einer Liquidation oder eines anderen Gerichtsverfahrens, bei dem von uns gehaltene personenbezogene Daten zu den übermittelten Vermögenswerten gehören, und Sie erklären sich damit einverstanden, einer solchen Offenlegung und/oder Übermittlung nicht zu widersprechen. Wir können keine Zusicherungen in Bezug auf die Verwendung oder Übermittlung von übermittelten Informationen machen, die uns im Falle eines Konkurses, einer Reorganisation, einer Insolvenz, eines Konkursverwalters oder einer Abtretung zugunsten von Gläubigern zur Verfügung stehen könnten. Darüber hinaus sind wir, außer wie gesetzlich vorgeschrieben, nicht verantwortlich für Sicherheitsverletzungen durch nicht verbundene Parteien oder für Handlungen von nicht verbundenen Parteien, die die übermittelten Informationen erhalten, die uns offengelegt werden.

3.5 ERFORDERLICHE OFFENLEGUNGEN; SCHUTZ DER RECHTE; SICHERHEIT
--------------------------------------------------------------

Sofern in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie nicht anders beschrieben, werden wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nicht an nicht verbundene Parteien weitergeben, es sei denn, dass wir gesetzlich sind, per Gerichtsbeschluss oder gerichtlichem Verfahren (z. B. Vorladung) dazu verpflichtet, insbesondere zur Beantwortung von Anfragen von Regierungen, Aufsichtsbehörden oder Lizenzgebern, oder wenn wir glauben, dass eine solche Maßnahme notwendig ist: (a) zur Einhaltung von Gesetzen, zur Befolgung von rechtlichen Verfahren, die uns oder unseren verbundenen Unternehmen, Tochtergesellschaften, Vertragshändlern oder Affinity-Partnern zugestellt werden, oder zur Untersuchung, Verhinderung oder Ergreifung von Maßnahmen in Bezug auf mutmaßliche oder tatsächliche illegale Aktivitäten; (b) zur Durchsetzung unserer Bedingungen oder Kundenvereinbarungen (einschließlich zu Abrechnungs- und Inkassozwecken); (c) um Vorkehrungen gegen Haftungsansprüche zu treffen; (d) zur Untersuchung und Abwehr von Ansprüchen oder Behauptungen Dritter; (e) zur Unterstützung staatlicher Vollzugsbehörden oder zur Erfüllung nationaler oder anderer staatlicher Sicherheitsanforderungen; (f) zum Schutz der Sicherheit oder Integrität unserer Websites, unserer Dienste und mobilen Anwendungen oder (g) zur Ausübung oder zum Schutz der Rechte, des Eigentums oder der persönlichen Sicherheit von uns, unseren Benutzern oder anderen. 

Wir werden versuchen, Sie nach Möglichkeit über diese Anfragen zu informieren, es sei denn, dass: (i) die Benachrichtigung durch das Gerichtsverfahren, durch eine gerichtliche Anordnung, die wir erhalten, oder durch geltendes Recht untersagt ist, oder (ii) wir der Ansicht sind, dass die Benachrichtigung aussichtslos oder ineffektiv wäre, das Risiko einer Verletzung oder eines körperlichen oder sonstigen Schadens für eine Person oder eine Gruppe bedeuten würde oder das Risiko eines Betrugs gegen uns, unsere Nutzer, unsere Websites, Dienste oder mobilen Anwendungen schaffen oder erhöhen würde. In Fällen, in denen wir rechtlichen Anfragen aus diesen Gründen ohne Vorankündigung nachkommen, werden wir versuchen, diesen Benutzer nachträglich über die Anfrage zu informieren, wenn wir in gutem Glauben feststellen, dass wir dies nicht mehr gesetzlich verboten sind und dass keine in diesem Absatz beschriebenen Risikoszenarien gelten.

3.6 OFFENLEGUNG ANONYMISIERTER PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN
------------------------------------------------------

Wir können anonymisierte personenbezogene Daten (insbesondere anonyme Nutzungsdaten, verweisende/Ausgangsseiten und URLs, IP-Adresse, Plattformtypen, Anzahl der Klicks usw.) an nicht verbundene Parteien auf jede von uns gewählte Weise und zu jedem beliebigen Zweck weitergeben, z. B. zur Systemverwaltung und zur Überwachung der Nutzung der Websites; zur Messung der Anzahl der Besuche auf unseren Websites, der durchschnittlichen Zeit, der Anzahl der angesehenen Seiten; und zur Überwachung verschiedener anderer Website-Statistiken zur Verbesserung des Inhalts.

4\.  „DO NOT TRACK“-ANFRAGEN
============================

Einige Webbrowser (einschließlich Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox und Chrome) enthalten eine „Do Not Track“-Funktion („DNT“) oder eine ähnliche Funktion, die Websites signalisiert, dass ein Benutzer seine Online-Aktivitäten und sein Online-Verhalten nicht verfolgen möchte. Wenn eine Website, die auf ein bestimmtes DNT-Signal reagiert, das DNT-Signal empfängt, kann der Browser diese Website daran hindern, bestimmte Informationen über den Benutzer des Browsers zu erheben. Nicht alle Browser bieten eine DNT-Option und DNT-Signale sind noch nicht einheitlich. Aus diesem Grund reagieren viele Website-Betreiber, einschließlich PlugShare, nicht auf DNT-Signale.

5\. PLUGSHARE-KOMMUNIKATION, PRÄFERENZEN UND ABMELDUNG (OPT-OUT)
================================================================

Indem Sie uns Ihre E-Mail-Adresse zur Verfügung stellen, willigen Sie ein, dass wir die E-Mail-Adresse verwenden, um Ihnen dienstbezogene Mitteilungen per E-Mail zu senden, einschließlich, aber nicht beschränkt auf gesetzlich vorgeschriebene Mitteilungen (z. B. Mitteilungen über Datenschutz- oder Sicherheitsvorfälle), anstelle der Kommunikation per Post. Sie erklären sich außerdem damit einverstanden, dass wir Ihnen Benachrichtigungen über Aktivitäten in Bezug auf unsere Produkte, Dienste, die Websites, die mobilen Anwendungen, Ihre personenbezogenen Daten oder jeden Aspekt unserer Beziehung gemäß den geltenden Datenschutzeinstellungen an die von Ihnen angegebene E-Mail-Adresse senden können. Wir können Ihre E-Mail-Adresse verwenden, um Ihnen andere Nachrichten oder Inhalte zu senden, wie z. B. Newsletter, Ergänzungen oder Änderungen an Funktionen des Dienstes oder Sonderangebote. Wenn Sie solche E-Mail-Nachrichten nicht erhalten möchten, können Sie sich abmelden, indem Sie auf Abmelden klicken, sofern verfügbar. Die Abmeldung kann Sie daran hindern, E-Mail-Nachrichten zu Updates, Verbesserungen, besonderen Funktionen, Ankündigungen oder Angeboten zu erhalten. Sie dürfen sich nicht von dienstbezogenen E-Mails abmelden. Wenn Sie sich entschieden haben, uns keine E-Mail-Adresse oder andere Adresse zur Verfügung zu stellen, erhalten Sie möglicherweise keine E-Mails im Zusammenhang mit unserem Service.

Über die Seite mit den Einstellungen Ihres Benutzerkontos können Sie auf bestimmte Informationen, die Sie uns zur Verfügung gestellt haben, wie Name und Passwort, E-Mail-Adresse, Adresse, Benutzerprofilinformationen usw. zugreifen und diese in einigen Fällen bearbeiten oder löschen. Die Informationen, die Sie anzeigen, aktualisieren und löschen können, können sich ändern, wenn sich die Produkte, Websites, Dienste oder unsere Praktiken ändern. Wenn Sie Fragen zur Anzeige oder Aktualisierung von Informationen haben, die wir über Sie gespeichert haben, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte. Wenn Sie jedoch Informationen aktualisieren, können wir eine Kopie der nicht überarbeiteten Informationen in unseren Unterlagen aufbewahren. Sie können die Löschung Ihres Kontos beantragen, indem Sie uns eine E-Mail senden. Es liegt in Ihrer Verantwortung, Ihre aktuelle E-Mail-Adresse bei uns zu pflegen. Je nachdem, in welchem Bundesstaat oder Land Sie wohnen, haben Sie möglicherweise zusätzliche Rechte. Weitere Informationen finden Sie unten.

6\. ENTWICKLER, DIE PLUGSHARE-PLATTFORMDIENSTE NUTZEN
=====================================================

Wir arbeiten mit Dritten zusammen und gestatten Dritten, die Entwicklerplattform von PlugShare zu nutzen, um Dienste und Funktionen in Verbindung mit PlugShare anzubieten. Diese externen Entwickler haben entweder eine Vereinbarung zur Nutzung der PlugShare-Plattformtechnologie ausgehandelt oder haben unseren Self-Service-Application-Programming-Schnittstellen („API“) und Plug-in-Bedingungen zugestimmt, um Softwareplattformanwendungen („Plattformanwendungen“) zu erstellen. Sowohl die ausgehandelten Vereinbarungen als auch unsere API- und Plug-in-Nutzungsbedingungen enthalten Einschränkungen darüber, wie Dritte auf die personenbezogenen Daten, die Sie PlugShare zur Verfügung stellen, zugreifen, diese speichern und verwenden dürfen. Wenn Sie sich für die Nutzung einer Plattformanwendung entscheiden, werden Sie gebeten, die Zustimmung zur Datenschutzrichtlinie und Benutzervereinbarung des Drittanbieters zu bestätigen. Um die für eine Plattformanwendung gewährte Berechtigung zu widerrufen, besuchen Sie bitte Ihre Einstellungen. Beachten Sie jedoch, dass Ihre Verbindungen, selbst wenn Sie die für eine Plattformanwendung erteilte Erlaubnis widerrufen, die Plattformanwendung weiterhin verwenden können, sodass die Plattformanwendung weiterhin Zugriff auf bestimmte Informationen über Sie haben kann, genau wie Ihre Verbindungen.

7\. AUFBEWAHRUNG PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN
========================================

Der Zeitraum, für den wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten aufbewahren, hängt von den Zwecken ab, für die wir sie verwenden. Wir werden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten so lange aufbewahren, wie Ihr Konto aktiv ist, oder solange Sie ein registrierter Kontoinhaber oder Nutzer unserer Dienste sind oder solange wir einen anderen Geschäftszweck dafür haben (z. B. aber nicht beschränkt auf für Unternehmen, Steuer oder rechtliche Zwecke) und danach, nicht länger als gesetzlich vorgeschrieben oder zulässig, oder unsere Richtlinie zur Aufbewahrung von Unterlagen, vernünftigerweise für interne Berichts- und Abstimmungszwecke erforderlich, oder um Ihnen Feedback oder Informationen zu geben, die Sie anfordern könnten. Dieser Aufbewahrungszeitraum unterliegt unserer Prüfung und Änderung. Wir können anonymisierte personenbezogene Daten so lange aufbewahren, wie wir es für angemessen halten.

Nach der Kündigung oder Deaktivierung Ihres Benutzerkontos können wir Ihre Profilinformationen und alle Informationen, die in öffentlichen Bereichen der Websites veröffentlicht werden, aufbewahren. Nach der Kündigung oder Deaktivierung Ihres Benutzerkontos können wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und andere Daten aufbewahren, werden diese jedoch gemäß den Bedingungen, dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie und den Anforderungen des geltenden Rechts vertraulich behandeln. Wir haben das Recht, alle Ihre personenbezogenen Daten und andere Daten nach der Kündigung Ihres Benutzerkontos ohne vorherige Ankündigung zu löschen.

8\. KEINE ABSICHTLICHE ERHEBUNG VON DATEN VON KINDERN
=====================================================

Wir erheben, erfragen oder speichern wissentlich keine personenbezogenen Daten von Personen unter 18 Jahren und gestatten diesen Personen wissentlich nicht, sich für unsere Dienste zu registrieren oder diese zu nutzen. Wenn Sie unter 18 Jahre alt sind, senden Sie uns bitte keine personenbezogenen Daten. Sollten wir erfahren, dass wir personenbezogene Daten von einem Kind unter 18 Jahren ohne Überprüfung der elterlichen Einwilligung erhoben haben, werden wir alle wirtschaftlich vertretbaren Anstrengungen unternehmen, um diese Daten aus unserer Datenbank zu löschen.

9\. WO PERSONENBEZOGENE DATEN VERARBEITET UND GESPEICHERT WERDEN; GELTENDES RECHT
=================================================================================

Wir haben unseren Hauptsitz in den Vereinigten Staaten. Die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir oder unsere Dienstleister erheben, können auf Servern innerhalb oder außerhalb der Vereinigten Staaten und überall dort gespeichert und verarbeitet werden, wo wir und unsere Dienstleister Einrichtungen auf der ganzen Welt haben, und bestimmte Informationen können für Personen oder Unternehmen außerhalb der Vereinigten Staaten zugänglich sein, die Dienstleistungen für uns erbringen. Sie willigen in die Übertragung und/oder Übertragung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten durch uns und unsere Dienstleister in Rechtsordnungen ein, die möglicherweise kein gleichwertiges Datenschutzniveau bieten wie Ihr Heimatland. Wir werden angemessene Maßnahmen ergreifen, um sicherzustellen, dass Ihre personenbezogenen Daten in den Ländern, in denen wir sie verarbeiten, ein angemessenes Schutzniveau erhalten.

Es gelten die US-Gesetze, sofern Sie in den Vereinigten Staaten ansässig sind. Andernfalls werden diese Datenschutzrichtlinie und alle anderen Angelegenheiten in Übereinstimmung mit den Gesetzen der Provinz/des Bundesstaates und der Bundesländer des Landes, in dem Sie wohnen, interpretiert und ausgelegt. Gerichtsbarkeiten außerhalb Ihres Wohnsitzes können andere Datenschutzgesetze als die in Ihrem Land haben, einschließlich des Rechts auf Strafverfolgung und Regierungsbehörden, auf die personenbezogenen Daten zuzugreifen. Soweit wir Daten außerhalb Ihres Landes verarbeiten, führen wir eine Datenschutz-Folgenabschätzung durch, um festzustellen, dass unsere Dienstleister im Wesentlichen das gleiche Schutzniveau bieten können, wie es in Ihrer Gerichtsbarkeit erforderlich ist, und schließen Verträge ab, um die Verpflichtungen zur angemessenen Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten weiter zu stärken.

10\. SICHERHEIT
===============

Wir haben technische und organisatorische Sicherheitsvorkehrungen getroffen, die Ihre personenbezogenen Daten vor versehentlichem Verlust und vor unbefugtem Zugriff, unbefugter Verwendung, Vernichtung, Änderung und Offenlegung schützen sollen. Bitte beachten Sie jedoch, dass das Internet keine zu 100 % sichere Umgebung ist. Es liegt in Ihrer Verantwortung, die Sicherheit Ihrer Anmeldeinformationen zu schützen, bei der Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten über E-Mails, Instant Messaging und ähnliche Kommunikationsmittel vorsichtig zu sein und gute Internet-Sicherheitspraktiken aufrechtzuerhalten. Wir werden Sie niemals per E-Mail nach Ihrem Passwort oder anderen Anmeldedaten für Ihr Konto fragen. Wenn Sie eine solche E-Mail erhalten, senden Sie diese bitte an uns, damit wir die Angelegenheit untersuchen können.

11\. ZUSÄTZLICHE DATENSCHUTZRECHTE BETROFFENER PERSONEN FÜR EINWOHNER BESTIMMTER GERICHTSBARKEITEN, DIE IN DEN ERGÄNZENDEN DATENSCHUTZERKLÄRUNGEN BESCHRIEBEN SIND
==================================================================================================================================================================

Im Folgenden wird jedes Recht der betroffenen Person erläutert, das in den ergänzenden Datenschutzerklärungen beschrieben wird:

* Recht auf Erhalt von Informationen zu Datenschutzpraktiken: Sie haben das Recht, bestimmte gesetzlich vorgeschriebene Informationen am oder vor dem Zeitpunkt der Erhebung oder als Reaktion auf Ihre Anfrage zu erhalten.
* Recht auf Löschung: Sie können verlangen, dass wir alle personenbezogenen Daten über Sie löschen, die wir von Ihnen erhoben haben, vorbehaltlich bestimmter Ausnahmen.
* Recht auf Berichtigung: Sie können verlangen, dass wir alle ungenauen personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie aufbewahren, korrigieren.
* Recht auf Kenntnis: Sie können verlangen, dass wir Ihnen spezifische Informationen darüber bereitstellen, wie wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten gehandhabt haben, einschließlich der Bereitstellung einer Kopie der spezifischen personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erhoben haben, in einem tragbaren Format.
* Recht auf Nichtdiskriminierung: Sie haben das Recht, nicht diskriminiert zu werden, wenn Sie Ihre Rechte als betroffene Person ausüben. Das bedeutet, dass Sie keine Waren oder Dienste an Sie ablehnen, Ihnen unterschiedliche Preise oder Preise in Rechnung stellen oder ein anderes Qualitätsniveau für Produkte oder Dienste bieten, weil Sie Ihre Rechte als betroffene Person ausüben.
* Recht auf Abmeldung (Opt-Out): Sie können verlangen, den Verkauf und die Weitergabe Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten, kontextübergreifende verhaltensbezogene oder gezielte Werbung, automatisierte Entscheidungsfindung oder Profilerstellung abzulehnen, soweit solche Aktivitäten nach geltendem Recht definiert und eingeschränkt sind.
* Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung: Sie können von uns verlangen, die Verarbeitung einiger Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu unterdrücken oder einzustellen, aber wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten weiterhin speichern.
* Recht auf Einschränkung der Verwendung Ihrer sensiblen personenbezogenen Daten: Sie können verlangen, die Verwendung Ihrer sensiblen personenbezogenen Daten auf die nach geltendem Recht zulässigen Zwecke zu beschränken.
* Recht auf Einreichung einer Beschwerde: Sie haben das Recht, eine Beschwerde bei Ihrer lokalen Datenschutzbehörde einzureichen, wenn Sie der Ansicht sind, dass die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten in Bezug auf Sie Ihre Rechte verletzt.
* Recht auf Widerruf der Einwilligung. Soweit unsere Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten ausschließlich auf Ihrer Einwilligung beruht, können Sie diese Einwilligung jederzeit widerrufen.

12\. KONTAKTINFORMATIONEN
=========================

PlugShare hat einen Datenschutzbeauftragten als die Person ernannt, die die Einhaltung der Datenschutzanforderungen überwacht. Der Datenschutzbeauftragte von PlugShare kann unter der unten angegebenen Adresse kontaktiert werden, wenn es um Datenschutzfragen geht.

Wenn Sie Fragen oder Anmerkungen zu dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie oder unseren Datenschutzpraktiken haben, kontaktieren Sie uns bitte unter: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 USA; Attn: Data Protection Officer; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

DATENSCHUTZERKLÄRUNG FÜR EINWOHNER BESTIMMTER US-BUNDESSTAATEN
==============================================================

Wenn Sie Ihren Wohnsitz in Kalifornien, Virginia, Colorado, Utah oder Connecticut haben (hier gelegentlich als „Verbraucher“ bezeichnet), bieten Ihnen die Landesgesetze zusätzliche Rechte in Bezug auf unsere Nutzung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten.

KALIFORNISCHES GESETZ „SHINE THE LIGHT“
---------------------------------------

Abschnitt 1798.83 des kalifornischen Zivilgesetzbuchs (California Civil Code), bekannt als das „Shine-The-Light“-Gesetz, gestattet es allen Benutzern, die in Kalifornien ansässig sind, eine Liste der personenbezogenen Daten (falls vorhanden), die wir im vorangegangenen Kalenderjahr an Dritte für Direktmarketingzwecke weitergegeben haben, sowie die Namen und Adressen dieser Dritten anzufordern und von uns zu erhalten. Anträge können nur einmal jährlich gestellt werden und sind kostenlos.

KALIFORNISCHES ONLINE-DATENSCHUTZGESETZ („CALOPPA“; CALIF. BUS. und PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, [HIER](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D) [](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D)[VERFÜGBAR](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D))
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA gilt nur für Unternehmen, die personenbezogene Daten von Einwohnern Kaliforniens erheben.

1. WIE WIR AUF „DO NOT TRACK“-SIGNALE REAGIEREN.

Einige Webbrowser übermitteln ein „Do Not Track“(DNT/GPC)-Signal an die Websites und andere Online-Dienste, die Sie über diesen Webbrowser nutzen. Es gibt bis dato keine einheitlichen Vorschriften dafür, wie, wenn überhaupt, Websites auf dieses Signal reagieren sollten; wir selbst haben jedoch Maßnahmen eingeführt, die bei Empfang eines solchen Signals umgesetzt werden.

2. VERHALTENSTRACKING DURCH DRITTE

Wir können diese Technologien auch verwenden, um Informationen über Ihre Online-Aktivitäten im Laufe der Zeit und über Websites Dritter oder andere Online-Dienste hinweg zu erheben oder personenbezogene Daten mit anderen auf diese Weise erhobenen Informationen zu verknüpfen. Wir können personenbezogene Daten verwenden, um die Klick- und Browsing-Muster der Benutzer zu verfolgen.

KALIFORNISCHES GESETZ ZUM SCHUTZ DER PRIVATSPHÄRE DER VERBRAUCHER (CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT) VON 2018 („CCPA“, [HIER](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.-jaYyHU_NGLTJkjNOiEJ) [](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.-CgrpbnaQ_)[VERFÜGBAR](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) UND DEREN NACHFOLGER, DAS CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT VON 2020 („CPRA“, [HIER](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-0O7lm28) [](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-onT2yKX5fwMvDDO)[VERFÜGBAR](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-HWpnRo6-Y01-QM_lB9)).
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Die folgende Tabelle beschreibt, wie wir personenbezogene Daten, die wir über Sie erhoben haben, offenlegen:

| Kategorie | Kategorien nicht verbundener Dritter, denen wir personenbezogene Daten offenlegen | Kategorien nicht verbundener Dritter, an die wir personenbezogene Daten verkaufen oder weitergeben |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifikatoren | Anbieter von Datenspeicherung oder Hosting<br><br>Anbieter von Identitätsmanagement<br><br>Anbieter von Zahlungslösungen<br><br>Anbieter von Umfragen und Forschung<br><br>Werbepartner, einschließlich Social-Media-Anbieter | n. z. |
| Demografische Daten | Anbieter von Umfragen und Forschung | n. z. |
| Kommerzielle Informationen | n. z. | n. z. |
| Internet- oder andere elektronische Netzwerkaktivitäten; Geräteinformationen | Anbieter von Datenspeicherung oder Hosting<br><br>Datenbank- und Software-Dienstleister<br><br>Anbieter von Identitätsmanagement<br><br>Werbepartner, einschließlich Social-Media-Anbieter | n. z. |
| Geolokalisierung | Anbieter von Datenspeicherung oder Hosting<br><br>Datenbank- und Software-Dienstleister<br><br>Werbepartner, einschließlich Social-Media-Anbieter | n. z. |
| Sonstiges | Anbieter von Datenspeicherung oder Hosting<br><br>Datenbank- und Software-Dienstleister<br><br>Anbieter von Umfragen und Forschung<br><br>Werbepartner, einschließlich Social-Media-Anbieter | Hersteller, Einzelhändler und Großhändler |

Sie können uns kontaktieren, um die folgenden Rechte gemäß CCPA und CPRA auszuüben (Beschreibungen dieser Rechte finden Sie in Abschnitt 11 unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie):

1. Recht auf Erhalt von Informationen zu Datenschutzpraktiken.
2. Recht, Folgendes zu wissen:

* Die Kategorien von personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erhoben haben.
* Die Kategorien von Quellen für die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erhoben haben.
* Unser geschäftlicher oder kommerzieller Zweck für die Erhebung dieser personenbezogenen Daten.
* Die Kategorien von Dritten, an die wir diese personenbezogenen Daten weitergeben.
* Die spezifischen personenbezogenen Daten, die wir über Sie erhoben haben (auch als Datenübertragbarkeitsanfrage bezeichnet) und Ihnen eine Kopie in elektronischer oder Papierform zur Verfügung stellen.
* Wenn wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten für einen Geschäftszweck offengelegt haben, eine Liste, die Offenlegungen für einen Geschäftszweck offenlegt und die Kategorien personenbezogener Daten identifiziert, die jede Empfängerkategorie erhalten hat.

3. Recht auf Löschung.
4. Recht auf Berichtigung.
5. Recht auf Abmeldung (Opt-Out) von kontextübergreifender verhaltensbezogener Werbung, dem Verkauf oder der Weitergabe personenbezogener Daten, der Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten für Profiling und der automatisierten Entscheidungsfindung.
6. Recht auf Einschränkung der Verwendung Ihrer sensiblen personenbezogenen Daten. Bitte beachten Sie, dass wir sensible personenbezogene Daten über Sie ausschließlich für gemäß CCPA oder CPRA zulässige Zwecke verwenden.

VIRGINIA-VERBRAUCHERDATENSCHUTZGESETZ (VCDPA), COLORADO-DATENSCHUTZGESETZ (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), UTAH-VERBRAUCHERDATENSCHUTZGESETZ (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) UND CONNECTICUT-DATENSCHUTZGESETZ (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Sie können sich mit uns in Verbindung setzen, um die folgenden Rechte nach diesen landesspezifischen Gesetzen auszuüben:

1. Recht auf Erhalt von Informationen zu Datenschutzpraktiken.
2. Recht auf Kenntnisnahme.
3. Recht auf Löschung.
4. Recht auf Berichtigung.
5. Recht auf Abmeldung (Opt-Out) von gezielter Werbung oder dem Verkauf personenbezogener Daten.
6. Recht auf Abmeldung von Profiling (automatisierte Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten zwecks Analyse oder Vorhersage der Merkmale oder des künftigen Verhaltens einer Einzelperson, die zu Entscheidungen führt, die die materiellen Rechte der Person betreffen).
7. Verbraucher aus Virginia, Colorado und Connecticut haben außerdem das Recht, gegen unsere Entscheidungen über ihre Datenanfragen Einspruch zu erheben, indem sie sich auf demselben Weg an uns wenden, auf dem sie eine Anfrage stellen. Bitte fügen Sie eine Kopie unserer Entscheidung über Ihre Anfrage bei oder verweisen Sie anderweitig ausdrücklich auf diese, damit wir Ihren Einspruch angemessen bearbeiten können. Wir werden auf Ihre Beschwerde in Übereinstimmung mit dem geltenden Recht antworten.

NEVADA
------

Wie oben beschrieben, können wir Ihre Kennungen oder andere identifizierende Informationen, die wir von unseren Websites und Online-Diensten erheben, an nicht verbundene Parteien zum Zwecke der kontextübergreifenden Verhaltensverfolgung im Sinne des Gesetzes von Nevada verkaufen. Sie haben das Recht, den Verkauf oder die Lizenzierung dieser Kategorien von personenbezogenen Daten über Sie an nicht verbundene Parteien abzulehnen.

AUSÜBUNG VON RECHTEN
--------------------

Um die oben beschriebenen Rechte auf Zugriff, Berichtigung, Datenübertragbarkeit und Löschung auszuüben, stellen Sie bitte eine Anfrage an uns, indem Sie unser Webformular [hier](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form) verwenden. Nur Sie oder eine Person, die Sie bevollmächtigt haben, in Ihrem Namen zu handeln, können eine Anfrage in Bezug auf Ihre personenbezogenen Daten stellen. Sie können auch im Namen Ihres minderjährigen Kindes eine Anfrage stellen. Wenn wir von einer Person eine Anfrage bezüglich der Ausübung von Rechten in Ihrem Namen erhalten, werden wir die Person um eine Kopie Ihrer unterzeichneten Erlaubnis zur Einreichung einer solchen Anfrage in Ihrem Namen bitten und wir werden Sie kontaktieren, um die Erteilung einer solchen Erlaubnis direkt von Ihnen bestätigen zu lassen. Sie können als Verbraucher nur zweimal innerhalb von 12 Monaten eine Anfrage auf Zugriff oder Datenübertragbarkeit stellen. Der überprüfbare Verbraucherantrag muss:

* Stellen Sie ausreichende Informationen zur Verfügung, die es uns ermöglichen, vernünftigerweise zu überprüfen, ob Sie die Person sind, über die wir personenbezogene Daten erhoben haben oder ob ein autorisierter Vertreter die Anfrage gestellt hat.
* Beschreiben Sie Ihre Anfrage mit ausreichenden Details, die es uns ermöglichen, sie richtig zu verstehen, zu bewerten und darauf zu reagieren.

Wir können Ihre Anfrage nicht beantworten oder Ihnen personenbezogene Daten zur Verfügung stellen, wenn wir nicht in der Lage sind, Ihre Identität oder Ihre Befugnis, die Anfrage zu stellen, zu überprüfen und zu bestätigen, dass sich die personenbezogenen Daten auf Sie beziehen. Wenn Sie eine Anfrage stellen, müssen Sie kein Konto bei uns erstellen. Wir werden personenbezogene Daten, die in einer Anfrage bereitgestellt werden, nur verwenden, um die Identität oder Befugnis des Antragstellers zu überprüfen, die Anfrage zu stellen.

Um wie oben beschrieben Ihr Recht auf Abmeldung von kontextübergreifender verhaltensbezogener Werbung, gezielter Werbung oder der Weitergabe personenbezogener Daten auszuüben, müssen Sie sich von der Plattform abmelden, über die diese Vorgänge stattfinden. Bitte beachten Sie, dass Ihre Abmeldeanfrage nur für das Gerät oder die Plattform gilt, über das/die Sie die Anfrage stellen. Das bedeutet, dass Sie evtl. mehrere Anfragen stellen müssen, um sich von diesen Verarbeitungsvorgängen geräte- oder plattformübergreifend abzumelden. Bitte klicken Sie:

* hier, um sich von Plugshare.com (Web-Plattform) abzumelden.
* hier, um sich von der PlugShare-iOS-App abzumelden.
* hier, um sich von der PlugShare-Android-App abzumelden.

### Verifizierungsprozess

Wenn Sie eine Anfrage auf Zugriff auf Ihre Daten oder auf deren Berichtigung oder Löschung oder auf Datenübertragbarkeit stellen, senden wir Ihnen innerhalb von 10 Werktagen eine E-Mail an die E-Mail-Adresse, die wir für Sie hinterlegt haben. In der E-Mail werden Sie gebeten, zu antworten, um Sie als den Verbraucher zu bestätigen, der die Anfrage stellt. Nach Erhalt Ihrer Verifizierung werden wir Ihre Daten mit den Daten in unserer Akte abgleichen. Nach der Überprüfung Ihrer Identität werden wir Ihre Anfrage bearbeiten und innerhalb von 45 Kalendertagen antworten, es sei denn, dass (a) wir Ihre Anfrage nicht verifizieren können, (b) wir nicht in der Lage sind, Sie mit Informationen in unserer Datenbank zu verbinden, oder (c) eine gesetzliche Ausnahme besteht, die uns von der Erfüllung Ihrer Anfrage befreit. Wenn wir mehr Zeit benötigen (bis zu weiteren fünfundvierzig (45) Kalendertagen), werden wir Sie schriftlich über den Grund und den Verlängerungszeitraum informieren.

Wenn wir einer Anfrage nicht nachkommen können, werden wir Ihnen in der Antwort, die wir Ihnen übermitteln, die Gründe dafür erläutern. Bei Anfragen zur Datenübertragbarkeit werden wir ein Format für die Bereitstellung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten wählen, das leicht zu verwenden ist und es Ihnen ermöglichen sollte, die Daten ungehindert von einer Stelle zu einer anderen Stelle zu übermitteln.

Wir erheben keine Gebühr für die Bearbeitung oder Beantwortung Ihrer nachprüfbaren Verbraucheranfrage, es sei denn, dass sie exzessiv, wiederholt oder offensichtlich unbegründet ist. Wenn wir zu dem Schluss gelangen, dass die Anfrage eine Gebühr rechtfertigt, werden wir Ihnen mitteilen, warum wir diese Entscheidung getroffen haben und Ihnen einen Kostenvoranschlag zukommen lassen, bevor wir Ihre Anfrage bearbeiten.

* * *

DATENSCHUTZERKLÄRUNGEN FÜR BESTIMMTE NICHT-US-LÄNDER
====================================================

ALLGEMEINE INFORMATIONEN
------------------------

1. ### IHRE SPEZIFISCHE EINWILLIGUNG ZUR VERARBEITUNG VON „SENSIBLEN“ ODER „BESONDEREN“ KATEGORIEN PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN

Gemäß den Datenschutzgesetzen einiger Länder gelten bestimmte Arten von personenbezogenen Daten als „sensible“ oder „besondere“ Kategorien von Informationen. Wir verarbeiten sensible oder besondere Datenkategorien nur selten, es sei denn, dass dies in Ihrem lebenswichtigen Interesse oder im Interesse einer anderen Person liegt. In allen anderen Fällen willigen Sie ausdrücklich darin ein, dass wir sensible oder besondere Kategorien personenbezogener Daten, wie in Abschnitt 1.2 unserer Hauptdatenschutzrichtlinie beschrieben, erheben, verarbeiten und aufbewahren, und willigen auch sonst in die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten in Übereinstimmung mit dieser Datenschutzerklärung ein.

2. ### UNSERE RECHTSGRUNDLAGEN FÜR DIE VERARBEITUNG PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN

Unsere Rechtsgrundlagen für die Erhebung und Nutzung der oben beschriebenen personenbezogenen Daten hängen von den betreffenden personenbezogenen Daten und dem spezifischen Kontext ab, in dem wir sie erheben. Im Allgemeinen erheben und verarbeiten wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten nur, wenn wir die personenbezogenen Daten benötigen, um Dienste für Sie zu erbringen, für die Sie einen Vertrag mit uns abgeschlossen haben, oder wenn die Verarbeitung in unserem berechtigten Interesse liegt und nicht durch Ihre Datenschutzinteressen oder Grundrechte und -freiheiten außer Kraft gesetzt wird, stützen wir uns auf Ihre Einwilligung, wenn wir gesetzlich dazu verpflichtet sind. In einigen Fällen können wir auch gesetzlich verpflichtet sein, personenbezogene Daten von Ihnen zu erheben oder anderweitig die personenbezogenen Daten benötigen, um Ihre lebenswichtigen Interessen oder die einer anderen Person zu schützen.

BERECHTIGTE INTERESSENGRUNDLAGE FÜR DIE ERHEBUNG PERSONENBEZOGENER DATEN: Die Erhebung und Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten kann für die Zwecke unserer berechtigten Interessen erforderlich sein. Zu diesen berechtigten Interessen können gehören:

* Betrugsprävention
* Gewährleistung der Netzwerk- und Informationssicherheit
* Hinweise auf mögliche kriminelle Handlungen oder Bedrohungen der öffentlichen Sicherheit, einschließlich der Verbesserung des Schutzes unserer Community vor Spam, Belästigung, Verletzung geistigen Eigentums, Kriminalität und Sicherheitsrisiken aller Art sowie der Durchsetzung von Rechtsansprüchen, einschließlich der Untersuchung möglicher Verstöße gegen unsere Nutzungsbedingungen
* wenn wir gesetzlichen Verpflichtungen nachkommen
* Verarbeitung von Daten von Mitarbeitern oder Besuchern, Mitgliedern, Teilnehmern oder Registranten
* die von Ihnen angeforderte Funktion oder Dienste auszuführen
* Bereitstellung unserer Dienste und ihrer Funktionalität für Sie, wenn eine solche Verarbeitung für die Zwecke der von uns oder unseren Dienstleistern im Zusammenhang mit den Diensten verfolgten berechtigten Interessen erforderlich ist
* Direktmarketing
* die relevante und angemessene Beziehung, die wir mit Ihnen haben
* Analysen, z. B. die Anzahl der Besucher, Seitenaufrufe, die Nutzung der Websites usw. zu bewerten, um zu verstehen, wie unsere Websites, Produkte und Dienste genutzt werden, um die Websites und/oder zukünftige Kommunikation zu optimieren und neue Dienste und Website-Funktionen zu entwickeln
* Aktualisierung Ihrer Informationen und Präferenzen
* Angebot und Verbesserung unserer Websites, Produkte und Dienste
* Durchsetzung von Rechtsansprüchen, einschließlich der Untersuchung potenzieller Verstöße gegen unsere Bedingungen

Zusätzlich zu den oben angegebenen Informationen gelten die folgenden Abschnitte nur für die Einwohner oder Bürger des besprochenen Landes oder der Region. Für die Zwecke der folgenden Abschnitte, sofern nicht ausdrücklich erwähnt, hat die Definition von „personenbezogenen Daten“ wie oben verwendet die Definition von personenbezogenen Daten, personenbezogenen Daten oder ähnlichen Begriffen, die gemäß den Datenschutzgesetzen dieses Landes oder dieser Region anwendbar sind. Im Falle eines Widerspruchs zwischen den nachstehenden Abschnitten und den vorstehenden Abschnitten haben die nachstehenden Abschnitte Vorrang.

DSGVO – DATENSCHUTZERKLÄRUNG FÜR EINWOHNER DES EUROPÄISCHEN WIRTSCHAFTSRAUMS (MEER), DES VEREINIGTEN KÖNIGREICHS UND DER SCHWEIZ
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### ÜBERSICHT

Die folgenden Bestimmungen gelten nur, wenn Sie im EWR, im Vereinigten Königreich oder in der Schweiz ansässig sind (in diesem Abschnitt aus Gründen der Übersichtlichkeit als die „EU-Region“ bezeichnet).

Für diese Einwohner erfolgt die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten in Übereinstimmung mit den Datenschutzrechten und -vorschriften, insbesondere (EU) 2016/679 des Europäischen Parlaments und des Rates vom 27. April 2016, bekannt als die Datenschutz-Grundverordnung oder die britische Datenschutz-Grundverordnung für Einwohner des Vereinigten Königreichs (zusammen „DSGVO“), und unsere Verarbeitung erfolgt in Übereinstimmung mit der DSGVO. Für die Zwecke der DSGVO sind wir der „Datenverantwortliche“ für personenbezogene Daten (in der DSGVO ([hier](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/) [](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)[verfügbar](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) als „personenbezogene Daten“ bezeichnet und definiert), die wir erheben, es sei denn, dass wir diese Daten im Auftrag eines „Datenverantwortlichen“ erheben und wir in damit ein „Datenverarbeiter“ sind. Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie gilt nicht für Websites, Anwendungen oder Dienste, die diese Datenschutzrichtlinie nicht anzeigen oder verlinken oder die eine andere Datenschutzrichtlinie anzeigen oder verlinken. Nur für Einwohner und Bürger der EU-Region gilt, soweit eine Definition in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie mit einer Definition gemäß der DSGVO im Widerspruch steht, die DSGVO-Definition.

Wir sorgen für einen angemessenen Schutz bei der Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Länder außerhalb der EU-Region durch eine oder mehrere der folgenden Methoden: (a) eine Reihe von Unternehmensvereinbarungen, die auf den Standardvertragsklauseln beruhen oder diese enthalten, (b) wir können uns auf die Angemessenheitsbeschlüsse der Europäischen Kommission über bestimmte Länder verlassen, (c) wir können Ihre Einwilligung in diese Datenübertragungen aus der EU-Region in die Vereinigten Staaten in andere Länder einholen, (d) wir können verbindliche unternehmensinterne Vorschriften erlassen, oder (e) soweit anwendbar, können wir uns auf Ausnahmeregelungen gemäß Artikel 49 der DSGVO für die Übermittlung und Weitergabe von personenbezogenen Daten, die von Personen in der EU-Region erhoben wurden, an die Vereinigten Staaten und andere Länder, die nach Ansicht der EU-Region keinen angemessenen Datenschutz bieten, berufen. In Bezug auf die Methode (e) können wir personenbezogene Daten mit Ihrer ausdrücklichen Einwilligung oder auf eine Weise, die Ihre Rechte und Freiheiten nicht überwiegt, an einen Dritten übermittelt, um einen Vertrag mit Ihnen zu erfüllen. Wenn diese personenbezogenen Daten nicht verarbeitet und übermittelt werden, können wir den Vertrag mit Ihnen nicht ausführen oder Sie haben keinen oder alle Vorteile und Funktionen, die mit Ihrer Transaktion verbunden sind.

Möglicherweise müssen wir Ihre Daten auch an andere Konzernunternehmen oder Dienstleister in Ländern außerhalb der EU-Region übermitteln. Dies kann der Fall sein, wenn unsere Server oder Lieferanten und Dienstleister ihren Sitz außerhalb der EU-Region haben oder wenn Sie unsere Produkte und/oder Dienste nutzen, während Sie Länder außerhalb dieser Gebiete besuchen.

Unsere Rechtsgrundlagen für die Erhebung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten werden besprochen .

2. ### IHRE DATENRECHTE GEMÄSS DSGVO.

Wenn Sie der DSGVO unterliegen, umfassen Ihre Rechte das Recht auf:

* Recht auf Kenntnisnahme.
* Recht auf Berichtigung.
* Recht auf Löschung.
* Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung. Sie haben das Recht, Widerspruch gegen Ihre personenbezogenen Daten einzulegen, die auf die folgenden Arten verwendet werden: (a) Verarbeitung auf der Grundlage berechtigter Interessen oder der Erfüllung einer Aufgabe im öffentlichen Interesse/der Ausübung von Amts wegen (einschließlich Profiling); (b) Direktmarketing (einschließlich Profiling); und (c) Verarbeitung für Zwecke der wissenschaftlichen/historischen Forschung und Statistik. Weitere Informationen finden Sie unten.
* Recht auf Abmeldung (Opt-Out). Sie haben das Recht, keiner ausschließlich auf automatisierter Verarbeitung, einschließlich Profiling, beruhenden Entscheidung unterworfen zu werden, die rechtliche Auswirkungen auf Sie hat oder Sie in ähnlicher Weise erheblich beeinträchtigt, mit Ausnahme der Ausnahmen, die gemäß den relevanten Datenschutzgesetzen gelten.
* Recht auf Einreichung einer Beschwerde. Wenn Sie Ihren Wohnsitz innerhalb des EWR haben, finden Sie eine Liste der nationalen Datenschutzbehörden [hier](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Wenn Sie Ihren Wohnsitz im Vereinigten Königreich haben, können Sie sich an das Information Commissioner's Office [hier](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/) [wenden.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Recht auf Widerruf der Einwilligung.

HINWEIS FÜR PERSONEN MIT WOHNSITZ IN BESTIMMTEN ANDEREN (NICHT US-AMERIKANISCHEN) LÄNDERN
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Die folgenden Angaben in diesem Abschnitt ergänzen die Informationen, die in unserer Hauptrichtlinie zum Datenschutz enthalten sind.

Wir respektieren die folgenden Rechte betroffener Personen für alle Einwohner außerhalb der USA:

* Recht auf Erhalt von Informationen zu Datenschutzpraktiken:

* unsere Identität und Kontaktinformationen,
* der spezifische Zweck unserer Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten,
* die Form und Dauer unserer Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten,
* Informationen über unsere Weitergabe und den Zweck der Weitergabe Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten,
* die Verantwortlichkeiten von Dritten, die Ihre personenbezogenen Daten verarbeiten, und
* Informationen über alle öffentlichen und privaten Rechtspersonen, an die wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten weitergegeben haben.

* Recht auf Kenntnis:

* Entscheidungen, die ausschließlich auf der Grundlage der automatisierten Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten getroffen werden.
* Zugriff auf Informationen über die personenbezogenen Daten, die wir erheben.

* Recht auf Berichtigung.
* Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung.
* Recht auf Widerruf der Einwilligung.

Jede Übersetzung dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie in eine andere Sprache als Englisch wird ausschließlich zu Informationszwecken bereitgestellt. Im Falle von Unstimmigkeiten ist die einzige rechtsgültige und verbindliche Version die englische Version dieses Dokuments.

1. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON ARGENTINIEN

Die von PlugShare implementierten technischen und organisatorischen Sicherheitsmaßnahmen würden auch die Regeln des argentinischen Datenschutzgesetzes (PDPA) 25.326 unterstützen, wie z. B. das Verbot jeglicher Sekundärnutzung der personenbezogenen Daten einer betroffenen Person und das Verbot der Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten in Länder, die kein angemessenes Schutzniveau bieten. PlugShare verwendet eine Datenübertragungs-/Verarbeitungsvereinbarung, um die Einhaltung der PDPA-Bestimmung 60-E/2016 zu unterstützen, die die grenzüberschreitende Übermittlung von personenbezogenen Daten regelt.

Einwohner Argentiniens haben (a) das Recht, Informationen über die Existenz und den Zweck solcher personenbezogenen Daten zu erhalten, und (b) das Recht auf Berichtigung und das Recht, die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten einzuschränken oder abzulehnen, wenn sie falsch, ungenau oder diskriminierend sind.

2. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON AUSTRALIEN

Wir können Ihre personenbezogenen Daten (wie nach australischem Recht definiert) verwenden und an Dritte weitergeben, die außerhalb Australiens, hauptsächlich in den Vereinigten Staaten, ansässig sind, wie in Abschnitt 9 unserer Hauptdatenschutzrichtlinie beschrieben. Sie erklären sich damit einverstanden und erkennen an, dass die Empfänger in Übersee den Datenschutzgesetzen ihrer lokalen Gerichtsbarkeit unterliegen und möglicherweise keinen Datenschutzverpflichtungen oder ähnlichen Grundsätzen wie den australischen Datenschutzgrundsätzen unterliegen. Sie unterliegen auch einem ausländischen Gesetz, das die Weitergabe von personenbezogenen Daten an eine dritte Partei, z. B. eine ausländische Behörde, erzwingen könnte. Sofern Sie uns nicht schriftlich etwas anderes mitteilen, wird davon ausgegangen, dass Sie in die Offenlegung personenbezogener Daten an Empfänger im Ausland durch uns eingewilligt haben. Sie haben die Möglichkeit, anonym zu bleiben, wenn Sie mit uns zu tun haben, oder bestimmte personenbezogenen Daten nicht an uns weiterzugeben. Dies kann jedoch bedeuten, dass wir möglicherweise daran gehindert werden, Ihnen unsere Dienste bereitzustellen.

Für Personen mit Wohnsitz in Australien sind Aktualisierungen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie wirksam, wenn wir Ihre ausdrückliche Einwilligung erhalten oder wenn wir bei der Ankündigung wesentlicher Änderungen (z. B. auf unseren Websites oder per E-Mail) eine Opt-Out-Möglichkeit anbieten.

3. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON BRASILIEN

Personen mit Wohnsitz in Brasilien haben das Recht, die folgenden Informationen zu kennen: ob Ihre Bereitstellung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an uns eine vertragliche Anforderung ist, oder wenn es irgendwelche Folgen hat, solche Daten nicht zur Verfügung zu stellen (die Antwort lautet „Nein“ für beide), Informationen zu automatisierten Entscheidungen (einschließlich Profiling), die wir durchführen (siehe Abschnitt 2.1 unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie), Sie haben das Recht, Ihre Einwilligung in die Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widerrufen, und, Ihre Zugriffsrechte für betroffene Personen (siehe unten).

Einwohner Brasiliens haben außerdem das: (a) Recht auf Kenntnisnahme, einschließlich des Rechts, eine Kopie dieser Informationen zu erhalten; (b) Recht auf Berichtigung; (c) Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung; (d) Recht auf Löschung; (e) Recht auf Informationen über die Datenschutzpraktiken der öffentlichen und privaten Stellen, mit denen Ihre personenbezogenen Daten geteilt wurden; und (f) Recht auf Einreichung einer Beschwerde bei der brasilianischen Datenaufsichtsbehörde (der ANPD).

4. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON KANADA (EINSCHLIESSLICH QUEBEC)

Unsere Datenschutzrichtlinie und unsere allgemeinen Praktiken sind so konzipiert, dass sie den kanadischen Datenschutzgesetzen entsprechen, einschließlich dem Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) und, falls zutreffend, Quebecs Datenschutzgesetz für den privaten Sektor, dem Schutz personenbezogener Daten im privaten Sektor (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Für alle Datenverarbeitungspraktiken, die nicht in angemessenem Zusammenhang mit den Zwecken stehen, für die Sie PlugShare kontaktiert haben, haben Sie das Recht, diese Datenverarbeitungspraktiken abzulehnen (einschließlich Marketing, Profilerstellung, verhaltensbezogene Werbung, Weitergabe an Dritte, die keine Dienstanbieter sind).

In Kanada ansässige Personen haben das Recht, die Verwendung personenbezogener Daten für Direktmarketingzwecke und andere Verarbeitungen abzulehnen, die nicht notwendig sind, um auf das zu reagieren, wofür Sie uns beauftragt haben.

5. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON HONGKONG

Wir verwenden Ihre personenbezogenen Daten für die folgenden Direktmarketingzwecke: (a) um mit Ihnen über unsere Produkte und Dienste und die unserer verbundenen Unternehmen zu kommunizieren; und (b) um Ihnen weitere Mitteilungen, Werbeaktionen oder andere Marketingmaterialien bezüglich unserer Websites, Produkte und Dienste und der unserer verbundenen Unternehmen zu senden. Ihre Einwilligung zu diesem Zweck wird zum Zeitpunkt Ihrer Übermittlung personenbezogener Daten (z. B. bei der Kontoerstellung, Veranstaltungsregistrierung usw.) an uns eingeholt.

6. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON MEXIKO

Zusätzlich zu den oben dargestellten Informationen haben Einwohner Mexikos das Recht, Informationen über die Datenschutzpraktiken zu erhalten, einschließlich (a) ob Ihre Bereitstellung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an uns eine vertragliche Anforderung ist oder ob es irgendwelche Folgen hat, wenn diese Daten nicht zur Verfügung gestellt werden (die Antwort lautet „Nein“ für beide), (b) Informationen über automatisierte Entscheidungsfindungen (einschließlich Profiling), die wir durchführen (die in Abschnitt 2.1 besprochen werden unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie), (c) wie lange sie aufbewahrt wird (siehe Abschnitt 7 unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie), (d) das Recht, die Einwilligung zur Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widerrufen, und, (e) Ihre Zugriffsrechte für betroffene Personen (siehe unten). Sie haben auch das Recht, die ausdrückliche Angabe der zu verarbeitenden sensiblen personenbezogenen Daten zu kennen.

Personen mit Wohnsitz in Mexiko haben außerdem: (a) das Recht, über die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten informiert zu werden, einschließlich der Information über die öffentlichen und privaten Einrichtungen, an die Ihre personenbezogenen Daten weitergegeben wurden, und der Erhalt einer Kopie dieser Informationen; (b) das Recht auf Berichtigung; (c) das Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung; und (d) das Recht auf Löschung.

7. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON SINGAPUR

Neben anderen Rechten haben Sie, wenn wir eine Niederlassung in Singapur haben, das Recht, dass Ihre personenbezogenen Daten, die wir besitzen, an eine andere Organisation übermittelt werden.

Die Personen oder Unternehmen, an die wir Ihre personenbezogenen Daten weitergeben und übermitteln, können sich außerhalb von Singapur befinden. Wir stellen sicher, dass die Empfänger der übermittelten personenbezogenen Daten in der Lage sind, den übermittelten personenbezogenen Daten einen Schutzstandard zu bieten, der mit den Schutzstandards des singapurischen Datenschutzgesetzes vergleichbar ist, indem wir schriftliche Datenübertragungsvereinbarungen (für Ü an Dritte) oder verbindliche Unternehmensregeln (für Übertragungen an unsere Tochtergesellschaften und andere mit uns verbundene Unternehmen) verwenden.

8. ### HINWEIS FÜR EINWOHNER VON TAIWAN

Personen mit Wohnsitz in Taiwan haben das Recht, Informationen über Datenschutzpraktiken zu erhalten.

Personen mit Wohnsitz in Taiwan haben zudem: (a) das Recht, über die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten informiert zu werden, einschließlich der Information über die öffentlichen und privaten Einrichtungen, an die Ihre personenbezogenen Daten weitergegeben wurden, und der Erhalt einer Kopie dieser Informationen; (b) das Recht auf Berichtigung; (c) das Recht auf Einschränkung oder Widerspruch gegen die Verarbeitung; und (d) das Recht auf Löschung.

Zusätzlich zu den oben dargestellten Informationen Personen mit Wohnsitz in Taiwan haben das Recht, bestimmte Informationen über die von uns erhobenen personenbezogenen Daten zu erhalten, einschließlich (a) ob Ihre Bereitstellung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten an uns eine vertragliche Anforderung ist oder ob es irgendwelche Folgen hat, wenn diese Daten nicht zur Verfügung gestellt werden (die Antwort lautet „Nein“ für beide), (b) Informationen über automatisierte Entscheidungsfindungen (einschließlich Profiling), die wir durchführen (die in Abschnitt 2.1 besprochen werden unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie), (c) wie lange sie aufbewahrt wird (siehe Abschnitt 7 unserer wichtigsten Datenschutzrichtlinie), (d) das Recht, die Einwilligung zur Verarbeitung Ihrer personenbezogenen Daten zu widerrufen, und, (e) Ihre Zugriffsrechte für betroffene Personen (siehe unten). Sie haben auch das Recht, die ausdrückliche Weise der zu verarbeitenden sensiblen personenbezogenen Daten zu kennen (wir erheben keine „sensiblen“ Daten).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) Das Colorado-Datenschutzgesetz tritt am 1. Juli 2023 in Kraft.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) Das Utah-Verbraucherdatenschutzgesetz tritt am 31. Dezember 2023 in Kraft.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) Das Connecticut-Datenschutzgesetz tritt am 1. Juli 2023 in Kraft.

POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDAD DE PLUGSHARE
===================================

FECHA DE ENTRADA EN VIGOR: 10 de julio de 2023
----------------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (“PlugShare”, “nosotros”, “nos” o “nuestro”) tiene el objetivo de crear una comunidad de apoyo de usuarios de vehículos eléctricos (“VE”) y proporcionar información de carga líder en el sector y una amplia gama de productos y servicios innovadores para ayudar a que la experiencia de conducción de vehículos eléctricos sea lo más fácil y gratificante posible. Esta Política de privacidad establece nuestras políticas sobre la recogida, uso, divulgación, retención y  transferencia de la Información personal (definida más adelante) que recogemos sobre usted (“usted” o “su”) a través de nuestras interacciones con usted mediante nuestros Sitios web ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); o [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); conjuntamente, “Sitios web”), los servicios correspondientes y nuestras aplicaciones móviles (conjuntamente “Servicios”), así como a través de interacciones con partes no afiliadas como nuestros proveedores que trabajan con nosotros para proporcionarle nuestros Servicios.

Lea detenidamente esta Política de privacidad. Si no desea que tratemos sus Datos personales, no nos los facilite; no obstante, es posible que no pueda beneficiarse de determinadas funciones de nuestros Servicios.

Su uso del Sitio web y nuestros Servicios también está sujeto en todo momento a nuestras Condiciones de uso, disponibles en [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) y actualizadas periódicamente (las “Condiciones”).

Esta Política de privacidad no se aplica a ningún sitio ni servicio no afiliado vinculado a, o desde, nuestros Sitios web o Servicios que no sean los de nuestros Proveedores de servicios, a nuestros canales o plataformas de redes sociales que los alojan, o a cualquier sitio o servicio recomendado o mencionado por nuestros Sitios web o Servicios o por nuestro personal.

Residentes de California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah y Connecticut: Consulte nuestro [Aviso de privacidad complementario para residentes de ciertos estados de EE. UU.](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) para obtener información adicional sobre nuestro tratamiento de su Información personal.

Residentes de otros países: Si reside en un país distinto de los Estados Unidos, consulte nuestra página web de Avisos de privacidad complementarios para determinados países no estadounidenses para obtener información adicional sobre nuestro tratamiento de su Información personal.

Trabajamos constantemente para mejorar nuestros Servicios, y es posible que también tengamos que cambiar esta Política de privacidad cada cierto tiempo. La Política de privacidad vigente en cada momento siempre estará en nuestros Sitios web. Tenga en cuenta la fecha de entrada en vigor de esta Política de privacidad y asegúrese de comprobar periódicamente si hay actualizaciones.

1\. QUÉ INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL RECOPILAMOS
========================================

1.1 QUÉ ES LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL
----------------------------------

Esta Política de privacidad cubre nuestro tratamiento de su información de identificación personal. Por lo general, “Información personal” se refiere a cualquier información no cifrada que identifique, se relacione, describa, sea capaz de asociarse o pueda vincularse, de modo razonable, con una persona en concreto, como, por ejemplo, su nombre, dirección postal, dirección de correo electrónico, número de teléfono, etc.

La Información personal no incluye su Información personal que haya sido anonimizada o agregada en las formas requeridas por las leyes aplicables para que la información ya no pueda usarse directamente o a través de otros medios disponibles con vistas a identificar a una persona (conjuntamente, “Información personal anonimizada”).

1.2 CATEGORÍAS DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL QUE RECOPILAMOS Y TRATAMOS
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Recogemos varias categorías de Información personal de usted y sobre usted como se resume en la siguiente tabla:

| Categoría | Datos específicos de Información personal |
| --- | --- |
| Identificadores | * nombre y apellidos<br>* nombre de usuario (que puede incluir nombre y apellidos)<br>* dirección de correo electrónico<br>* código postal<br>* sexo, género<br>* identificador personal único, p. ej., nombre o número de cliente o cuenta, número de teléfono, identificador de dispositivo móvil |
| Datos demográficos | * país de residencia |
| Información comercial | * historial y tendencias de compra de productos/servicios |
| Internet u otra actividad de red electrónica; información del dispositivo | * tipo y fabricante del dispositivo y su ID/UDID o código similar específico del dispositivo<br>* sistema operativo y plataforma<br>* resolución de pantalla<br>* nombre del proveedor de servicios de Internet o del operador de telefonía móvil, velocidad y tipo de conexión<br>* Dirección del protocolo de Internet (o IP), protocolo e información de secuencia<br>* cookies<br>* etiquetas de píxeles<br>* Dirección de control de acceso a medios (MAC, por sus siglas en inglés) de las páginas que ha visitado<br>* identificador de publicidad de dispositivo móvil<br>* tipo de navegador, idioma y versión<br>* Navegación por el sitio web, sesión, interacción e historial de búsqueda, material y páginas vistas, hora y fecha de acceso a los Sitios web, número de bytes transferidos, número de clics por visita, tiempo dedicado a una página, datos de clics y secuencia de clics, consultas realizadas, resultados de búsqueda seleccionados, comentarios realizados<br>* sello de fecha y URL de la última página web visitada antes de visitar nuestros Sitios web, y URL de la primera página visitada después de salir de nuestros Sitios web<br>* tipo de servicio solicitado<br>* encabezados de protocolo de transferencia de hipertexto, cliente de aplicación y banners de servidor |
| Geolocalización | * ubicación física y/o movimientos |
| Otro | * Datos de carga del VE, marca del vehículo, modelo y año<br>* Información facilitada por usted como parte de una respuesta de comentarios u otra consulta general realizada a través de nuestros Sitios web<br>* Inferencias extraídas de cualquiera de las informaciones enumeradas para crear un perfil sobre un consumidor que refleje sus preferencias, características, tendencias psicológicas, predisposiciones, comportamiento, actitudes, inteligencia, capacidades o aptitudes. |

1.3 DÓNDE RECOPILAMOS INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL
------------------------------------------

Podemos recoger Información personal directamente de usted a través de nuestros Servicios cuando usted:

* Nos proporciona Información personal al rellenar formularios web en nuestros Sitios web o hacer transacciones en tiendas (marcas matrices, subsidiarias y afiliadas). Esto incluye información proporcionada al crear una cuenta en línea, comprar nuestros Servicios, suscribirse a nuestros boletines electrónicos u otras comunicaciones, solicitarnos información, enviar o publicar material (cuando esté permitido) en nuestros foros, o interactuar con el servicio o la atención al cliente, informar de un problema con nuestros Sitios web, aplicaciones móviles o Servicios, o comunicarse de otro modo con nosotros.
* Se pone en contacto con nosotros. Esto incluye todos los registros y copias de su correspondencia con nosotros, como, por ejemplo, con nuestras oficinas o con el servicio o la asistencia al cliente o el envío por correo de un cheque.
* Se inscribe en un evento o nos informa de cualquier solicitud de accesibilidad u otro tipo de adaptación.
* Responde a encuestas que nosotros o nuestros Proveedores de servicios podríamos pedirle que complete con fines de investigación.
* Hace búsquedas en los Sitios web.
* Participa en programas de fidelización/bonificaciones.
* Solicita empleo.
* Utiliza dispositivos y redes para acceder a nuestros Servicios, como sincronizar su VE con nuestros Servicios.
* Utiliza ciertas funciones en nuestros Sitios web y aplicaciones móviles. Aunque los usuarios pueden acceder a funciones limitadas sin divulgar su Información personal, como navegar por estaciones de carga públicas sin una cuenta, recogemos Información personal cuando los usuarios crean una cuenta. Los usuarios pueden elegir usar solo su correo electrónico y contraseña para explorar los cargadores domésticos. Los usuarios también pueden optar por aprovechar las funciones mejoradas enviando, comentando, publicando o compartiendo Información Personal adicional con la comunidad. En términos generales, los usuarios eligen cuánta información quieren mostrar sobre sí mismos y pueden darse de baja en cualquier momento.

También podemos recoger Información personal de partes no afiliadas, lo que incluye:

* Proveedores de datos (p. ej., empresas que proporcionan datos demográficos y otra información sobre los consumidores)
* Aplicaciones móviles (marcas matrices, subsidiarias y afiliadas)
* Socios de marketing conjuntos
* Empresas o plataformas de publicidad en línea (por ejemplo, si usted vincula o conecta voluntariamente su perfil de redes sociales con nuestros Servicios).
* Proveedores de servicios de tramitación de pedidos y entrega
* Empresas de redes sociales
* Otros proveedores de servicios
* Respuesta a las ofertas de empleo
* Acciones del usuario en el sitio web / formulario web o aplicación
* Proveedores de verificación de empleo o verificación de antecedentes
* Permitirnos, a través de la configuración de su dispositivo o servicios de terceros, recibir datos de geolocalización para mostrar información local (por ejemplo, una estación de carga local) en nuestras aplicaciones móviles.

1.4 INFORMACIÓN RECOPILADA A TRAVÉS DE TECNOLOGÍAS AUTOMATIZADAS
----------------------------------------------------------------

A medida que navega e interactúa con nuestros Servicios, también podemos utilizar tecnologías de recogida automática de datos para recoger cierta información de su dispositivo, navegador u otras actividades de red, tal y como se describe en nuestra Política de cookies, disponible en [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Visita al sitio web e información del dispositivo. Recogemos información sobre sus visitas a nuestros Sitios web y el uso de nuestras Aplicaciones móviles, incluidos, entre otros, datos de tráfico, datos de geolocalización, registros y otros datos de comunicación, así como los recursos a los que accede y que utiliza en los Sitios web. Recogemos información sobre su ordenador, dispositivo móvil y conexión a Internet, incluida su dirección IP, sistema operativo, tipo de navegador, patrones de secuencia de clics (es decir, en qué hace clic en un sitio web), la URL del sitio web más reciente que visitó antes de visitar nuestros Sitios web, la cantidad de tiempo que pasó en nuestros Sitios web y las páginas que vio mientras estaba en nuestros Sitios web. Podemos obtener una estimación aproximada de su ubicación de su dirección IP cuando visita nuestros Sitios web. Para los usuarios de nuestras Aplicaciones móviles, también podemos recoger y mantener un historial de su información de ubicación precisa utilizando tecnologías Wi-Fi y/o Bluetooth, así como los identificadores de su dispositivo y las coordenadas GPS (p. ej., latitud/longitud). Si desea evitar la recogida de la información de su ubicación, ajuste su configuración en su dispositivo móvil para limitar el acceso de la aplicación móvil a la información de su ubicación.

Cuando utiliza nuestro sitio web, compartimos la información que recopilamos de usted, como su correo electrónico (en formato hash), dirección IP o información sobre su navegador o sistema operativo, con nuestros socios de identidad/proveedores de servicios. Estos socios devuelven un código de identificación en línea que podemos almacenar en nuestra cookie de origen para nuestro uso en publicidad en línea, en la aplicación y en varios canales, y se puede compartir con empresas de publicidad para habilitar la publicidad dirigida y basada en intereses. Para cancelar este uso, haga clic aquí ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Seguimiento del comportamiento. También podemos utilizar estas tecnologías para recoger información sobre sus actividades en línea a lo largo del tiempo y a través de sitios web de terceros u otros servicios en línea, o asociar Información personal con otra información recogida de esta manera.

Análisis de ubicación: nuestras Aplicaciones móviles y Sitios web de navegador móvil incluyen una funcionalidad (p. ej., para el envío de una reseña de un conductor sobre una instalación de carga) que nos permite identificar la ubicación de un conductor y la de la instalación de carga en que se encuentra actualmente un usuario. Recogemos información como la dirección IP, el ID del dispositivo y la geolocalización. Los usuarios de la Aplicación móvil pueden optar por utilizar las Aplicaciones móviles de forma anónima o iniciar sesión como usuario identificado, en cuyo caso se pueden utilizar los datos personales proporcionados al registrarse.

Para los usuarios de las Aplicaciones móviles, podemos solicitar permiso para acceder a cierta información desde su dispositivo móvil, incluida su lista de contactos, fotos y vídeos, así como micrófono y cámara. Es opcional que nos proporcione acceso a esta información. Sin embargo, es posible que ciertas funciones de las Aplicaciones móviles no funcionen de forma óptima si decide no darnos permiso. 

Balizas web. Las páginas de nuestros Sitios web y nuestros correos electrónicos pueden contener pequeños archivos electrónicos conocidos como balizas web (también denominados gifs transparentes, etiquetas de píxel y gifs de un solo píxel) que nos permiten, por ejemplo, contar  los usuarios que han visitado esas páginas o abierto un correo electrónico y para otras estadísticas relacionadas del sitio web (por ejemplo, registrar la popularidad de cierto contenido del sitio web y verificar la integridad del sistema y del servidor).

Seguimiento de píxeles. Además de utilizar cookies, los Sitios web pueden usar el “seguimiento de píxeles”. El seguimiento de píxeles implica el uso de etiquetas de píxeles que no son visibles para el usuario y constan de algunas líneas de código informático. El seguimiento de píxeles mide la eficacia de los anuncios y compila estadísticas de uso agregadas y específicas. Podemos acceder a estas etiquetas de píxeles para identificar actividades e intereses que nos permitan adaptar mejor nuestros Productos, Servicios y ofertas a sus intereses y necesidades. Por ejemplo, si visita usted nuestros Sitios web desde un anuncio en otro sitio web, la etiqueta de píxel permitirá al anunciante hacer un seguimiento y ver que su anuncio le trajo a usted a los Sitios web. Si visita usted nuestros Sitios web y le enlazamos a otro sitio web, también podremos observar que a usted se le envió a un sitio web de terceros y/o que usted ha efectuado transacciones con dicha web de terceros.

GIF. Podemos utilizar imágenes diminutas conocidas como GIF transparentes para realizar un seguimiento del comportamiento de los usuarios, incluidas estadísticas sobre quién abre nuestros correos electrónicos.

Dirección IP. Nuestros servidores (o los de nuestros proveedores de servicios) registran automáticamente cierta información de archivos de registro procedente de su navegador cuando accede a los Sitios web. Estos registros de servidor pueden incluir información como qué páginas de los Sitios web visitó, su dirección de protocolo de Internet (“IP”, por sus siglas en inglés), tipo de navegador y otra información sobre cómo interactúa con los Sitios web. Estos archivos de registro generalmente se eliminan periódicamente.

Métricas y análisis de terceros. Métricas y análisis de terceros, en ciertas páginas o características de los Servicios para ayudarnos a entender y analizar el tráfico de visitantes, medir la eficacia promocional y la eficacia de nuestras características, ofertas y campañas de marketing. También utilizamos estas herramientas para identificar errores, deficiencias y áreas de nuestras operaciones que necesitan mejoras, y para ver el rendimiento general y la clasificación de nuestra presencia en línea. Estas herramientas pueden almacenar cookies en su dispositivo a su discreción.

POLÍTICA Y AVISO DE COOKIES

Las tecnologías que utilizamos para la recogida automática de datos también incluyen cookies, como se describe a continuación.

Cookies del navegador

Las cookies del navegador son pequeños archivos colocados en el disco duro de su ordenador o dispositivo móvil. Pueden contener ciertos datos, incluidos, entre otros, el nombre del servidor que lo ha colocado allí, un identificador en forma de un número único y una fecha de caducidad (solo algunas cookies). Las cookies del navegador se gestionan mediante el navegador web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) en su ordenador o dispositivo móvil. En nuestros Sitios web se utilizan diferentes tipos de cookies que tienen diferentes fines.

Cookies esenciales

Las cookies esenciales son esenciales para permitirle navegar por nuestros Sitios web y utilizar sus funciones. Sin ellas, no funcionarán servicios como la cesta de la compra o la facturación electrónica.

Cookies de rendimiento

Las cookies de rendimiento recogen información sobre el uso de nuestros Sitios web, como qué páginas se consultan con más frecuencia. Esta información nos permite optimizar nuestros Sitios web y simplificar la navegación. Las cookies de rendimiento también permiten a nuestros afiliados y socios averiguar si usted ha accedido a una de nuestras páginas del Sitio web desde su sitio y si su visita ha llevado al uso o la compra de un Producto o Servicio en nuestros Sitios web, incluidas las referencias del Producto o Servicio comprado. Toda la información recogida por las cookies de rendimiento se agrega y, por lo tanto, es anónima.

Cookies de funcionalidad

Las cookies de funcionalidad permiten que nuestros Sitios web recuerden las elecciones que usted ha tomado al navegar. Por ejemplo, podemos almacenar su ubicación geográfica en una cookie para que se muestren los Sitios web correspondientes a su área. También podemos recordar sus preferencias, como el tamaño del texto, la fuente y otros aspectos personalizables de los Sitios web. Las cookies de funcionalidad también pueden realizar un seguimiento de los productos o vídeos consultados para evitar repeticiones La información recogida por estas cookies no puede utilizarse para identificarle y no puede controlar su actividad de navegación en sitios web que no nos pertenecen. Las cookies de funcionalidad nos permiten mostrar publicidad adaptada a usted en nuestros Sitios web, para comprender qué partes de nuestro contenido le interesan más y qué categorías de Productos o Servicios solicita. Algunos de nuestros proveedores de servicios pueden colocar cookies en nuestros Sitios web. Esas empresas también pueden proporcionarle la opción de impedir el uso de cookies en el futuro.

En cualquier momento, puede impedir o rechazar el uso futuro de determinadas cookies activando la configuración adecuada en su navegador para no aceptar cookies del navegador. Sin embargo, si lo hace, su experiencia en nuestros Sitios web puede verse afectada; por ejemplo, es posible que no pueda acceder a ciertas partes de nuestros Sitios web. A menos que haya ajustado la configuración de su navegador para que rechace las cookies, nuestro sistema emitirá cookies cuando dirija su navegador a nuestros Sitios web.

Cookies de almacenamiento local

Ciertas funciones de nuestros Sitios web pueden utilizar objetos locales almacenados para recoger y almacenar información sobre sus preferencias y navegación hacia,  desde y en los Sitios web. Las cookies de almacenamiento local no se gestionan con la misma configuración del navegador que se utiliza para las cookies del navegador.

También podemos combinar la Información personal que recogemos de usted fuera de nuestros Sitios web o Servicios con Información personal que se recoge a través de nuestros Sitios web o Servicios o por otros medios, tal y como se ha descrito anteriormente.

1.5 INFORMACIÓN DE DISPOSITIVO, RED, GEOLOCALIZACIÓN Y VE
---------------------------------------------------------

Cuando usted visita o sale de nuestros Sitios web o Servicios haciendo clic en un hipervínculo o ve un complemento en un sitio web de terceros, recibimos automáticamente la URL del sitio del que procede o al que se le dirige. Además, los anunciantes reciben la URL de la página en la que se encuentra cuando hace clic en cualquier anuncio que aparezca en nuestros Servicios. También recibimos la dirección de protocolo de Internet (“IP”) de su ordenador o del servidor proxy que utiliza para acceder a Internet, a los datos del sistema operativo de su ordenador, a su tipo de navegador web, a su dispositivo móvil (incluido el identificador de su dispositivo móvil proporcionado por el sistema operativo de su dispositivo móvil), a su sistema operativo móvil (si accede a nuestros sitios web o servicios mediante un dispositivo móvil) y al nombre del proveedor de servicios de internet (ISP, por sus siglas en inglés) o su proveedor de telefonía móvil.

1.6 ENCUESTAS
-------------

Nosotros o partes no afiliadas podemos realizar encuestas de usuario sobre nuestros Servicios. Algunas partes no afiliadas pueden enviarle publicidad o promociones en función de sus respuestas a la encuesta. Nosotros o las partes no afiliadas desarrollamos nuevos programas o productos basados en la información que usted comparte en las encuestas. Podemos utilizar partes no afiliadas a fin de ofrecerle incentivos financieros o de otro tipo para participar en encuestas. Si la entrega de incentivos requiere su información de contacto, es posible que se le pida que proporcione Información personal a la parte no afiliada que se encarga de la oferta de incentivos, y que se utilizará solo con el fin de entregar los incentivos prometidos y verificar su información de contacto. Usted es quien decide si facilita esa información o si desea aprovechar una oferta de incentivo. La parte no afiliada que se encargue de la encuesta le pedirá explícitamente su consentimiento para el uso de cualquier Información personal para los fines establecidos en la encuesta. Para darse de baja de nuestras encuestas, puede enviarnos su solicitud utilizando la información de contacto que aparece más adelante.

2\. NATURALEZA Y FINALIDAD DEL TRATAMIENTO DE LA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL
=====================================================================

Utilizamos la información que recogemos sobre usted o que nos proporciona, incluida cualquier Información personal, para uno o más de los siguientes fines:

* Para presentarle nuestros Sitios web y aplicaciones móviles y su contenido.
* Para proporcionarle información y responder a las preguntas sobre Productos o Servicios que nos solicite y darle información sobre nuevos productos y servicios, descuentos, promociones especiales o próximos eventos, así como características u ofertas que creemos que serán de su interés o en relación con una promoción, concurso o sorteo en el que haya participado
* Para tratar la información de la cuenta y los pagos de transacciones, incluidos, entre otros, los cargos por Productos y/o Servicios, y los pagos y reembolsos por cualquier Producto o Servicio comprado (aunque no recibimos su número completo de tarjeta de crédito o débito).
* Para tramitar descuentos, ofertas, recompensas de fidelidad y/o solicitudes de reembolso, formularios y solicitudes y coordinarse con el fabricante, minorista y/o mayorista.
* Para proporcionarle avisos sobre su cuenta, incluidos avisos de vencimiento y renovación.
* Para notificarle información sobre, o cambios en, nuestros Sitios web, nuestras políticas, términos o cualquier Producto o Servicio que ofrezcamos o proporcionemos, o con respecto a su cuenta.
* Para tratar Información personal u otra información que nos envíe.
* Para permitirle participar en funciones interactivas en nuestros Sitios web.
* Para mejorar nuestros Productos y Servicios y desarrollar otros nuevos, por ejemplo, analizando las tendencias de los usuarios y midiendo los datos demográficos y los intereses.
* Para el funcionamiento interno del sitio web, el servicio y el sistema, la administración, el mantenimiento, las auditorías y revisiones internas, el diagnóstico de problemas técnicos y el mantenimiento de la seguridad.
* Para investigar cualquier incumplimiento de nuestras Condiciones de uso o de esta Política de privacidad.
* Para realizar un seguimiento de posibles problemas y tendencias con el uso de nuestros Sitios web y Servicios por parte de los Usuarios y personalizar nuestro soporte para prestarle un mejor servicio.
* Para proporcionar estadísticas sobre los niveles de uso de los Sitios web y demás información relacionada con nuestros Proveedores de servicios.
* Para notificarle incidentes de privacidad de datos o proporcionarle la información legalmente exigida.
* Para solicitar su participación en evaluaciones, reseñas, encuestas, grupos muestra u otras iniciativas que nos ayuden a recoger información utilizada para desarrollar y mejorar nuestros Productos y Servicios.
* Para cumplir con cualquier otro fin para el que usted proporcione Información personal.
* De cualquier otra forma que describamos y para la que obtengamos su consentimiento cuando nos facilite la información.

Utilizamos cookies, gifs transparentes e información de archivos de registro para: (a) recordar información para que usted no tenga que volver a introducirla durante su visita o la próxima vez que visite los Sitios web; (b) proporcionar datos personalizados, contenido e información personalizados; (c) supervisar la eficacia de nuestros Servicios; (d) supervisar las métricas agregadas, como el número total de visitantes, tráfico y patrones demográficos; (e) diagnosticar o solucionar problemas tecnológicos notificados por nuestros usuarios o ingenieros asociados con determinadas direcciones IP; y/o, (f) ayudarle a acceder eficientemente a su información después de iniciar sesión.

Los datos estadísticos que recogemos automáticamente nos ayudan a mejorar nuestros Sitios web y a ofrecer Productos y Servicios mejores y más personalizados, lo que incluye, entre otras cosas, lo siguiente: calcular el tamaño de nuestra audiencia/visitantes y los patrones de uso, almacenar información sobre sus preferencias, lo que nos permite personalizar y mejorar nuestros sitios web, acelerar sus búsquedas y/o reconocerle cuando vuelve a nuestros sitios web.

Podemos recoger y utilizar la información de su sesión de carga de VE (p. ej., tiempo de carga, consumo de energía, propiedad y datos de la estación, etc.) y la marca, el modelo y el año de su vehículo para administrar su cuenta, como para distinguir entre múltiples vehículos o usuarios que comparten una sola cuenta, y con fines analíticos.

En la medida en que usted no dé su consentimiento a las prácticas de tratamiento de la información aquí establecidas, podrá tener derecho a excluirse de dichas prácticas. Todas las solicitudes de exclusión deben dirigirse a [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Las solicitudes de exclusión voluntaria tendrán efecto para el tratamiento futuro y no para el tratamiento que se haya producido sobre la base del consentimiento previo.

2.1 TOMA DE DECISIONES AUTOMATIZADA
-----------------------------------

Podemos utilizar la Información personal que nos proporcione y que obtengamos de otras fuentes para entender mejor sus intereses, de modo que podamos intentar predecir qué otros Productos, Servicios e información podrían interesarle más. Esta práctica implica tomar decisiones automatizadas sobre usted basadas en esta información con el fin de permitirnos adaptar mejor nuestras interacciones con usted para que sean más relevantes e interesantes. Puede oponerse a que lo hagamos en cualquier momento o solicitarnos más información sobre la metodología aplicada en nuestros procesos automatizados de toma de decisiones poniéndose en contacto con nosotros (véase la sección 12 más adelante).

2.2 MENSAJES DE TEXTO
---------------------

Nuestros Servicios pueden incluir el envío de mensajes de texto (“SMS”); usted puede recibir hasta dos mensajes por día en su dispositivo inalámbrico (a no ser que se comunique más con nosotros), pero la frecuencia de los mensajes puede variar.  Cuando da su consentimiento expreso para recibir mensajes de texto de nuestra parte y facilita un número de teléfono móvil, está dando su consentimiento expreso para recibir de forma recurrente mensajes de texto informativos y transaccionales de nuestra parte o en nuestro nombre al número que ha facilitado. Al dar su consentimiento expreso para recibir mensajes SMS de nuestra parte y facilitarnos un número de teléfono móvil, usted garantiza y declara que es el propietario del número de teléfono móvil que nos facilita. Podemos utilizar su información para ponernos en contacto con usted en relación con su uso, compras, devoluciones (si están disponibles), actualizaciones del Sitio web, realización de encuestas o comunicaciones informativas y relacionadas con el servicio, incluidas actualizaciones de seguridad importantes. Después de que nos envíe el mensaje SMS “STOP”, le enviaremos un mensaje SMS para confirmar que se ha dado de baja. Como alternativa, puede enviarnos su solicitud por correo electrónico, incluida la dirección de correo electrónico y el número de teléfono que registró con nosotros, o por cualquier medio que considere oportuno. A partir de ese momento, dejará de recibir nuestros mensajes SMS. Si quiere volver a participar, basta con que se registre como la primera vez y empezaremos a enviarle mensajes SMS de nuevo Para obtener ayuda, responda a un texto con AYUDA. Es posible que se le apliquen las tarifas correspondientes a mensajes y datos, según su plan de telefonía móvil. Los operadores no son responsables de mensajes con retraso o no entregados.

2.3 COMPLEMENTOS PARA REDES SOCIALES
------------------------------------

Integramos interfaces o complementos de programas de aplicaciones de redes sociales (“Complementos”) de redes sociales, incluidas Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest y/u posiblemente otras empresas, en los Sitios web. Para registrarse como usuario con nosotros, es posible que tenga la opción de iniciar sesión utilizando su inicio de sesión de Facebook u otro sitio de redes sociales.

Por ejemplo, cuando visita nuestros Sitios web, el complemento crea una conexión directa entre su navegador y el servidor de Facebook. Esto permite a Facebook recibir información sobre su visita a nuestros Sitios web con su dirección IP. Si hace clic en el botón “Me gusta” de Facebook mientras inicia sesión en su cuenta de Facebook, puede vincular el contenido de nuestros Sitios web a su perfil de Facebook. Esto permite a Facebook asignar su visita a nuestros Sitios web a su cuenta de usuario. Tenga en cuenta que, como proveedor de los Sitios web, no recibimos ninguna notificación sobre el contenido de los datos transmitidos o su uso por parte de Facebook. Si no quiere que Facebook asigne su visita a nuestros Sitios web a su cuenta de usuario de Facebook, cierre sesión en su cuenta de usuario de Facebook.

Si inicia sesión a través de un Complemento de redes sociales, nos autoriza a acceder a cierta información de cuenta desde ese sitio de redes sociales, como su perfil público en las redes sociales (de acuerdo con su configuración de privacidad en el sitio de las redes sociales), su dirección de correo electrónico, intereses, sus “me gusta”, género, cumpleaños, estudios, relaciones, intereses, ciudad actual, fotos, descripción personal, lista de amigos, e información y fotos de sus amigos de redes sociales que podrían ser amigos en común de redes sociales con otros usuarios. Los Complementos pueden transferir información sobre usted a la plataforma respectiva del Complemento sin que usted actúe. Esta información puede incluir su número de identificación de usuario de la plataforma, o en qué sitio web se encuentra, entre otros. Interactuar con un Complemento transmitirá información directamente a la red social de ese Complemento y esa información puede ser visible para otros en esa plataforma. Los Complementos se rigen por la política de privacidad del sitio de la red social correspondiente (disponible en su sitio web), y no por nuestra Política de privacidad.

3\. CÓMO DIVULGAMOS INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL A PARTES NO AFILIADAS
==============================================================

3.1 TIPOS DE PARTES NO AFILIADAS
--------------------------------

Podemos divulgar su Información personal, en su totalidad o en parte, a los siguientes tipos de partes no afiliadas, y para uno o más de los siguientes fines:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Tipo de parte no afiliada | Fin |
| Proveedores de almacenamiento o alojamiento de datos | almacenamiento seguro y transmisión de sus datos |
| Proveedores de servicios de bases de datos y software | gestión y seguimiento de sus datos |
| Asesores jurídicos y fiscales, como asesores externos, auditores externos o asesores fiscales | Proporcionarnos servicios profesionales |
| Proveedores de gestión de identidad | fines de autenticación |
| Proveedores de soluciones de pago | procesamiento seguro de los pagos que nos proporcione |
| Fabricantes, minoristas y mayoristas | envío, procesamiento y gestión de reembolsos, descuentos, ofertas, bonificaciones de fidelidad y similares |
| Proveedores de cumplimiento y envío | tramitación de pedidos y entrega de Productos, Servicios y mercancía |
| Proveedores de encuestas e investigaciones | realizar estudios en nuestro nombre |
| Socios publicitarios, incluidos proveedores de redes sociales | entrega de anuncios dirigidos |

Para cualquier transferencia de Información personal que no sea necesaria para lograr los fines para los que usted interactúa con PlugShare (como para fines de marketing o encuestas), usted tiene derecho a optar por no participar en dicho tratamiento. Para ejercer su derecho de exclusión, póngase en contacto con nosotros en [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 PROVEEDORES DE SERVICIOS, SOCIOS COMERCIALES Y SUBCONTRATISTAS
------------------------------------------------------------------

 Podemos compartir su Información personal con Proveedores de servicios que prestan servicios en nuestro nombre, como se ha mencionado anteriormente. Estos Proveedores de servicios pueden tener acceso a su Información personal para proporcionarnos estos servicios a nosotros o en nuestro nombre. Si contratamos a Proveedores de servicios para cualquiera de los casos anteriores, el uso de la Información personal suya estará sometido a obligaciones de confidencialidad y el uso que hagan los Proveedores de la Información personal se limitará a la prestación de sus servicios en beneficio nuestro. Podemos almacenar Información personal en ubicaciones fuera de nuestro control directo (por ejemplo, en servidores o bases de datos ubicadas o coubicadas con Proveedores de servicios de alojamiento de datos).  

3.3 PUBLICIDAD CONDUCTUAL EN CONTEXTOS CRUZADOS
-----------------------------------------------

Estamos obligados a divulgar si compartimos Información personal con un tercero que participa en publicidad de comportamiento (dirigida) en contextos cruzados. En los doce (12) meses anteriores, hemos divulgado o puede que hayamos divulgado las siguientes categorías de Información personal en un contexto que, según ciertas leyes (p. ej., la CPRA de California, el RGPD o el RGPD del Reino Unido) puede considerarse una venta:

* Identificadores
* Internet u otra actividad de red similar
* Datos de geolocalización

Usted tiene la posibilidad de excluirse de este intercambio haciendo clic en las indicaciones de exclusión que aparecerán en el aviso que se le envía cuando visite por primera vez nuestras aplicaciones móviles o Sitios web.

3.4 TRANSFERENCIAS COMERCIALES
------------------------------

Usted reconoce (y no se opondrá a) nuestra divulgación o transferencia de su Información personal, Información personal anonimizada, y demás información que nos proporcione, así como los derechos que ha otorgado o reconocido en esta Política de privacidad (conjuntamente, “Información transferida”) en favor de un comprador potencial o real de nuestra empresa u otro sucesor con el fin de considerar o someterse a una fusión, desinversión, reestructuración, reorganización, disolución, cambio de control, o transferencia de algunos o todos nuestros activos (denominándose cada una de las anteriores eventualidades, una “Transferencia”), ya sea como empresa en operación o como parte de un proceso concursal, de liquidación u otro procedimiento judicial, en el que la Información personal que tenemos se encuentre entre los activos transferidos, y usted acepta no oponerse a dicha divulgación y/o transferencia. No podemos hacer ninguna declaración con respecto al uso o transferencia de la Información transferida que tengamos en caso de concurso, reorganización, insolvencia, administración judicial o cesión en beneficio de acreedores. Además, excepto según lo exija la ley, no somos ni seremos responsables de ninguna violación de la seguridad de datos por parte de ninguna parte no afiliada ni de ninguna acción de parte alguna no afiliada que reciba Información transferida de la que se nos divulgue.

3.5 DIVULGACIONES REQUERIDAS; PROTECCIÓN DE DERECHOS; SEGURIDAD
---------------------------------------------------------------

Salvo que se describa lo contrario en esta Política de privacidad, no divulgaremos su Información personal a ninguna parte no afiliada a menos que lo exija la ley, una orden judicial o un proceso legal (p. ej., citación), incluyendo, entre otros, para responder a cualquier gobierno, órgano regulador o solicitud de licencia, o si creemos que dicha acción es necesaria para: (a) cumplir con la ley, cumplir con procesos legales que nos sean notificados a nosotros o a nuestras filiales, subsidiarias, proveedores contratados o socios afines, o investigar, prevenir o tomar medidas en relación con actividades ilegales supuestas o reales; (b) hacer cumplir nuestras Condiciones o el contrato del cliente (incluido a efectos de facturación y cobro); (c) tomar precauciones contra posibles responsabilidades; (d) investigar y defendernos contra cualquier reclamación o alegación de terceros; (e) ayudar a las agencias de cumplimiento del gobierno o cumplir con los requisitos de seguridad nacionales o de otro tipo; (f) proteger la seguridad o integridad de nuestros Sitios web, nuestros Servicios y aplicaciones móviles; o (g) ejercer o proteger los derechos, la propiedad o la seguridad personal nuestra, de nuestros usuarios o de terceros. 

Intentaremos informarle, cuando sea posible, de estas solicitudes a menos que: (i) la notificación esté prohibida por el propio proceso legal, por una orden judicial que recibamos o por la legislación aplicable, o (ii) creamos que informar sería inútil, ineficaz, crearía un riesgo de lesiones o daños físicos o de otro tipo a un individuo o grupo, o crearía o aumentaría un riesgo de fraude para nosotros, nuestros usuarios, nuestros Sitios web, Servicios o aplicaciones móviles. En los casos en que cumplamos con las solicitudes legales sin previo aviso por estas razones, intentaremos informar a ese usuario de la solicitud después del hecho si determinamos de buena fe que ya no se nos prohíbe legalmente hacerlo y no se aplican los escenarios de riesgo descritos en este párrafo.

3.6 DIVULGACIÓN DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL ANONIMIZADA
---------------------------------------------------

Podemos compartir información personal no identificable (incluidos, entre otros, datos de uso anónimos, páginas y URL de referencia/salida, dirección IP, tipos de plataforma, número de clics, etc.) con partes no afiliadas de la forma que elijamos y con cualquier fin, como la administración del sistema y la supervisión del uso de los Sitios web; la medición del número de visitas a nuestros Sitios web, el tiempo medio de permanencia, el número de páginas visitadas; y la supervisión de otras estadísticas del Sitio web para mejorar el contenido.

4\.  SOLICITUDES DE “NO RASTREAR”
=================================

Algunos navegadores web (incluidos Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox y Chrome) incorporan una función “No rastrear” (“DNT”, por sus siglas en inglés) o similar que indica a los sitios web que un usuario no desea que se realice un seguimiento de su actividad y comportamiento en línea. Si un sitio web que responde a una señal DNT en particular recibe la señal DNT, el navegador puede bloquear ese sitio web para que no recoja cierta información sobre el usuario del navegador. No todos los navegadores ofrecen una opción DNT y las señales DNT aún no son uniformes. Por este motivo, muchos operadores de sitios web, incluido PlugShare, no responden a las señales DNT.

5\. COMUNICACIONES DE PLUGSHARE, PREFERENCIAS Y BAJA VOLUNTARIA
===============================================================

Al proporcionarnos su dirección de correo electrónico, usted acepta que utilicemos la dirección de correo electrónico para enviarle avisos relacionados con el Servicio por correo electrónico, incluidos, entre otros, cualquier aviso que exija la ley (p. ej., aviso de incidentes de privacidad de datos o seguridad), en lugar de la comunicación por correo postal. También acepta que podemos enviarle notificaciones de actividad con respecto a nuestros Productos, Servicios, Sitios web, aplicaciones móviles, su Información personal o cualquier aspecto de nuestra relación, a la dirección de correo electrónico que nos proporcione, de acuerdo con cualquier configuración de privacidad aplicable. Podemos utilizar su dirección de correo electrónico para enviarle otros mensajes o contenido, como, entre otros, boletines informativos, adiciones o cambios en las funciones del Servicio u ofertas especiales. Si no desea recibir dichos mensajes de correo electrónico, puede optar por no recibirlos haciendo clic en Darse de baja cuando esté disponible. Si decide darse de baja, es posible que no reciba mensajes de correo electrónico sobre actualizaciones, mejoras, funciones especiales, anuncios u ofertas. No puede darse de baja de los correos electrónicos relacionados con el Servicio. Si ha elegido no facilitarnos un correo electrónico u otra dirección, es posible que no reciba nuestros correos electrónicos relacionados con el Servicio.

A través de la página de configuración de su cuenta de usuario, puede acceder y, en algunos casos, editar o eliminar cierta información que nos ha facilitado, como nombre y contraseña, dirección de correo electrónico, dirección postal, información de perfil de usuario, etc. La información que puede ver, actualizar y eliminar puede cambiar a medida que cambien los Productos, los Sitios web, los Servicios o nuestras prácticas. Si tiene alguna pregunta sobre cómo ver o actualizar la información que tenemos registrada sobre usted, póngase en contacto con nosotros. Sin embargo, cuando actualiza información, podemos conservar una copia de la información no revisada en nuestros registros. Puede solicitar la eliminación de su cuenta enviándonos un correo electrónico. Es responsabilidad suya que la dirección de correo electrónico que tenemos de usted esté actualizada. Dependiendo del estado o país en el que resida, puede tener derechos adicionales. Para más información, véase más abajo.

6\. DESARROLLADORES QUE UTILIZAN SERVICIOS DE PLATAFORMA PLUGSHARE
==================================================================

Colaboramos y permitimos que terceros utilicen la plataforma de desarrolladores de PlugShare para ofrecer servicios y funcionalidades junto con PlugShare. Estos desarrolladores externos han negociado un acuerdo para utilizar la tecnología de plataforma PlugShare o han aceptado nuestras interfaces de programación de aplicaciones (“API”, por sus siglas en inglés) y las condiciones de los Complementos para crear aplicaciones de plataforma de software (“Aplicaciones de plataforma”). Tanto los acuerdos negociados como nuestras condiciones de uso de API y Complementos contienen restricciones sobre cómo los terceros pueden acceder, almacenar y utilizar la Información personal que usted proporciona a PlugShare. Si decide utilizar una Aplicación de plataforma, se le pedirá que confirme la aceptación de la política de privacidad y el acuerdo de usuario del desarrollador externo. Para revocar el permiso otorgado a una Aplicación de plataforma, visite su configuración. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que incluso si retira el permiso otorgado a una Aplicación de plataforma, sus conexiones pueden seguir utilizando la Aplicación de plataforma, por lo que la Aplicación de plataforma puede seguir teniendo acceso a cierta información sobre usted, igual que sus conexiones.

7\. RETENCIÓN DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL
=====================================

El periodo de tiempo durante el cual conservamos su Información personal depende de los fines para los que la utilicemos. Conservaremos su Información personal mientras su cuenta esté activa, o siempre que usted sea titular de cuenta registrado o usuario de nuestros Servicios o mientras tengamos otro fin comercial para hacerlo (como, por ejemplo, entre otros, con fines comerciales, fiscales o legales) y, a partir de entonces, no más tiempo del exigido o permitido por la ley, o por nuestra política de conservación de registros, o el necesario a efectos de informes internos y conciliación, o para proporcionarle comentarios o información que solicite. Este periodo de retención está sujeto a nuestra revisión y modificación. Podemos retener Información personal no identificada durante el tiempo que consideremos apropiado.

Tras la terminación o desactivación de su cuenta de usuario, podemos retener su información de perfil y toda la información publicada en áreas públicas de los Sitios web. Tras la terminación o desactivación de su cuenta de usuario, podemos retener su Información personal y otros datos, pero la mantendremos como confidencial de acuerdo con las Condiciones, esta Política de privacidad y según lo exija la legislación aplicable. Tenemos derecho a eliminar toda su Información personal y demás datos después de la terminación de su cuenta de usuario sin previo aviso.

8\. NO RECOPILAMOS INTENCIONADAMENTE DATOS DE MENORES
=====================================================

No recogemos, solicitamos ni conservamos conscientemente Información personal de personas menores de 18 años ni permitimos conscientemente que dichas personas se registren o utilicen nuestros Servicios. Si es menor de 18 años, no nos envíe Información personal. En caso de que tengamos conocimiento de que hemos recogido Información personal de un menor de 18 años sin la verificación del consentimiento de los padres, haremos todo lo posible, dentro de lo razonable desde el punto de vista comercial, para eliminar esa información de nuestra base de datos.

9\. CUÁNDO SE TRATA Y ALMACENA INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL; LEGISLACIÓN APLICABLE
==========================================================================

Tenemos nuestra sede central en los Estados Unidos. La Información personal que nosotros o nuestros Proveedores de servicios recogemos puede almacenarse y tratarse en servidores dentro o fuera de los Estados Unidos y dondequiera que nosotros y nuestros Proveedores de servicios tengamos instalaciones en todo el mundo, y cierta información puede ser accesible por personas o empresas fuera de los Estados Unidos que nos prestan servicios. Usted consiente que nosotros y nuestros Proveedores de Servicios transmitamos y/o transfiramos su Información Personal a jurisdicciones que pueden no proporcionar niveles de protección de datos equivalentes a los de su jurisdicción de origen, o que accedamos a ella en dichas jurisdicciones. Tomaremos medidas razonables para garantizar que su Información personal reciba un nivel adecuado de protección en las jurisdicciones en las que la tratamos.

Las leyes estadounidenses se aplican en la medida en que usted sea residente de los Estados Unidos. De lo contrario, esta Política de privacidad y todos los demás aspectos se interpretarán de acuerdo con las leyes provinciales/estatales y federales de la jurisdicción en la que usted resida. Las jurisdicciones ajenas a su lugar de residencia podrían tener leyes de privacidad diferentes a las suyas, incluido el derecho de las autoridades policiales y gubernamentales a acceder a la Información personal.  Cuando tratamos datos fuera de su país, llevamos a cabo una evaluación del impacto sobre la privacidad para determinar si nuestros Proveedores de servicios pueden ofrecer prácticamente el mismo nivel de protección que el exigido en su jurisdicción y establecemos contratos para reforzar aún más las obligaciones de tratar adecuadamente su Información personal.

10\. SEGURIDAD
==============

Hemos implementado medidas de seguridad técnicas y organizativas diseñadas para proteger su Información personal frente a la pérdida accidental y al acceso, uso, destrucción, alteración y divulgación no autorizados. Sin embargo, tenga en cuenta que Internet no es un entorno 100 % seguro. Es su responsabilidad proteger la seguridad de su información de inicio de sesión, tener cuidado al transmitir cualquier Información personal a través de correos electrónicos, mensajería instantánea y medios de comunicación similares, y mantener buenas prácticas de seguridad de Internet. Nunca le enviaremos un correo electrónico para pedirle su contraseña u otra información de inicio de sesión de la cuenta. Si recibe dicho correo electrónico, envíenoslo para que podamos investigarlo.

11\. DERECHOS ADICIONALES DE LOS INTERESADOS PARA RESIDENTES EN CIERTAS JURISDICCIONES DESCRITAS EN LOS AVISOS DE PRIVACIDAD COMPLEMENTARIOS
============================================================================================================================================

A continuación se explican los derechos de cada interesado descritos en los Avisos de privacidad complementarios:

* Derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad: Tiene derecho a recibir cierta información legalmente necesaria en el momento de la recogida o antes, o en respuesta a su solicitud.
* Derecho de supresión: Puede solicitar que eliminemos cualquier Información personal sobre usted que hayamos recogido de usted, sujeto a ciertas excepciones.
* Derecho de corrección: Puede solicitar que corrijamos cualquier información personal incorrecta que conservemos sobre usted.
* Derecho a saber: Puede solicitar que le facilitemos información específica sobre cómo hemos manejado su Información personal, incluyendo proporcionarle una copia de las partes específicas de Información personal que hemos recopilado sobre usted en un formato portátil.
* Derecho a la no discriminación: Tiene derecho a no ser discriminado por ejercer sus derechos como interesado. Esto significa no denegarle bienes o servicios, cobrarle precios o tarifas diferentes, o proporcionar un nivel diferente de calidad en productos o servicios por el hecho de haber ejercido sus derechos como interesado.
* Derechos de exclusión: Puede solicitar que se le excluya de la venta y uso compartido de su Información personal, de la publicidad dirigida o basada en el comportamiento en contextos cruzados, de la toma de decisiones automatizada o de la elaboración de perfiles, en la medida en que dichas actividades estén definidas y limitadas por la legislación aplicable.
* Derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento: Puede solicitarnos que suprimamos o cesemos el tratamiento de parte de su Información personal, pero aún podremos almacenar su Información personal.  
* Derecho a limitar el uso de su Información personal sensible: Puede solicitar limitar el uso de su Información personal sensible solo a los fines autorizados por las leyes aplicables.
* Derecho a presentar una reclamación: Tiene derecho a presentar una reclamación ante su autoridad local de protección de datos si considera que el tratamiento de la Información personal relacionada con usted infringe sus derechos.
* Derecho a retirar el consentimiento: En la medida en que nuestro tratamiento de su Información personal se base únicamente en su consentimiento, puede retirar dicho consentimiento en cualquier momento.

12\. INFORMACIÓN DE CONTACTO
============================

PlugShare ha designado a un Delegado de protección de datos como la persona que supervisará el cumplimiento de los requisitos de privacidad. Puede ponerse en contacto con el Delegado de protección de datos de PlugShare en la siguiente dirección en relación con cualquier problema de la política de privacidad.

Si tiene alguna pregunta o comentario sobre esta Política de privacidad o nuestras prácticas de privacidad, póngase en contacto con nosotros en: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 EE. UU.; A la atención de: Responsable de protección de datos; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

AVISO DE PRIVACIDAD PARA RESIDENTES DE CIERTOS ESTADOS DE EE. UU.
=================================================================

Si usted reside en California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah o Connecticut (en lo sucesivo, “Consumidor”), las leyes estatales le otorgan derechos adicionales con respecto al uso que hacemos de su Información personal.

LEY “SHINE THE LIGHT” DE CALIFORNIA
-----------------------------------

La sección 1798.83 del Código Civil de California, conocida como la Ley “Shine The Light”, permite a cualquier usuario que sea residente de California solicitar y obtener de nosotros una lista de qué Información personal (si la hubiera) divulgamos a terceros con fines de marketing directo en el año natural anterior y los nombres y direcciones de esos terceros. Las solicitudes solo se pueden realizar una vez al año y son gratuitas.

LEY DE PROTECCIÓN DE LA PRIVACIDAD EN LÍNEA DE CALIFORNIA (“CALOPPA” \[por sus siglas en inglés\]; CÓDIGO DE NEGOCIOS Y PROFESIONES DE CALIFORNIA, secciones 22575-22578, DISPONIBLE [AQUÍ](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D-))
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

La CalOPPA solo se aplica a empresas que recogen Información personal de residentes de California.

1. CÓMO RESPONDEMOS A LAS SEÑALES DE NO RASTREAR.

Algunos navegadores web transmiten señales de "no rastrear" (DNT/GPC) a los sitios web y otros servicios en línea con los que se comunica su navegador web. En la actualidad no existe ninguna norma que regule qué deben hacer los sitios web, si es que deben hacer algo, cuando reciben estas señales; sin embargo, actualmente contamos con medidas para actuar en respuesta a estas señales.

2. SEGUIMIENTO DEL COMPORTAMIENTO DE TERCEROS

También podemos utilizar estas tecnologías para recopilar información sobre sus actividades en línea a lo largo del tiempo y a través de sitios web de terceros u otros servicios en línea, o asociar Información personal con otra información recopilada de esta manera. Podemos utilizar Información personal no identificada para realizar un seguimiento de los patrones de navegación y clic de los usuarios.

LEY DE PRIVACIDAD DEL CONSUMIDOR DE CALIFORNIA DE 2018 (“CCPA” \[por sus siglas en inglés\], DISPONIBLE [AQUÍ](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) Y SU SUCESORA, LA LEY DE DERECHOS DE PRIVACIDAD DE CALIFORNIA DE 2020 (“CPRA” \[por sus siglas en inglés\], DISPONIBLE [AQUÍ](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-MjdeXn1)).
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

La siguiente tabla detalla cómo divulgamos la información personal que hemos recogido sobre usted:

| Categoría | Categorías de terceros no afiliados a quienes divulgamos Información personal | Categorías de terceros no afiliados a quienes vendemos o con quien compartimos Información personal |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificadores | Proveedores de almacenamiento o alojamiento de datos<br><br>Proveedores de gestión de identidad<br><br>Proveedores de soluciones de pago<br><br>Proveedores de encuestas e investigaciones<br><br>Socios publicitarios, incluidos proveedores de redes sociales | n/a |
| Datos demográficos | Proveedores de encuestas e investigaciones | n/a |
| Información comercial | n/a | n/a |
| Internet u otra actividad de red electrónica; información del dispositivo | Proveedores de almacenamiento o alojamiento de datos<br><br>Proveedores de servicios de bases de datos y software<br><br>Proveedores de gestión de identidad<br><br>Socios publicitarios, incluidos proveedores de redes sociales | n/a |
| Geolocalización | Proveedores de almacenamiento o alojamiento de datos<br><br>Proveedores de servicios de bases de datos y software<br><br>Socios publicitarios, incluidos proveedores de redes sociales | n/a |
| Otro | Proveedores de almacenamiento o alojamiento de datos<br><br>Proveedores de servicios de bases de datos y software<br><br>Proveedores de encuestas e investigaciones<br><br>Socios publicitarios, incluidos proveedores de redes sociales | Fabricantes, minoristas y mayoristas |

Puede ponerse en contacto con nosotros para ejercer los siguientes derechos en virtud de la CCPA y la CPRA (consulte la sección 11 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal para obtener descripciones de estos derechos):

1. Derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad.
2. Derecho a saber lo siguiente:

* Las categorías de Información personal que recogemos sobre usted.
* Las categorías de fuentes de la Información personal que recogemos sobre usted.
* Nuestro fin comercial o empresarial para recoger esa Información personal.
* Las categorías de terceros con los que compartimos esa Información personal.
* Los datos personales concretos que hayamos recogido sobre usted (también denominado solicitud de portabilidad de datos) y facilitarle una copia en formato electrónico o en papel.
* Si divulgamos su Información personal con un fin comercial, una lista de las divulgaciones con un fin comercial, identificando las categorías de Información personal que obtuvo cada categoría de destinatario.

3. Derecho de supresión.
4. Derecho de corrección.
5. Derecho a darse de baja de la publicidad conductual en contextos cruzados, de la venta o del intercambio de Información personal, del tratamiento de Información personal para la elaboración de perfiles y de la toma de decisiones automatizada.
6. Derecho a limitar el uso de su Información personal sensible. Tenga en cuenta que no utilizamos su Información personal sensible para fines no autorizados por la CCPA y la CPRA.

LEY DE PROTECCIÓN DE DATOS DE CONSUMIDORES DE VIRGINIA (VCDPA, por sus siglas en inglés), LEY DE PRIVACIDAD DE COLORADO (CPA, por sus siglas en inglés)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), LEY DE PRIVACIDAD DE CONSUMIDORES DE UTAH (UCPA, por sus siglas en inglés)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) Y LEY DE PRIVACIDAD DE DATOS DE CONNECTICUT (CDPA, por sus siglas en inglés).[\[3\]](#ftnt3) 
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Puede ponerse en contacto con nosotros para ejercer los siguientes derechos en virtud de estas leyes estatales específicas:

1. Derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad.
2. Derecho a saber.
3. Derecho de supresión.
4. Derecho de corrección.
5. Derecho de exclusión voluntaria de la publicidad dirigida o la venta de Información personal.
6. Derecho a la exclusión voluntaria de la elaboración de perfiles (tratamiento automatizado de datos personales con fines de análisis o predicción de las características o el comportamiento futuro de una persona, que dé lugar a decisiones que afecten a sus derechos sustantivos).  
7. Los consumidores de Virginia, Colorado y Connecticut también tienen derecho a recurrir nuestras decisiones sobre sus solicitudes de interesados poniéndose en contacto con nosotros a través del mismo método para enviar una solicitud. Adjunte una copia de nuestra decisión sobre su solicitud de interesado o haga referencia a ella de otro modo, para que podamos abordar adecuadamente su recurso. Responderemos a su recurso de acuerdo con la ley aplicable.

NEVADA
------

Como se ha descrito anteriormente, podemos vender sus identificadores u otra información de identificación que recojamos de nuestros Sitios web y Servicios en línea a partes no afiliadas para fines de seguimiento de comportamiento en contextos cruzados en el sentido de la ley de Nevada. Tiene derecho a darse de baja de la venta o licencia de esas categorías de Información personal sobre usted a partes no afiliadas.

EJERCICIO DE LOS DERECHOS
-------------------------

Para ejercer los derechos de acceso, rectificación, portabilidad de datos y supresión descritos anteriormente, envíenos una solicitud a través de nuestro formulario web disponible [aquí](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Sólo usted o una persona a la que haya autorizado a actuar en su nombre podrá realizar una solicitud relacionada con sus Datos personales. También puede presentar una solicitud en nombre de su hijo menor de edad. Si recibimos una solicitud de una persona para ejercer derechos en su nombre, le solicitaremos una copia de su permiso firmado autorizando a presentar dichas solicitudes en su nombre y nos pondremos en contacto con usted para confirmar directamente dicha autorización. Solo puede realizar una solicitud de acceso o portabilidad de datos dos veces en un periodo de 12 meses. La solicitud verificable del Consumidor debe:

* Proporcionar información suficiente que nos permita verificar que usted es la persona sobre la que recogemos Información personal o que un representante autorizado ha realizado la solicitud.
* Describir su solicitud con suficiente detalle, que nos permita comprenderla, evaluarla y responderla correctamente.

No podemos responder a su solicitud ni proporcionarle Información personal si no podemos verificar su identidad o autoridad para realizar la solicitud y confirmar que la Información personal guarda relación con usted. Efectuar una solicitud no requiere que usted cree una cuenta con nosotros. Solo utilizaremos la Información personal facilitada en una solicitud para verificar la identidad o autoridad del solicitante para realizar la solicitud.

Para ejercer los derechos de exclusión voluntaria de la publicidad basada en el comportamiento en contextos cruzados, la publicidad dirigida o el intercambio de Información personal como se ha descrito anteriormente, tendrá que excluirse en función de la plataforma en la que se encuentre.  Tenga en cuenta que su solicitud de exclusión voluntaria es específica para el dispositivo y la plataforma en los que presente dicha solicitud, por lo que es posible que tenga que presentar varias solicitudes si pretende excluirse de estas actividades de procesamiento específicas para varios dispositivos y plataformas. Por favor, haga clic:

* aquí para darse de baja de Plugshare.com (plataforma web)
* aquí para darse de baja de la aplicación iOS de Plugshare
* aquí para darse de baja de la aplicación Android de Plugshare

### Proceso de verificación

Cuando recibamos una solicitud suya de acceso, rectificación, portabilidad o supresión de datos, le enviaremos un correo electrónico en un plazo de 10 días laborables a la dirección de correo electrónico que tenemos registrada. El correo electrónico le pedirá que responda para verificar que usted es el Consumidor que realiza la solicitud. Una vez recibida su verificación, vincularemos su información con la que figura en nuestro archivo. Tras la verificación de su identidad, procederemos a procesar su solicitud y responderemos en un plazo de 45 días naturales, a menos que (a) no podamos verificar su solicitud, (b) no podamos relacionarle con la información de nuestra base de datos, o (c) exista una excepción en virtud de la ley que nos exima de cumplir con su solicitud. Si necesitamos más tiempo (hasta cuarenta y cinco \[45\] días calendario adicionales), le informaremos del motivo y del plazo de ampliación por escrito.

Si no podemos atender su solicitud, la respuesta que le demos le explicará los motivos. Para las solicitudes de portabilidad de datos, seleccionaremos un formato para proporcionar su Información personal que sea fácilmente utilizable y que le permita transmitir la información de una entidad a otra sin obstáculos.

No cobramos un cargo por procesar o responder a su solicitud verificable del Consumidor a menos que sea excesiva, repetitiva o manifiestamente infundada. Si determinamos que la solicitud justifica el pago de una tasa, le explicaremos por qué hemos tomado esa decisión y le facilitaremos una estimación del coste antes de completar su solicitud.

* * *

AVISOS DE PRIVACIDAD PARA CIERTOS PAÍSES NO ESTADOUNIDENSES
===========================================================

INFORMACIÓN GENERAL
-------------------

1. ### SU CONSENTIMIENTO ESPECÍFICO PARA EL TRATAMIENTO DE CATEGORÍAS “SENSIBLES” O “ESPECIALES” DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Según las leyes de privacidad de algunos países, ciertos tipos de Información personal se consideran categorías de información “sensible” o “especial”. Rara vez tratamos datos sensibles o de categorías especiales, a menos que lo hagamos en su interés vital o en el de otra persona. Para todas las demás circunstancias, usted consiente específicamente en que recojamos, tratemos y conservemos categorías sensibles o especiales de Información personal según se describe en la sección 1.2 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal y, de lo contrario, consiente el tratamiento de Información personal de acuerdo con este Aviso de privacidad.  

2. ### NUESTRAS BASES JURÍDICAS PARA EL TRATAMIENTO DE INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL

Nuestras bases jurídicas para recoger y utilizar la Información personal descrita anteriormente dependerán de la Información personal en cuestión y del contexto específico en el que la recojamos. En términos generales, recogeremos y trataremos su Información personal únicamente cuando la necesitemos para prestarle los Servicios que haya contratado con nosotros, o cuando el tratamiento responda a nuestros intereses legítimos y no prevalezcan sus intereses en materia de protección de datos o sus derechos y libertades fundamentales, y nos basaremos en su consentimiento cuando estemos legalmente obligados a hacerlo. En algunos casos, también podemos tener la obligación legal de recoger Información personal de usted o quizá necesitemos la Información personal para proteger sus intereses vitales o los de otra persona.

BASE DE INTERÉS LEGÍTIMO PARA RECOGER INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL: La recogida y el tratamiento de su Información personal pueden ser necesarios para los fines de nuestros intereses legítimos. Dichos fines de interés legítimo pueden incluir:

* prevenir el fraude
* garantizar la seguridad de la red y la información
* indicar posibles actos delictivos o amenazas a la seguridad pública, incluida la mejora de la protección de nuestra comunidad contra el spam, el acoso, la infracción de la propiedad intelectual, los delitos y los riesgos de seguridad de todo tipo, y la aplicación de reclamaciones legales, incluida la investigación de posibles infracciones de nuestras Condiciones de uso
* cuando cumplamos obligaciones legales
* tratar datos de empleados o visitantes, miembros, asistentes o inscritos
* realizar la función o el servicio que nos solicitó
* proporcionarle nuestros Servicios y su funcionalidad cuando dicho tratamiento sea necesario a efectos de los intereses legítimos que nosotros o nuestros proveedores de servicios tengamos en relación con los Servicios
* marketing directo
* la relación relevante y apropiada que tenemos con usted
* llevar a cabo análisis, p. ej., evaluar el número de visitantes, vistas de página, uso de los Sitios web, etc., para entender cómo se utilizan nuestros Sitios web, Productos y Servicios, para optimizar los Sitios web y/o futuras comunicaciones, y para desarrollar nuevos servicios y características del Sitio web
* actualizar su información y preferencias
* ofrecer y mejorar nuestros Sitios web, Productos y Servicios
* hacer cumplir las reclamaciones legales, incluida la investigación de posibles infracciones de nuestras Condiciones

Además de la información proporcionada anteriormente, las siguientes secciones solo se aplican a los residentes o ciudadanos del país o región analizados. A los efectos de las siguientes secciones, a menos que se mencione específicamente, la definición de “Información personal” utilizada anteriormente tendrá la definición de información personal, datos personales o término similar, según corresponda, que contemplen las leyes de privacidad de datos de ese país o región. En caso de conflicto entre las secciones siguientes y las anteriores, prevalecerán las secciones siguientes.

RGPD: AVISO DE PRIVACIDAD PARA RESIDENTES EN EL ESPACIO ECONÓMICO EUROPEO (EEE), REINO UNIDO Y SUIZA
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### DESCRIPCIÓN GENERAL

Las siguientes disposiciones se aplican solo si usted es residente del EEE, el Reino Unido o Suiza (denominadas en esta Sección, por comodidad, como la “Región de la UE”).

Para dichos residentes, todo el tratamiento de su Información personal se realiza de acuerdo con los derechos de privacidad y el reglamento, en particular, (UE) 2016/679 del Parlamento Europeo y del Consejo, de 27 de abril de 2016, conocido como el Reglamento General de Protección de Datos o el Reglamento General de Protección de Datos del Reino Unido para residentes del Reino Unido (conjuntamente, el “RGPD”), y nuestro tratamiento tendrá lugar de acuerdo con el RGPD. A los efectos del RGPD, seremos el “responsable del tratamiento” de la Información personal (denominada y definida en el RGPD, disponible [aquí](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/), como “datos personales”) que recogemos, a menos que recojamos dicha información en nombre de un “responsable del tratamiento”, en cuyo caso seremos un “encargado del tratamiento”. Esta Política de privacidad no se aplica a sitios web, aplicaciones o servicios que no muestren, o enlacen con,  esta Política de privacidad o que muestren o enlacen con una política de privacidad diferente. Solo para residentes y ciudadanos de la Región de la UE, en la medida en que cualquier definición de esta Política de privacidad entre en conflicto con una definición conforme al RGPD, prevalecerá la definición del RGPD.

Proporcionamos la protección adecuada para la transferencia de Información personal a países fuera de la Región de la UE a través de uno o más de los siguientes métodos: (a) una serie de acuerdos interempresariales basados en, o que incorporen, las Cláusulas contractuales tipo, (b) podemos basarnos en las decisiones de adecuación de la Comisión Europea sobre ciertos países, según corresponda, (c) podemos obtener su consentimiento para estas transferencias de datos desde la Región de la UE a los Estados Unidos a otros países, (d) podemos adoptar normas corporativas vinculantes, o (e) en la medida aplicable, podemos basarnos en excepciones según lo establecido en el artículo 49 del RGPD para la transferencia y transferencia ulterior de la Información personal recogida de personas en la Región de la UE a los Estados Unidos y demás países que la Región de la UE considera que no proporcionan una protección de datos adecuada. Con respecto al método (e), podemos transferir Información personal a un tercero para ejecutar un contrato con usted, con su consentimiento explícito o de una manera que no afecte a sus derechos y libertades. Si esta Información personal no se trata ni se transfiere, no podremos ejecutar el contrato con usted o usted no tendrá acceso a determinados o a ninguno de los beneficios y características que se asocian con su transacción.

También es posible que tengamos que transferir su información a otras empresas del grupo o proveedores de servicios en países fuera de la Región de la UE. Esto puede suceder si nuestros servidores o proveedores y proveedores de servicios están ubicados fuera de la Región de la UE, o si utiliza nuestros Productos y/o Servicios mientras visita países fuera de estas zonas.

Se analizan nuestras bases jurídicas para recoger su Información personal.

2. ### SUS DERECHOS DE DATOS EN VIRTUD DEL RGPD.

Si está sujeto al RGPD, sus derechos incluyen el derecho a:

* Derecho a saber.
* Derecho de corrección.
* Derecho de supresión.
* Derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento. Tiene derecho a oponerse a que su Información personal se utilice de las siguientes maneras: (a) tratamiento basado en intereses legítimos o en la realización de una tarea en interés público/ejercicio de la autoridad oficial (incluida la elaboración de perfiles); (b) marketing directo (incluida la elaboración de perfiles); y (c) tratamiento para fines de investigación científica/histórica y estadísticas. Para más información, véase más adelante.
* Derecho de exclusión. Tiene derecho a no estar sujeto a una decisión basada únicamente en el tratamiento automatizado, incluida la elaboración de perfiles, que produzca efectos legales sobre usted o le afecte de forma significativa, excepto por las excepciones aplicables en virtud de las leyes de protección de datos pertinentes.
* Derecho a presentar una reclamación. Si reside dentro del EEE, puede encontrar una lista de las autoridades nacionales de protección de datos [aquí](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Si reside en el Reino Unido, puede ponerse en contacto con la Oficina del Comisionado de Información [aquí.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Derecho a retirar el consentimiento.

AVISOS A LOS RESIDENTES DE OTROS PAÍSES (NO PERTENECIENTES A EE. UU.)
---------------------------------------------------------------------

La información que figura en esta sección es adicional a la que figura en nuestra Política de privacidad principal.

Respetaremos los siguientes derechos de los interesados para todos los residentes fuera de los EE. UU.:

* Derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad:

* Nuestra identidad e información de contacto,
* El fin específico de nuestro tratamiento de su Información personal,
* La forma y duración de nuestro tratamiento de su Información personal,
* Información sobre nuestro uso compartido y fin para compartir su Información personal,
* Las responsabilidades de cualquier tercero que trate su Información personal, y
* Información relativa a cualquier entidad jurídica pública y privada con la que hayamos compartido su Información personal.  

* Derecho a saber:

* Decisiones tomadas exclusivamente sobre la base del tratamiento automatizado de la Información personal.
* Acceso a información sobre la Información personal que recopilamos.  

* Derecho de corrección.
* Derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento.  
* Derecho a retirar el consentimiento.

Cualquier traducción de esta Política de privacidad a un idioma que no sea el inglés se proporciona únicamente con fines informativos. En caso de discrepancias, la única versión legalmente válida y vinculante será la versión en inglés de este documento.

1. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE ARGENTINA

Las medidas de seguridad técnicas y organizativas implementadas por PlugShare también respaldarían las normas de la Ley de Protección de Datos Personales (PDPA) 25.326 de Argentina, como la prohibición de cualquier uso secundario de los datos personales de un interesado y la prohibición de la transferencia de datos personales a países que no ofrecen un nivel adecuado de protección. PlugShare utiliza un acuerdo de transferencia/tratamiento de datos para ayudar a cumplir con la disposición 60-E/2016 de la PDPA, que regula la transferencia transfronteriza de datos personales.

Los residentes de Argentina tienen (a) el derecho a conocer información sobre la existencia y el fin de dicha Información personal, y (b) el derecho a la corrección y el derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento de su Información personal si es falsa, incorrecta o discriminatoria.

2. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE AUSTRALIA

Podemos utilizar y divulgar su Información personal (según se define en la legislación de Australia) a terceros con sede fuera de Australia, principalmente en los Estados Unidos, como se describe en la sección 9 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal. Usted acepta y reconoce que los destinatarios en el extranjero estarán sujetos a la ley de privacidad de su jurisdicción local y no podrán estar sujetos a ninguna obligación de privacidad ni a ningún principio similar a los Principios de privacidad australianos. También estarán sujetos a una ley extranjera que podría obligar a la divulgación de Información personal a un tercero, como una autoridad extranjera. A menos que nos notifique por escrito lo contrario, se le pedirá que haya dado su consentimiento para la divulgación de Información personal a destinatarios extranjeros. Tiene la opción de permanecer en el anonimato cuando trate con nosotros, o de no divulgarnos cierta Información personal. Sin embargo, esto puede significar que no podamos prestarle nuestros Servicios.

Para los residentes de Australia, las actualizaciones de esta Política de privacidad son efectivas si obtenemos su consentimiento expreso o si proporcionamos la opción de excluirse cuando se anuncien cambios sustanciales (p. ej., en nuestros Sitios web o por correo electrónico).

3. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE BRASIL

Los residentes de Brasil tienen derecho a conocer la siguiente información: si el hecho de que nos facilite su Información personal es un requisito contractual, o si existe alguna consecuencia por no facilitar dichos datos (la respuesta es no a ambos), información relativa a cualquier toma de decisiones automatizada (incluida la elaboración de perfiles) que realicemos (véase la sección 2.1 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal), tiene derecho a retirar su consentimiento para el tratamiento de su Información personal, y a conocer sus derechos de acceso del interesado (véase mayor información más adelante).

Los residentes de Brasil también tienen estos derechos: (a) derecho a saber, incluido obtener una copia de dicha información; (b) derecho a la corrección; (c) derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento; (d) derecho a la supresión; (e) derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad sobre las entidades públicas y privadas con las que se ha compartido su Información personal; y (f) derecho a presentar una reclamación ante la autoridad de control de datos brasileña, la Autoridad Nacional de Protección de Datos Personales (ANPD, por sus siglas en inglés).

4. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE CANADÁ (INCLUIDO QUEBEC)

Nuestra Política de privacidad y nuestras prácticas generales están diseñadas para cumplir con las leyes de privacidad canadienses, incluida la Ley de Protección de Información Personal y Documentos Electrónicos (PIPEDA, por sus siglas en inglés) y, cuando corresponda, la ley de privacidad del sector privado de Quebec, la Protección de Información Personal en el Sector Privado (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Para cualquier práctica de tratamiento de la información que no esté relacionada con los fines para los que se puso en contacto con PlugShare, tiene derecho a excluirse de dichas prácticas de tratamiento de la información (incluyendo marketing, elaboración de perfiles, publicidad basada en el comportamiento, compartir con un tercero que no sea un proveedor de servicios).  

Los residentes canadienses tienen derecho a oponerse a que utilicemos sus datos personales para fines de marketing directo y demás tratamientos que no sean necesarios para responder a lo que nos ha solicitado.

5. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE HONG KONG

Utilizamos su Información personal para los siguientes fines de marketing directo: (a) para comunicarnos con usted sobre nuestros productos y servicios y los de nuestras filiales; y (b) para enviarle más avisos, promociones u otros materiales de marketing relativos a nuestros Sitios web, Productos y Servicios, y los de nuestras filiales. Su consentimiento para este fin se solicitará en el momento en que nos envíe su Información personal (por ejemplo, al crear una cuenta, registrarse en un evento, etc.).

6. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE MÉXICO

Además de la información presentada anteriormente, los residentes de México tienen derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad, incluido (a) si el hecho de que usted nos proporcione su Información personal es un requisito contractual o si existe alguna consecuencia por no proporcionar dichos datos (la respuesta es no a ambas), (b) información sobre cualquier toma de decisiones automatizada (incluida la elaboración de perfiles) que realicemos (que se analiza en la sección 2.1 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal), (c) cuánto tiempo se conserva (véase la sección 7 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal), (d) el derecho a retirar su consentimiento para el tratamiento de su Información personal y, (e) sus derechos de acceso del interesado (véase mayor información más adelante). También tiene derecho a conocer la indicación expresa de la Información personal sensible que se va a tratar.

Los residentes de México también tienen: (a) derecho a conocer la Información personal que recogemos, lo que incluye ser informado sobre las entidades públicas y privadas con las que se ha compartido su información personal y obtener una copia de dicha información; (b) derecho a la corrección; (c) derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento; y (d) derecho a la supresión.

7. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE SINGAPUR

Entre otros derechos, si tenemos presencia en Singapur, tiene derecho a que la Información personal suya de que dispongamos se transmita a otra organización.

Las personas o empresas a las que divulgamos y transferimos su Información personal pueden estar ubicadas fuera de Singapur. Nos aseguraremos de que los destinatarios de la Información personal transferida puedan proporcionar a la Información personal transferida un nivel de protección comparable a los niveles de protección establecidos en la ley de privacidad de Singapur mediante el uso de acuerdos de transferencia de datos escritos (para transferencias a terceros) o normas corporativas vinculantes (para transferencias a nuestras filiales y otras entidades relacionadas con nosotros).

8. ### AVISO A LOS RESIDENTES DE TAIWÁN

Los residentes de Taiwán tienen derecho a recibir información sobre prácticas de privacidad.

Los residentes de Taiwán también tienen: (a) derecho a conocer la Información personal que recogemos, incluido ser informados sobre las entidades públicas y privadas con las que se ha compartido su Información personal y obtener una copia de dicha información; (b) derecho a la corrección; (c) derecho a limitar u oponerse al tratamiento; y (d) derecho a la supresión.

Además de la información presentada anteriormente, los residentes de Taiwán tienen derecho a conocer cierta información sobre la Información personal que recogemos, incluido (a) si el hecho de que usted nos proporcione su Información personal es un requisito contractual o si existe alguna consecuencia por no proporcionar dichos datos (la respuesta es no a ambas), (b) información sobre cualquier toma de decisiones automatizada (incluida la elaboración de perfiles) que realicemos (que se analiza en la sección 2.1 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal), (c) cuánto tiempo se conserva (véase la sección 7 de nuestra Política de privacidad principal), (d) el derecho a retirar su consentimiento para el tratamiento de su Información personal y, (e) sus derechos de acceso del interesado (véase mayor información más adelante). También tiene derecho a conocer la indicación expresa de la Información personal sensible que se va a tratar (no recogemos información “sensible”).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) La Ley de Privacidad de Colorado entra en vigor el 1 de julio de 2023

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) La Ley de Privacidad del Consumidor de Utah entra en vigor el 31 de diciembre de 2023

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) La Ley de Privacidad de Datos de Connecticut entra en vigor el 1 de julio de 2023

POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ DE PLUGSHARE
=========================================

DATE D’ENTRÉE EN VIGUEUR : 10 juillet 2023
------------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (« PlugShare », « nous », « notre » ou « nos ») a pour objectif de créer une communauté de soutien pour les utilisateurs de véhicules électriques (« VE »), et de fournir des informations de premier plan sur la recharge et une large gamme de produits et services innovants afin de rendre l’expérience de conduite des VE aussi facile et gratifiante que possible. La présente Politique de confidentialité énonce nos politiques sur la collecte, l’utilisation, la divulgation, la conservation et le transfert des Renseignements personnels (définis ci-dessous) que nous recueillons à votre sujet (« vous » ou « votre ») par le biais de nos interactions avec vous par l’intermédiaire de nos sites Web  ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); ou [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); collectivement, « Sites Web »), les services correspondants et nos applications mobiles (collectivement, les « Services »), ainsi que par le biais d’interactions avec des parties non affiliées comme nos fournisseurs qui travaillent avec nous pour vous fournir nos Services.

Veuillez lire attentivement cette Politique de confidentialité. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que nous traitions vos Renseignements personnels, veuillez ne pas nous en fournir; toutefois, il se peut que vous ne puissiez pas profiter de certaines fonctions de nos Services.

Votre utilisation du Site Web et de nos Services est également en tout temps assujettie à nos Conditions d’utilisation (consultables à l’adresse [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html)et mises à jour de temps à autre \[les « Conditions »\]).

La présente Politique de confidentialité ne s’applique à aucun site ou service non affilié lié à ou depuis nos Sites Web ou Services autres que ceux de nos Prestataires de services, à nos canaux de médias sociaux ou aux plateformes qui les hébergent, ou à tout site ou service recommandé ou référencé par nos Sites Web ou Services ou par notre personnel.

Résidents de la Californie, de la Virginie, du Colorado, de l’Utah et du Connecticut : Veuillez consulter notre [Avis de confidentialité supplémentaire pour les résidents de certains États des États-Unis](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) concernant des renseignements supplémentaires sur notre traitement de vos Renseignements personnels.

Résidents d’autres pays : Si vous résidez dans un pays autre que les États-Unis, veuillez consulter la page intitulé Avis de confidentialité supplémentaires pour certains pays autres que les États-Unis sur notre Site Web pour obtenir des renseignements supplémentaires sur notre traitement de vos Renseignements personnels.

Nous travaillons constamment à l’amélioration de nos services, et il se peut que nous devions également modifier cette Politique de confidentialité de temps à autre. Notre Politique de confidentialité actuelle sera toujours consultable sur nos Sites Web. Veuillez noter la date d’entrée en vigueur de la présente Politique de confidentialité et vous assurer de vérifier régulièrement les mises à jour.

1\. RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS QUE NOUS RECUEILLONS
==================================================

1.1 DÉFINITION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS
--------------------------------------------

La présente Politique de confidentialité couvre notre traitement de vos renseignements personnels identifiables. « Renseignements personnels » désigne généralement toute information non chiffrée qui identifie, se rapporte à, décrit, est raisonnablement capable d’être associée à ou pourrait raisonnablement être liée à une personne particulière, comme, mais sans s’y limiter, votre nom, votre adresse postale, votre adresse courriel, votre numéro de téléphone, etc.

Les Renseignements personnels ne comprennent pas vos Renseignements personnels qui ont été dépersonnalisés, anonymisés ou regroupés de manière requise en vertu des lois applicables afin que les renseignements ne puissent plus être utilisés directement ou par d’autres moyens raisonnablement disponibles pour identifier une personne (collectivement, les « Renseignements personnels dépersonnalisés »).

1.2 CATÉGORIES DE RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS QUE NOUS RECUEILLONS ET TRAITONS
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

Nous recueillons plusieurs catégories de Renseignements personnels auprès de vous et à votre sujet, comme le résume le tableau suivant :

| Catégorie | Éléments spécifiques de renseignements personnels |
| --- | --- |
| Identificateurs | * prénom et nom<br>* identifiant (qui peut inclure le prénom et le nom de famille)<br>* adresse courriel<br>* code postal<br>* sexe, genre<br>* identifiant personnel unique (nom ou numéro du client ou du compte, numéro de téléphone, identifiant de l’appareil mobile) |
| Données démographiques | * pays de résidence |
| Renseignements commerciaux | * historique et tendances d’achat de produits/services |
| Activité sur Internet ou autre réseau électronique; renseignements sur l’appareil | * type et fabricant de l’appareil et son ID/UDID ou un code similaire spécifique à l’appareil<br>* système d’exploitation et plateforme<br>* résolution de l’écran<br>* nom du fournisseur de service Internet ou du fournisseur de services mobiles, vitesse de connexion et type de connexion<br>* adresse, protocole et information de séquence du protocole Internet (IP)<br>* témoins<br>* pixels invisibles<br>* adresse MAC (Media Access Control) des pages que vous avez visitées<br>* identificateur publicitaire de l’appareil mobile<br>* type de navigateur, langue et version<br>* navigation sur le site Web, session, interaction et historique de recherche, matériel et pages consultés, heure et date d’accès aux sites Web, nombre d’octets transférés, nombre de clics par visite, temps passé sur une page, données de clics et de parcours de navigation, requêtes effectuées, résultats de recherche sélectionnés, commentaires faits<br>* date et URL de la dernière page Web visitée avant de visiter nos Sites Web, et URL de la première page visitée après avoir quitté nos Sites Web<br>* type de Service demandé<br>* en-têtes de protocole de transfert hypertexte, bannières de client d’application et de serveur |
| Géolocalisation | * emplacement physique et/ou mouvements |
| Autre | * données de charge du VE, marque, modèle et année du véhicule<br>* Renseignements que vous avez fournis volontairement dans le cadre d’une réponse à une rétroaction ou d’une autre demande générale faite par l’intermédiaire de nos Sites Web<br>* Inférences tirées de l’un des renseignements énumérés pour créer un profil sur un consommateur reflétant les préférences, les caractéristiques, les tendances psychologiques, les prédispositions, le comportement, les attitudes, l’intelligence, les capacités ou les aptitudes du consommateur |

1.3 OÙ NOUS RECUEILLONS DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS
-----------------------------------------------------

Nous pouvons recueillir des Renseignements personnels directement auprès de vous par l’intermédiaire de nos Services lorsque :

* Vous nous fournissez des renseignements personnels en remplissant des formulaires Web sur nos Sites Web ou en effectuant des transactions en magasin (marques mères, filiales et affiliées). Il s’agit notamment des renseignements fournis lors de la création d’un compte en ligne, de l’achat de nos Services, de l’abonnement à nos bulletins d’information électroniques ou à d’autres communications, de la demande d’informations, de la soumission ou de la publication de matériel (lorsque cela est autorisé) sur nos forums, ou de l’interaction avec le service ou l’assistance à la clientèle, du signalement d’un problème avec nos Sites Web, nos Applications mobiles ou nos Services, ou de toute autre communication avec nous.
* Vous communiquez avec nous. Cela comprend tous les dossiers et copies de votre correspondance avec nous, par exemple avec nos bureaux ou notre service ou assistance à la clientèle ou lors d’envoi de chèque par courrier postal.
* Vous vous inscrivez à un événement ou nous informez de toute demande d’accessibilité ou d’autres mesures d’aménagements.
* Vous répondez aux enquêtes que nous ou nos Prestataires de services pourraient vous demander de remplir à des fins de recherche.
* Vous effectuez des requêtes de recherche sur les Sites Web.
* Vous participez à des programmes de fidélisation/récompenses.
* Vous postulez à un emploi.
* Vous utilisez des appareils et des réseaux pour accéder à nos Services, comme lors de la synchronisation de votre VE avec nos Services.
* Vous utilisez certaines fonctionnalités sur nos Sites Web et applications mobiles. Bien que les utilisateurs puissent accéder à des fonctionnalités limitées sans divulguer leurs Renseignements personnels, telles que naviguer sur les bornes de recharge publiques sans compte, nous recueillons des Renseignements personnels lorsque les utilisateurs ouvrent un compte. Les utilisateurs peuvent choisir d’utiliser uniquement leur adresse courriel et leur mot de passe pour naviguer sur les chargeurs à domicile. Les utilisateurs peuvent également choisir de profiter des capacités améliorées en postant, commentant, publiant ou partageant des Renseignements personnels supplémentaires avec la communauté. En général, les utilisateurs choisissent la quantité d’informations qu’ils souhaitent afficher à leur sujet, et peuvent se retirer à tout moment.

Nous pouvons également recueillir des Renseignements personnels auprès de parties non affiliées, notamment :

* Les fournisseurs de données (p. ex., les sociétés qui fournissent des données démographiques et d’autres informations concernant les consommateurs)
* Sur les applications mobiles (marques mères, filiales et affiliées)
* Les partenaires de commercialisation en commun
* Les entreprises ou plateformes de publicité en ligne (par exemple, si vous liez ou connectez volontairement votre profil de médias sociaux à nos Services)
* Les Prestataires de services de gestion des commandes et de livraison
* Les entreprises de médias sociaux
*  D’autres Prestataires de services
* Réponses aux opportunités d’emploi
* Actions de l’utilisateur sur le site Web/le formulaire Web ou l’application
* Fournisseurs de vérification d’emploi ou de vérification des antécédents
* Nous permettre, par l’intermédiaire des paramètres de votre appareil ou des services tiers, de recevoir des données de géolocalisation afin d’afficher des renseignements locaux (par exemple, une station de recharge locale) sur nos applications mobiles.

1.4 INFORMATIONS RECUEILLIES PAR LE BIAIS DE TECHNOLOGIES AUTOMATISÉES
----------------------------------------------------------------------

Lorsque vous naviguez et interagissez avec nos Services, nous pouvons également utiliser des technologies de collecte automatique de données pour recueillir certains renseignements sur votre appareil, votre navigateur ou d’autres activités de réseau, comme décrit dans notre Politique sur les témoins, consultable à l’adresse [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Visite du site Web et renseignements sur l’appareil. Nous recueillons les détails de vos visites sur nos Sites Web et de l’utilisation de nos Applications mobiles, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, les données de trafic, les données de géolocalisation, les journaux et autres données de communication et les ressources auxquelles vous accédez et que vous utilisez sur les Sites Web. Nous recueillons des informations sur votre ordinateur, votre appareil mobile et votre connexion Internet, notamment votre adresse IP, votre système d’exploitation, votre type de navigateur, vos parcours sur la toile (c’est-à-dire ce sur quoi vous cliquez sur un site Web), l’URL du site Web le plus récent que vous avez visité avant de venir sur nos Sites Web, le temps que vous avez passé sur nos Sites Web et les pages que vous avez consultées sur nos Sites Web. Nous pouvons obtenir une estimation approximative de votre emplacement à partir de votre adresse IP lorsque vous visitez nos Sites Web. Pour les utilisateurs de nos Applications mobiles, nous pouvons également recueillir et maintenir un historique de vos renseignements de localisation précis à l’aide des technologies Wi-Fi et/ou Bluetooth, ainsi que les identifiants de votre appareil et les coordonnées GPS (p. ex., latitude/longitude). Si vous souhaitez empêcher la collecte de vos renseignements de localisation, veuillez ajuster vos paramètres dans votre appareil mobile afin de limiter l’accès de l’Application mobile à vos renseignements de localisation.

Lorsque vous utilisez notre site Web, nous partageons les informations que nous recueillons auprès de vous, telles que votre adresse e-mail (sous forme hachée), votre adresse IP ou des informations sur votre navigateur ou votre système d'exploitation, avec nos partenaires d'identité/fournisseurs de services. Ces partenaires renvoient un code d'identification en ligne que nous pouvons stocker dans notre cookie propriétaire pour notre utilisation dans la publicité en ligne, intégrée à l'application et multicanal et il peut être partagé avec des sociétés de publicité pour permettre une publicité ciblée et basée sur les centres d'intérêt. Pour refuser cette utilisation, veuillez cliquer ici ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Suivi comportemental. Nous pouvons également utiliser ces technologies pour recueillir des informations sur vos activités en ligne au fil du temps et sur des sites Web de tiers ou d’autres services en ligne, ou associer des Renseignements personnels à d’autres informations recueillies de cette manière.

Analyse de l’emplacement : Nos Applications mobiles et nos Sites Web de navigateur mobile comprennent des fonctionnalités (p. ex., pour la soumission d’un examen par le conducteur d’une installation de recharge) qui nous permettent d’identifier l’emplacement du conducteur et l’emplacement de la installation de recharge où un utilisateur est actuellement situé. Nous recueillons des informations telles que l’adresse IP, l’identifiant de l’appareil et la géolocalisation. Les utilisateurs des Applications mobiles peuvent choisir d’utiliser les Applications mobiles de manière anonyme ou de se connecter en tant qu’utilisateur identifié, auquel cas les données personnelles fournies lors de l’inscription peuvent être utilisées.

Pour les utilisateurs des Applications mobiles, nous pouvons demander la permission d’accéder à certains renseignements à partir de votre appareil mobile, y compris votre liste de contacts, vos photos et vidéos, ainsi que votre microphone et votre appareil photo. L’accès à ces renseignements est facultatif. Cependant, certaines fonctionnalités des Applications mobiles pourraient ne pas fonctionner de manière optimale si vous décidez de ne pas nous donner votre autorisation.

Balises Web. Les pages de nos Sites Web et nos courriels peuvent contenir de petits fichiers électroniques connus sous le nom de balises Web (également appelées pixels invisibles, balises pixel et gifs à pixel unique) qui nous permettent, par exemple, de compter les utilisateurs qui ont visité ces pages ou ouvert un courriel et de réaliser d’autres statistiques connexes sur les sites Web (par exemple, enregistrer la popularité de certains contenus de sites Web et vérifier l’intégrité du système et du serveur).

Suivi des pixels. En plus d’utiliser des témoins, les Sites Web peuvent utiliser le « suivi des pixels ». Le suivi des pixels implique l’utilisation de pixels invisibles pour l’utilisateur et composés de quelques lignes de code informatique. Le suivi des pixels mesure l’efficacité des publicités et compile des statistiques d’utilisation globales et spécifiques. Nous pouvons accéder à ces pixels invisibles pour identifier l’activité et les intérêts qui peuvent nous permettre de mieux adapter nos Produits, Services et offres à vos intérêts et besoins. Par exemple, si vous visitez nos Sites Web à partir d’une publicité sur un autre site Web, le pixel invisible permettra à l’annonceur de savoir que sa publicité vous a amené sur les Sites Web. Si vous visitez nos Sites Web et que nous vous dirigeons vers un autre site Web, nous pouvons également être en mesure de déterminer que vous avez été envoyé vers un site Web tiers et/ou que vous avez effectué une transaction avec celui-ci.

GIF. Nous pouvons utiliser de minuscules images appelées GIF clairs pour suivre le comportement des utilisateurs, y compris des statistiques sur les personnes qui ouvrent nos courriels.

Adresse IP. Nos serveurs (ou ceux de nos fournisseurs de services) enregistrent automatiquement certaines informations de fichier journal signalées à partir de votre navigateur lorsque vous accédez aux sites Web. Ces journaux de serveur peuvent inclure des informations telles que les pages des sites Web que vous avez visitées, votre adresse de protocole Internet (« IP »), votre type de navigateur et d’autres informations sur la façon dont vous interagissez avec les Sites Web. Ces fichiers journaux sont généralement supprimés périodiquement.

Mesures et analyses de tiers. Les mesures et analyses de tiers, sur certaines pages ou fonctionnalités des Services, nous aident à comprendre et à analyser le trafic des visiteurs, à mesurer l’efficacité des promotions et l’efficacité de nos fonctionnalités, offres et campagnes de marketing. Nous utilisons également ces outils pour identifier les écueils, les défauts et les domaines de nos opérations qui doivent être améliorés, et pour visualiser le rendement global et le classement de notre présence en ligne. Ces outils peuvent stocker des témoins sur votre appareil à leur discrétion.

AVIS ET POLITIQUE SUR LES TÉMOINS

Les technologies que nous utilisons pour recueillir automatiquement des données comprennent également des témoins, comme décrit ci-dessous.

Témoins du navigateur

Les témoins de navigateur sont de petits fichiers placés sur le disque dur de votre ordinateur ou de votre appareil mobile. Ils peuvent contenir certaines données, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, le nom du serveur qui les a placés, un identifiant sous la forme d’un numéro unique, et, une date d’expiration (certains témoins uniquement). Les témoins de navigateur sont gérés par le navigateur Web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) de votre ordinateur ou de votre appareil mobile. Différents types de témoins ayant des objectifs différents sont utilisés sur nos Sites Web.

Témoins essentiels

Les témoins essentiels sont indispensables pour vous permettre de naviguer sur nos Sites Web et d’utiliser ses fonctions. Sans eux, des services tels que les paniers de magasinage et la facturation électronique ne pourraient pas fonctionner.

Témoins de performance

Les témoins de rendement recueillent des informations sur l’utilisation de nos Sites Web, comme les pages les plus souvent consultées. Ces renseignements nous permettent d’optimiser nos Sites Web et de simplifier la navigation. Les témoins de performance permettent également à nos sociétés affiliées et partenaires de savoir si vous avez accédé à l’une des pages de notre Site Web depuis leur site et si votre visite a conduit à l’utilisation ou à l’achat d’un Produit ou d’un Service sur nos Sites Web, y compris les références du Produit ou du Service acheté. Toutes les informations recueillies par les témoins de performance sont agrégées, et donc anonymes.

Témoins de fonctionnalité

Les témoins de fonctionnalité permettent à nos Sites Web de se souvenir des choix que vous avez faits lorsque vous naviguez. Par exemple, nous pouvons enregistrer votre position géographique dans un témoin afin d’afficher les Sites Web correspondant à votre région. Nous pouvons également nous souvenir de vos préférences, telles que la taille du texte, la police et d’autres aspects personnalisables des Sites Web. Les témoins de fonctionnalité peuvent également permettre de garder une trace des produits ou des vidéos consultés afin d’éviter les répétitions. Les informations recueillies par ces témoins ne peuvent pas être utilisées pour vous identifier et ne peuvent pas surveiller votre activité de navigation sur des sites Web qui ne nous appartiennent pas. Les témoins de fonctionnalité nous permettent d’afficher des publicités qui vous sont adaptées sur nos sites Web, de comprendre quelles parties de notre contenu vous intéressent le plus et quelles catégories de Produits ou de Services vous demandez. Certains de nos prestataires de services sont autorisés à placer des témoins sur nos Sites Web. Ces sociétés peuvent également vous offrir la possibilité d’empêcher l’utilisation des témoins à l’avenir.

À tout moment, vous pouvez empêcher ou refuser l’utilisation future de certains témoins en activant le paramètre approprié de votre navigateur pour refuser les témoins de navigation. Toutefois, si vous le faites, votre expérience sur nos Sites Web peut être affectée; par exemple, vous pouvez être incapable d’accéder à certaines parties de nos Sites Web. À moins que vous n’ayez réglé les paramètres de votre navigateur pour qu’il refuse les témoins, notre système émettra des témoins lorsque vous dirigerez votre navigateur vers nos Sites Web.

Témoins de stockage local

Certaines fonctionnalités de nos Sites Web peuvent utiliser des objets stockés localement (pour recueillir et stocker des informations sur vos préférences et votre navigation vers, depuis et sur nos Sites Web. Les témoins de stockage local ne sont pas gérés par les mêmes paramètres que ceux utilisés pour les témoins de navigateur.

Nous pouvons également combiner les Renseignements personnels que nous recueillons auprès de vous en dehors de nos Sites Web ou Services avec des Renseignements personnels recueillis par l’intermédiaire de nos Sites Web ou Services ou par d’autres moyens comme décrits ci-dessus.

1.5 INFORMATIONS SUR LES APPAREILS, LE RÉSEAU, LA GÉOLOCALISATION ET LES VE
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Lorsque vous visitez ou quittez nos Sites Web ou nos Services en cliquant sur un hyperlien ou en affichant un plugiciel sur un site Web tiers, nous recevons automatiquement l’URL du site d’où vous venez ou celui vers lequel vous êtes dirigé. De même, les annonceurs reçoivent l’URL de la page sur laquelle vous vous trouvez lorsque vous cliquez sur une publicité qui peut apparaître sur nos Services. Nous recevons également l’adresse de protocole Internet (« IP ») de votre ordinateur ou du serveur proxy que vous utilisez pour accéder à Internet, les détails du système d’exploitation de votre ordinateur, votre type de navigateur Web, votre appareil mobile (y compris l’identifiant de votre appareil mobile fourni par le système d’exploitation de votre appareil mobile), votre système d’exploitation mobile (si vous accédez à nos sites Web ou services à l’aide d’un appareil mobile) et le nom de votre fournisseur d’accès à Internet ou de votre opérateur mobile.

1.6 SONDAGES
------------

Nous ou des parties non affiliées pouvons mener des sondages auprès des utilisateurs concernant nos Services. Certaines parties non affiliées peuvent vous adresser des publicités ou des promotions en fonction de vos réponses au sondage. Nous ou des parties non affiliées développons de nouveaux programmes ou produits sur la base des renseignements que vous partagez dans les sondages. Nous pouvons faire appel à des parties non affiliées pour vous offrir des incitatifs financiers ou autres à participer à des sondages. Si la fourniture d’incitations nécessite vos coordonnées, il se peut que l’on vous demande de fournir des Renseignements personnels à la partie non affiliée qui réalise l’offre d’incitation, qui ne seront utilisés que dans le but de fournir les incitations promises et de vérifier vos coordonnées. C’est à vous de décider si vous fournissez ces informations ou si vous souhaitez profiter d’une offre incitative. Votre consentement à l’utilisation de tout Renseignement personnel aux fins énoncées dans le sondage sera explicitement demandé par la partie non affiliée qui le mène. Pour ne pas participer à nos sondages, vous pouvez nous envoyer votre demande en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous.

2\. LA NATURE ET LE BUT DU TRAITEMENT DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS
===================================================================

Nous utilisons les informations que nous recueillons à votre sujet ou que vous nous fournissez, y compris toute information personnelle, à une ou plusieurs des fins suivantes :

* vous présenter nos Sites Web et nos Applications mobiles et leur contenu;
* vous fournir des renseignements et répondre à vos questions sur les Produits ou Services que vous nous demandez et des renseignements sur les nouveaux produits et services, les rabais, les promotions spéciales ou les événements à venir, ainsi que les caractéristiques ou offres qui, selon nous, vous intéresseront ou concernant une promotion, un concours ou un tirage auquel vous avez participé;
* traiter les renseignements sur le compte et les paiements de transactions, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, les frais de Produit et/ou de Service, ainsi que les paiements et remboursements pour tout Produit ou Service acheté (bien que nous ne recevions pas votre numéro de carte de crédit ou de débit complet);
* traiter les rabais, les offres, les récompenses de fidélité et/ou les demandes de rabais, les formulaires et les demandes et coordonner avec le fabricant, le détaillant et/ou le grossiste;
* vous fournir des avis sur votre compte, y compris des avis d’expiration et de renouvellement;
* vous informer des renseignements concernant nos Sites Web, nos politiques, nos conditions ou tout Produit ou Service que nous offrons ou fournissons, ou concernant votre compte;
* traiter les Renseignements personnels ou d’autres renseignements que vous nous soumettez;
* vous permettre de participer à des fonctionnalités interactives sur nos Sites Web;
* améliorer nos Produits et Services et en développer de nouveaux, par exemple en analysant les tendances des utilisateurs et en mesurant les données démographiques et les intérêts;
* pour le fonctionnement interne du Site Web, du Service et du système, l’administration, la maintenance, les vérifications et les examens internes, le diagnostic des problèmes techniques et le maintien de la sécurité;
* pour enquêter sur toute violation de nos Conditions d’utilisation ou de la présente Politique de confidentialité;
* pour suivre les problèmes potentiels et les tendances liés à l’utilisation de nos Sites Web et Services par les utilisateurs et personnaliser notre assistance pour mieux vous servir;
* fournir des statistiques sur les niveaux d’utilisation des Sites Web et d’autres renseignements connexes à nos Prestataires de services;
* vous aviser des incidents liés à la confidentialité des données ou vous fournir les renseignements requis par la loi;
* demander votre participation à des évaluations, des évaluations, des sondages, des groupes de discussion ou d’autres initiatives qui nous aident à recueillir des renseignements utilisés pour développer et améliorer nos Produits et Services;
* répondre à toute autre fin pour laquelle vous fournissez des Renseignements personnels;
* de toute autre manière que nous pouvons décrire et pour laquelle nous obtenons votre consentement lorsque vous fournissez les renseignements.

Nous utilisons des témoins, des pixels invisibles et des informations de fichiers journaux pour : (a) mémoriser les informations afin que vous n’ayez pas à les saisir à nouveau lors de votre visite ou lors de votre prochaine visite sur les Sites Web; (b) fournir un contenu et des informations personnalisés; (c) contrôler l’efficacité de nos Services; (d) contrôler les mesures globales telles que le nombre total de visiteurs, le trafic et les modèles démographiques; (e) diagnostiquer ou corriger les problèmes technologiques signalés par nos utilisateurs ou ingénieurs qui sont associés à certaines adresses IP; et/ou (f) vous aider à accéder efficacement à vos informations après votre inscription.

Les données statistiques que nous recueillons automatiquement nous aident à améliorer nos Sites Web et à fournir des Produits et Services de meilleure qualité et plus personnalisés, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, en nous permettant : d’estimer la taille de notre audience/visiteurs et leurs habitudes d’utilisation, de stocker des informations sur vos préférences, ce qui nous permet de personnaliser et d’améliorer nos Sites Web, d’accélérer vos recherches, et/ou de vous reconnaître lorsque vous revenez sur nos Sites Web.

Nous pouvons recueillir et utiliser les informations relatives à votre séance de recharge de VE (par exemple, le temps de recharge, la consommation d’énergie, la propriété et les données de la station, etc.) ainsi que la marque, le modèle et l’année de votre véhicule pour gérer votre compte, par exemple pour faire la distinction entre plusieurs véhicules ou utilisateurs partageant un même compte, et à des fins d’analyse.

Dans la mesure où vous ne consentez pas aux pratiques de traitement des renseignements énoncés aux présentes, vous pourriez avoir le droit de vous retirer de ces pratiques. Toutes les demandes de retrait doivent être adressées à [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Dans la mesure où les demandes de retrait sont honorées, elles auront un effet sur le traitement futur et non sur le traitement qui a déjà eu lieu sur la base d’un consentement préalable.

2.1 PRISE DE DÉCISION AUTOMATISÉE
---------------------------------

Nous pouvons utiliser les Renseignements personnels que vous nous fournissez et ceux que nous obtenons d’autres sources pour mieux comprendre vos intérêts afin d’essayer de prévoir quels autres Produits, Services et informations pourraient vous intéresser le plus. Cette pratique consiste à prendre des décisions automatisées à votre sujet sur la base de ces informations afin de nous permettre de mieux adapter nos interactions avec vous pour les rendre plus pertinentes et intéressantes. Vous pouvez vous opposer à cette pratique à tout moment ou nous demander plus de renseignements sur la méthodologie appliquée dans nos processus de prise de décision automatisée en communiquant avec nous (voir la section 12 ci-dessous).

2.2 MESSAGES TEXTE
------------------

Nos Services peuvent comprendre l’envoi de messages texte (« SMS ») à votre appareil sans fil, qui peuvent transmettre jusqu’à deux messages par jour (à moins que vous ne communiquiez davantage avec nous), mais la fréquence des messages peut varier.  Lorsque vous consentez expressément à recevoir des messages texte de notre part et que vous fournissez un numéro de téléphone cellulaire, vous consentez expressément à recevoir des messages textes d’information et transactionnels récurrents de notre part ou en notre nom au numéro que vous avez fourni. En consentant expressément à recevoir des messages SMS de notre part et en fournissant un numéro de téléphone cellulaire, vous garantissez et déclarez que vous êtes le propriétaire du numéro de téléphone cellulaire que vous nous fournissez. Nous pouvons utiliser vos renseignements pour communiquer avec vous au sujet de votre utilisation, de vos achats, de vos retours (le cas échéant), des mises à jour du site Web, de la réalisation de sondages ou des communications d’information et liées au service, y compris des mises à jour importantes sur la sécurité. Après que vous nous ayez envoyé le message texte « STOP », nous vous enverrons un message texte pour confirmer que vous avez été désinscrit. Vous pouvez également nous soumettre votre demande par courriel, en indiquant l’adresse courriel et le numéro de téléphone que vous avez enregistrés auprès de nous, ou par tout autre moyen raisonnable. Après cela, vous ne recevrez plus de messages SMS de notre part. Si vous souhaitez vous réinscrire, il vous suffit de vous inscrire comme vous l’avez fait la première fois et nous recommencerons à vous envoyer des SMS. Pour obtenir de l’aide, veuillez répondre à un message texte avec HELP. Des tarifs de messages et de données peuvent s’appliquer, en fonction de votre forfait de téléphone cellulaire. Les transporteurs ne sont pas responsables des messages retardés ou non livrés.

2.3 PLUGICIELS DE MÉDIAS SOCIAUX
--------------------------------

Nous intégrons des interfaces ou des Plugiciels (« Plugiciels ») de programmes de médias sociaux à partir de réseaux sociaux, y compris Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest et/ou possiblement d’autres entreprises, dans les Sites Web. Afin de vous inscrire en tant qu’utilisateur chez nous, vous pouvez avoir la possibilité de vous connecter à l’aide de votre identifiant Facebook ou d’un autre site de médias sociaux.

Par exemple, lorsque vous visitez nos Sites Web, le plugiciel crée une connexion directe entre votre navigateur et le serveur Facebook. Cela permet à Facebook de recevoir des informations sur votre visite sur nos Sites Web avec votre adresse IP. Si vous cliquez sur le bouton « J’aime » de Facebook pendant que vous êtes connecté à votre compte Facebook, vous pouvez lier le contenu de nos Sites Web à votre profil Facebook. Cela permet à Facebook d’attribuer votre visite à nos sites Web à votre compte d’utilisateur. Veuillez noter qu’en tant que fournisseur des Sites Web, nous ne recevons aucune notification concernant le contenu des données transmises ou leur utilisation par Facebook. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que Facebook attribue votre visite sur nos Sites Web à votre compte utilisateur Facebook, veuillez vous déconnecter de votre compte utilisateur Facebook.

Si vous vous connectez par le biais d’un Plugiciel de médias sociaux, vous nous autorisez à accéder à certaines informations de compte de ce site de médias sociaux, telles que votre profil public de médias sociaux (conformément à vos paramètres de confidentialité sur le site de médias sociaux), votre adresse courriel, vos centres d’intérêt, vos goûts, votre sexe, votre date d’anniversaire, vos antécédents en matière d’éducation, vos relations, votre ville actuelle, vos photos, votre description personnelle, votre liste d’amis, ainsi que les informations et les photos de vos amis de sites de médias sociaux qui pourraient être des amis communs de sites de médias sociaux avec d’autres utilisateurs. Les Plugiciels peuvent transférer des renseignements vous concernant sur la plateforme respective du Plugiciel sans que vous ayez à agir. Ces renseignements peuvent inclure votre numéro d’identification d’utilisateur de plateforme, le site Web sur lequel vous vous trouvez et plus encore. L’interaction avec un Plugiciel transmet des informations directement au réseau social de ce Plugiciel et ces informations peuvent être visibles par d’autres personnes sur cette plateforme. Les Plugiciels sont contrôlés par la politique de confidentialité du site de médias sociaux respectif (disponible sur leur site Web) et non par notre Politique de confidentialité.

3\. NOTRE DIVULGATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS À DES PARTIES NON AFFILIÉES
===============================================================================

3.1 TYPES DE PARTIES NON AFFILIÉES
----------------------------------

Nous pouvons divulguer ou divulguons vos Renseignements personnels, en tout ou en partie, aux types de partie non affiliée suivants, et à l’une ou plusieurs des fins suivantes :

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Type de partie non affiliée | Objectif |
| Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données | Stockage et transmission sécurisés de vos données |
| Prestataires de services de bases de données et de logiciels | Gestion et suivi de vos données |
| Conseillers juridiques et de conformité, comme des conseillers juridiques externes, des vérificateurs externes ou des conseillers fiscaux | Nous fournir des services professionnels |
| Fournisseurs de gestion des identités | Fins d’authentification |
| Fournisseurs de solutions de paiement | Traitement sécurisé des paiements que vous nous fournissez |
| Fabricants, détaillants et grossistes | Soumission, traitement et gestion des rabais, des rabais, des offres, des récompenses de fidélité, etc. |
| Fournisseurs de services d’exécution et d’expédition | Exécution et livraison des Produits, des Services et de la marchandise |
| Fournisseurs de sondages et de recherche | Effectuer des études en notre nom |
| Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de médias sociaux | Fourniture de publicités ciblées |

Vous avez le droit de vous retirer de ce traitement pour tout transfert de Renseignements personnels qui n’est pas raisonnablement nécessaire pour atteindre les objectifs pour lesquels vous vous engagez avec PlugShare (comme à des fins de marketing ou de sondage). Pour exercer votre droit de retrait, veuillez communiquer avec nous à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 PRESTATAIRES DE SERVICES, PARTENAIRES COMMERCIAUX ET SOUS-TRAITANTS
-----------------------------------------------------------------------

 Nous pouvons partager vos Renseignements personnels avec des Prestataires de services qui fournissent des services en notre nom, comme indiqué ci-dessus. Ces Prestataires de services peuvent avoir accès à vos Renseignements personnels afin de nous fournir ces services ou en notre nom. Si nous engageons des Prestataires de services pour l’une des activités susmentionnées, l’utilisation de vos Renseignements personnels sera liée à des obligations de confidentialité et leur utilisation des Renseignements personnels sera limitée à la prestation de leurs services pour nous. Nous pouvons stocker des Renseignements personnels dans des endroits hors de notre contrôle direct (par exemple, sur des serveurs ou des bases de données situés ou coimplantés avec des Prestataires de services d’hébergement de données).  

3.3 PUBLICITÉ COMPORTEMENTALE MULTICONTEXTE
-------------------------------------------

Nous sommes tenus de divulguer si nous partageons des Renseignements personnels avec un tiers qui est engagé dans une publicité comportementale (ciblée) multicontexte. Au cours des douze (12) mois précédents, nous avons ou pouvons avoir divulgué les catégories suivantes de Renseignements personnels dans un contexte qui peut, en vertu de certaines lois (p. ex., la CPRA de la Californie, le RGPD ou le RGPD du Royaume-Uni) être considéré comme une vente :

* Identificateurs
* Internet ou autre activité réseau similaire
* Données de géolocalisation

Vous avez la possibilité de vous retirer de ce partage en cliquant sur les invites de désabonnement qui apparaîtront sur l’avis que vous recevez lorsque vous visitez nos applications mobiles ou nos Sites Web pour la première fois.

3.4 TRANSFERTS D’AFFAIRES
-------------------------

Vous reconnaissez (et ne vous y opposerez pas) que nous divulguons ou transférons vos Renseignements personnels, vos Renseignements personnels dépersonnalisés et les autres renseignements que vous nous fournissez, ainsi que les droits que vous avez accordés ou reconnus dans la présente Politique de confidentialité (collectivement, les « Renseignements transférés ») à un acheteur ou acquéreur potentiel ou réel de notre société ou à un autre successeur dans le but d’envisager ou de réaliser une fusion, cession, restructuration, réorganisation, dissolution, changement de contrôle ou transfert de tout ou partie de nos actifs (chacun de ces éléments étant désigné par le terme « Transfert »), que ce soit dans le cadre d’une poursuite d’activité ou d’une faillite, d’une liquidation ou de toute autre procédure judiciaire, dans laquelle les Renseignements personnels que nous détenons font partie des actifs transférés, et vous consentez à ne pas vous opposer à une telle divulgation ou à un tel transfert. Nous ne pouvons faire aucune déclaration concernant l’utilisation ou le transfert des Informations transférées que nous pourrions avoir en cas de faillite, de réorganisation, d’insolvabilité, de mise sous séquestre ou de cession au profit des créanciers. En outre, sauf si la loi l’exige, nous ne sommes pas et ne serons pas responsables de toute violation de la sécurité par des parties non affiliées ou de toute action de parties non affiliées qui reçoivent des Renseignements  transférés qui nous sont divulgués.

3.5 DIVULGATIONS REQUISES; PROTECTION DES DROITS; SÉCURITÉ
----------------------------------------------------------

Sauf indication contraire dans la présente Politique de confidentialité, nous ne divulguerons pas vos Renseignements personnels à une partie non affiliée, à moins que la loi, une ordonnance d’un tribunal ou une procédure judiciaire (par exemple, une assignation à comparaître) ne nous y oblige, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, pour répondre à une demande d’un gouvernement, d’un organisme de réglementation ou d’une licence, ou si nous pensons qu’une telle action est nécessaire pour : (a) nous conformer à la loi, nous conformer aux procédures légales qui nous sont signifiées ou qui sont signifiées à nos sociétés affiliées, filiales, vendeurs sous contrat ou partenaires d’affinité, ou enquêter, prévenir ou prendre des mesures concernant des activités illégales suspectées ou réelles; (b) appliquer nos Conditions ou notre contrat client (y compris à des fins de facturation et de collecte); (c) prendre des précautions contre la responsabilité; (d) enquêter et nous défendre contre toute réclamation ou allégation de tiers; (e) aider les organismes d’application de la loi ou répondre aux exigences de sécurité nationales ou gouvernementales; (f) protéger la sécurité ou l’intégrité de nos Sites Web, de nos Services et de nos applications mobiles; ou (g) exercer ou protéger les droits, la propriété ou la sécurité personnelle de nous, de nos utilisateurs ou d’autres personnes. 

Nous tenterons de vous informer, dans la mesure du possible, de ces demandes, à moins que : (i) l’envoi d’un avis ne soit interdit par le processus légal lui-même, par une ordonnance du tribunal que nous recevons, ou par la loi applicable, ou (ii) nous estimions que l’envoi d’un avis serait futile, inefficace, créerait un risque de blessure ou de préjudice corporel ou autre pour un individu ou un groupe, ou créerait ou augmenterait un risque de fraude à notre égard, à l’égard de nos utilisateurs, de nos Sites Web, de nos Services ou de nos applications mobiles. Dans les cas où nous nous conformons à des demandes légales sans préavis pour ces raisons, nous tenterons d’informer cet utilisateur de la demande après coup si nous déterminons de bonne foi qu’il ne nous est plus légalement interdit de le faire et qu’aucun des scénarios de risque décrits dans ce paragraphe ne s’applique.

3.6 DIVULGATION DE RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS DÉPERSONNALISÉS
------------------------------------------------------------

Nous pouvons partager des Renseignements personnels dépersonnalisés (y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, les données d’utilisation anonymes, les pages et les URL de renvoi/sortie, les adresses IP, les types de plateforme, le nombre de clics, etc.) avec des parties non affiliées de la manière que nous choisissons et à quelque fin que ce soit, telle que pour l’administration du système et pour surveiller l’utilisation des Sites Web; pour mesurer le nombre de visites sur nos Sites Web, le temps moyen passé, le nombre de pages consultées; et pour surveiller diverses autres statistiques des Sites Web afin d’améliorer le contenu.

4\.  DEMANDE DE REFUS DE SUIVI
==============================

Certains navigateurs Web (y compris Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox et Chrome) intègrent une fonction de refus du suivi (Do Not Track, DNT) ou similaire qui signale aux sites Web qu’un utilisateur ne veut pas faire suivre son activité et son comportement en ligne. Si un site Web qui répond à un signal DNT particulier reçoit le signal DNT, le navigateur peut empêcher ce site Web de recueillir certaines informations sur l’utilisateur du navigateur. Les navigateurs n’offrent pas tous une option DNT et les signaux DNT ne sont pas encore uniformes. Pour cette raison, de nombreux exploitants de Sites Web, y compris PlugShare, ne répondent pas aux signaux DNT.

5\. COMMUNICATIONS, PRÉFÉRENCES ET RETRAIT DE PLUGSHARE
=======================================================

En nous fournissant votre adresse courriel, vous consentez à ce que nous utilisions cette adresse courriel pour vous envoyer des avis relatifs au Service par courriel, y compris, mais sans s’y limiter, tout avis requis par la loi (par exemple, avis de protection des données ou d’incidents de sécurité), au lieu de la communication par courrier. Vous acceptez également que nous puissions vous envoyer des notifications d’activité concernant nos Produits, Services, Sites Web, applications mobiles, vos Renseignements personnels ou tout autre aspect de notre relation, à l’adresse courriel que vous nous avez donnée, conformément aux paramètres de confidentialité applicables. Nous pouvons utiliser votre adresse courriel pour vous envoyer d’autres messages ou contenus, tels que, mais sans s’y limiter, des bulletins d’information, des ajouts ou des modifications aux fonctionnalités du Service, ou des offres spéciales. Si vous ne souhaitez pas recevoir de tels courriels, vous pouvez vous désabonner en cliquant sur « Se désabonner » lorsque cela est possible. Le refus peut vous empêcher de recevoir des courriels concernant des mises à jour, des améliorations, des fonctionnalités spéciales, des annonces ou des offres. Vous ne pouvez pas vous désabonner des courriels liés au Service. Si vous avez choisi de ne pas nous fournir une adresse courriel ou autre, vous pourriez ne pas recevoir nos courriels liés au Service.

Par le biais de la page des paramètres de votre compte utilisateur, vous pouvez accéder et, dans certains cas, modifier ou supprimer certaines informations que vous nous avez fournies, telles que le nom et le mot de passe, l’adresse courriel, l’adresse, les informations du profil utilisateur, etc. Les informations que vous pouvez consulter, mettre à jour et supprimer peuvent changer au fur et à mesure que les Produits, Sites Web, Services ou nos pratiques évoluent. Si vous avez des questions sur la consultation ou la mise à jour des informations que nous détenons sur vous, veuillez nous contacter. Toutefois, lorsque vous mettez à jour des informations, nous pouvons conserver une copie des informations non révisées dans nos dossiers. Vous pouvez demander la suppression de votre compte en nous envoyant un courriel. Il est de votre responsabilité de conserver votre adresse courriel actuelle avec nous. Selon l’État ou le pays dans lequel vous résidez, vous pouvez avoir des droits supplémentaires. Veuillez voir ci-dessous pour plus d’informations.

6\. DÉVELOPPEURS UTILISANT DES SERVICES DE PLATEFORME PLUGSHARE
===============================================================

Nous collaborons avec des tiers et leur permettons d’utiliser la plateforme de développeur PlugShare pour offrir des services et des fonctionnalités en conjonction avec PlugShare. Ces développeurs tiers ont négocié une entente pour utiliser la technologie de la plateforme PlugShare ou ont accepté nos interfaces de programmation d’applications en libre-service (« API ») et nos conditions de plugiciel afin de créer des applications de plateforme logicielle (« Applications de plateforme »). Les contrats négociés ainsi que les conditions d’utilisation de nos API et Plugiciels contiennent des restrictions sur la manière dont les tiers peuvent accéder, stocker et utiliser les renseignements personnels que vous fournissez à PlugShare. Si vous choisissez d’utiliser une Application de plateforme, il vous sera demandé de confirmer l’acceptation de la politique de confidentialité et du contrat d’utilisation du développeur tiers. Pour révoquer l’autorisation accordée à une Application de plateforme, veuillez consulter vos paramètres. Notez toutefois que même si vous révoquez l’autorisation accordée à une Application de plateforme, vos connexions peuvent toujours utiliser l’Application de plateforme, de sorte que l’Application de plateforme peut toujours avoir accès à certaines informations vous concernant, tout comme vos connexions.

7\. CONSERVATION DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS
==============================================

La période pendant laquelle nous conservons vos Renseignements personnels dépend des fins pour lesquelles nous les utilisons. Nous conserverons vos Renseignements personnels aussi longtemps que votre compte sera actif, ou tant que vous êtes un titulaire de compte enregistré ou un utilisateur de nos Services ou aussi longtemps que nous avons un autre objectif commercial de le faire (comme mais sans s’y limiter, pour les affaires, taxes, ou à des fins juridiques) et, par la suite, pour une durée ne dépassant pas celle requise ou permise par la loi, ou notre politique de conservation des dossiers, raisonnablement nécessaire aux fins de rapports internes et de rapprochement, ou pour vous fournir des commentaires ou des renseignements que vous pourriez demander. Cette période de conservation est soumise à notre examen et à notre modification. Nous pouvons conserver les Renseignements personnels anonymisés aussi longtemps que nous le jugeons approprié.

À la suite de la résiliation ou de la désactivation de votre compte d’utilisateur, nous pouvons conserver les renseignements de votre profil et tous les renseignements affichés sur les zones publiques des Sites Web. À la suite de la résiliation ou de la désactivation de votre compte utilisateur, nous pouvons conserver vos Renseignements personnels et autres données, mais nous en assurerons la confidentialité conformément aux Conditions, à la présente Politique de confidentialité et aux exigences de la loi applicable. Nous avons le droit de supprimer tous vos Renseignements personnels et autres données après la résiliation de votre compte d’utilisateur sans préavis.

8\. AUCUNE COLLECTE INTENTIONNELLE DE DONNÉES D’ENFANTS
=======================================================

Nous ne recueillons, ne sollicitons ou ne conservons pas sciemment des Renseignements personnels de quiconque âgé de moins de 18 ans et nous ne permettons pas sciemment à ces personnes de s’inscrire ou d’utiliser nos Services. Si vous avez moins de 18 ans, veuillez ne pas nous envoyer de Renseignements personnels. Dans le cas où nous apprenons que nous avons recueilli des Renseignements personnels auprès d’un enfant de moins de 18 ans sans vérification du consentement parental, nous déploierons des efforts commercialement raisonnables pour supprimer ces renseignements de notre base de données.

9\. OÙ LES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS SONT TRAITÉS ET STOCKÉS; DROIT APPLICABLE
==============================================================================

Notre siège social est situé aux États-Unis. Les Renseignements personnels que nous ou nos Prestataires de services recueillons peuvent être stockés et traités sur des serveurs à l’intérieur ou à l’extérieur des États-Unis et partout où nous et nos Prestataires de services avons des installations dans le monde, et certains renseignements peuvent être accessibles par des personnes ou des entreprises à l’extérieur des États-Unis qui nous fournissent des services. Vous consentez à ce que nos Prestataires de services et nous-mêmes transmettions et/ou transférions vos Renseignements personnels à des juridictions, ou y accédions, qui peuvent ne pas offrir des niveaux de protection des données équivalents à ceux de votre juridiction d’origine. Nous prendrons des mesures raisonnables pour nous assurer que vos Renseignements personnels bénéficient d’un niveau de protection adéquat dans les juridictions où nous les traitons.

Les lois américaines s’appliquent dans la mesure où vous êtes un résident des États-Unis. Autrement, la présente Politique de confidentialité et toutes les autres questions doivent être interprétées conformément aux lois d’État, provinciales et fédérales de votre juridiction de résidence. Les juridictions à l’extérieur de votre lieu de résidence peuvent avoir des lois sur la protection de la vie privée différentes de celles de votre juridiction, y compris le droit des autorités policières et gouvernementales d’accéder aux Renseignements personnels.  Dans la mesure où nous traitons des données à l’extérieur de votre pays, nous entreprenons une évaluation de l’impact sur la confidentialité pour déterminer que nos Prestataires de services peuvent offrir sensiblement le même niveau de protection que celui requis dans votre juridiction et concluons des contrats pour renforcer davantage les obligations de traiter correctement vos Renseignements personnels.

10\. SÉCURITÉ
=============

Nous avons mis en place des mesures de sécurité techniques et organisationnelles conçues pour protéger vos Renseignements personnels contre la perte accidentelle et contre l’accès, l’utilisation, la destruction, l’altération et la divulgation non autorisés. Cependant, n’oubliez pas qu’Internet n’est pas un environnement entièrement sécurisé. Il est de votre responsabilité de protéger la sécurité de vos informations de connexion, de faire preuve de prudence lors de la transmission de tout Renseignement personnel par courriel, messagerie instantanée et autres moyens de communication similaires, et de maintenir de bonnes pratiques de sécurité sur Internet. Nous ne vous enverrons jamais de courriel pour vous demander votre mot de passe ou d’autres informations de connexion à votre compte. Si vous recevez un tel courriel, veuillez nous l’envoyer afin que nous puissions enquêter.

11\. DROITS SUPPLÉMENTAIRES DES PERSONNES CONCERNÉES POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINES JURIDICTIONS DÉCRITES DANS LES AVIS DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ SUPPLÉMENTAIRES
===========================================================================================================================================================

Ce qui suit explique chaque droit de personne concernée décrit dans les Avis de confidentialité supplémentaires :

* Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité : Vous avez le droit de recevoir certains renseignements requis par la loi au moment de la collecte ou avant celui-ci, ou en réponse à votre demande.
* Droit de suppression : Vous pouvez nous demander de supprimer tout Renseignement personnel vous concernant que nous avons recueilli auprès de vous, sous réserve de certaines exceptions.
* Droit de correction : Vous pouvez nous demander de corriger tout Renseignement personnel inexact que nous conservons à votre sujet.
* Droit de savoir : Vous pouvez demander que nous vous fournissions des renseignements précis sur la façon dont nous avons traité vos Renseignements personnels, y compris en vous fournissant une copie des Renseignements personnels spécifiques que nous avons recueillis à votre sujet dans un format portable.
* Droit à la non-discrimination : Vous avez le droit de ne pas faire l’objet de discrimination pour avoir exercé vos droits en tant que personne concernée. Cela signifie ne pas qu’il ne faut pas vous refuser des biens ou des services, ne pas vous facturer des prix ou des tarifs différents ou ne pas vous fournir un niveau de qualité différent pour des produits ou des services parce que vous avez exercé vos droits en tant que personne concernée.
* Droits de retrait : Vous pouvez demander de refuser la vente et le partage de vos Renseignements personnels, la publicité comportementale multicontexte ou ciblée, la prise de décision automatisée ou le profilage, dans la mesure où ces activités sont définies et restreintes en vertu des lois applicables.
* Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer : Vous pouvez nous demander de supprimer ou de cesser le traitement de certains de vos Renseignements personnels, mais nous pouvons toujours stocker vos Renseignements personnels.  
* Droit de limiter l’utilisation de vos Renseignements personnels sensibles : Vous pouvez demander de limiter l’utilisation de vos Renseignements personnels sensibles uniquement aux fins autorisées par les lois applicables.
* Droit de déposer une plainte : Vous avez le droit de déposer une plainte auprès de votre autorité locale de protection des données si vous estimez que le traitement des Renseignements personnels vous concernant enfreint vos droits.
* Droit de retirer votre consentement : Dans la mesure où notre traitement de vos Renseignements personnels est uniquement fondé sur votre consentement, vous pouvez retirer ce consentement à tout moment.

12\. COORDONNÉES
================

PlugShare a désigné un Responsable de la protection des données comme étant la personne qui supervisera la conformité aux exigences de confidentialité. Le Responsable de la protection des données de PlugShare peut être contacté à l’adresse ci-dessous pour toute question relative à la politique de confidentialité.

Si vous avez des questions ou des commentaires sur cette Politique de confidentialité ou sur nos pratiques de confidentialité, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse suivante : PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 États-Unis; À l’attention de : Responsable de la protection des données; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

AVIS DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINS ÉTATS DES ÉTATS-UNIS
===========================================================================

Si vous êtes un résident de la Californie, de la Virginie, du Colorado, de l’Utah ou du Connecticut (parfois appelé « Consommateur » dans les présentes), les lois d’État vous accordent des droits supplémentaires concernant notre utilisation de vos Renseignements personnels.

LOI CALIFORNIENNE SHINE THE LIGHT
---------------------------------

L’article 1798.83 du Code civil de la Californie, connu sous le nom de loi « Shine The Light », permet à tous les utilisateurs qui sont résidents de la Californie de demander et d’obtenir de nous une liste des Renseignements personnels (le cas échéant) que nous avons divulgués à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct au cours de l’année civile précédente et les noms et adresses de ces tiers. Les demandes ne peuvent être faites qu’une fois par an et sont gratuites.

CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (« CALOPPA »; CALIF. BUS. & PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, DISPONIBLE [ICI](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D))
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA ne s’applique qu’aux entreprises qui recueillent des renseignements personnels des résidents de la Californie.

1. COMMENT NOUS RÉPONDONS AUX SIGNAUX « DO NOT TRACK » (NE PAS SUIVRE)

Certains navigateurs Web transmettent des signaux « Do not track » (DNT/GPC) aux sites Web et autres services en ligne avec lesquels votre navigateur Web communique. Il n’existe actuellement aucune norme régissant ce que les sites Web doivent faire, le cas échéant, lorsqu’ils reçoivent ces signaux; cependant, nous disposons actuellement de mesures pour agir en réponse à ces signaux.

2. SUIVI COMPORTEMENTAL TIERS

Nous pouvons également utiliser ces technologies pour recueillir des informations sur vos activités en ligne au fil du temps et sur des sites Web de tiers ou d’autres services en ligne, ou associer des Renseignements personnels à d’autres informations recueillies de cette manière. Nous pouvons utiliser les Renseignements personnels pour suivre les habitudes de clic et de navigation des utilisateurs.

CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT DE 2018 (« CCPA », DISPONIBLE [ICI](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) ET SON SUCCESSEUR, LE CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT DE 2020 (« CPRA », DISPONIBLE [ICI](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)).
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Le tableau ci-dessous détaille la façon dont nous divulguons les renseignements personnels que nous avons recueillis à votre sujet :

| Catégorie | Catégories de tiers non affiliés à qui nous divulguons des renseignements personnels | Catégories de tiers non affiliés à qui nous vendons ou partageons des renseignements personnels |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificateurs | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Fournisseurs de gestion des identités<br><br>Fournisseurs de solutions de paiement<br><br>Fournisseurs de sondages et de recherche<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de médias sociaux | s.o. |
| Données démographiques | Fournisseurs de sondages et de recherche | s.o. |
| Renseignements commerciaux | s.o. | s.o. |
| Activité sur Internet ou autre réseau électronique; renseignements sur l’appareil | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de bases de données et de logiciels<br><br>Fournisseurs de gestion des identités<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de médias sociaux | s.o. |
| Géolocalisation | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de bases de données et de logiciels<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de médias sociaux | s.o. |
| Autre | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de bases de données et de logiciels<br><br>Fournisseurs de sondages et de recherche<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de médias sociaux | Fabricants, détaillants et grossistes |

Vous pouvez communiquer avec nous pour exercer les droits suivants en vertu de la CCPA et de la CPRA (veuillez consulter la section 11 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale pour obtenir des descriptions de ces droits) :

1. Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité.
2. Droit de savoir ce qui suit :

* Les catégories de Renseignements personnels que nous avons recueillis à votre sujet.
* Les catégories de sources de Renseignements personnels que nous avons recueillis à votre sujet.
* Notre objectif commercial ou d’affaires pour recueillir ces Renseignements personnels.
* Les catégories de tiers avec lesquels nous partageons ces Renseignements personnels.
* Les Renseignements personnels spécifiques que nous avons recueillis à votre sujet (aussi appelés demande de portabilité des données); nous vous en fournissons une copie sous forme électronique ou papier.
* Si nous avons divulgué vos Renseignements personnels à des fins commerciales, une liste de divulgation à des fins commerciales, identifiant les catégories de Renseignements personnels que chaque catégorie de destinataire a obtenues.

3. Droit de suppression.
4. Droit de correction.
5. Droit de se retirer de la publicité comportementale multicontexte, de la vente ou du partage de Renseignements personnels, du traitement des Renseignements personnels à des fins de profilage, et de la prise de décision automatisée.
6. Droit de limiter l’utilisation de vos Renseignements personnels sensibles. Veuillez noter que nous n’utilisons pas les Renseignements personnels sensibles vous concernant à des fins non autorisées par la CCPA et la CPRA.

VIRGINIA CONSUMER DATA PROTECTION ACT (VCDPA), COLORADO PRIVACY ACT (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), UTAH CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) ET CONNECTICUT DATA PRIVACY ACT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Vous pouvez communiquer avec nous pour exercer les droits suivants en vertu de ces lois spécifiques à chaque État :

1. Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité.
2. Droit de savoir.
3. Droit de suppression.
4. Droit de correction.
5. Droit de se retirer de la publicité ciblée ou de la vente de Renseignements personnels.
6. Droit de refuser le profilage (traitement automatisé de renseignements personnels à des fins d’analyse ou de prévision des caractéristiques d’une personne ou de son comportement futur, aboutissant à des décisions qui affectent les droits substantiels d’une personne).  
7. Les consommateurs de Virginie, du Colorado et du Connecticut ont également le droit faire appel de nos décisions concernant leurs demandes en tant que personnes concernées en communiquant avec nous par la même méthode que celle utilisée pour soumettre une demande. Veuillez joindre une copie de notre décision ou faire référence à celle-ci de manière spécifique sur votre demande en tant que personne concernée afin que nous puissions traiter adéquatement votre appel. Nous répondrons à votre appel conformément à la loi applicable.

NEVADA
------

Comme décrit ci-dessus, nous pouvons vendre vos identifiants ou d’autres renseignements pouvant permettre de vous identifier que nous recueillons sur nos Sites Web et nos Services en ligne à des parties non affiliées à des fins de suivi du comportement multi-contexte au sens de la loi du Nevada. Vous disposez d’un Droit de retrait de la vente ou de l’octroi de licences pour ces catégories de renseignements personnels vous concernant à des parties non affiliées.

EXERCER VOS DROITS
------------------

Pour exercer les droits d’accès, de rectification, de portabilité des données et d’effacement décrits ci-dessus, veuillez nous en faire la demande en utilisant notre formulaire Web disponible [ici](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Seul vous ou une personne que vous avez autorisée à agir en votre nom peut faire une demande relative à vos Renseignements personnels. Vous pouvez également faire une demande au nom de votre enfant mineur. Si nous recevons une demande de la part d’une personne pour exercer un droit en votre nom, nous vous demanderons une copie de votre autorisation signée donnant l’autorisation de soumettre de telles demandes en votre nom et nous vous contacterons pour confirmer directement cette autorisation. Vous ne pouvez faire une demande d’accès ou de portabilité des données que deux fois au cours d’une période de 12 mois. La demande vérifiable du consommateur doit :

* Fournir suffisamment de renseignements qui nous permettent de vérifier raisonnablement que vous êtes la personne au sujet de laquelle nous avons recueilli des Renseignements personnels ou qu’un représentant autorisé a fait la demande;
* Décrire votre demande avec suffisamment de détails pour nous permettre de bien la comprendre, l’évaluer et y répondre.

Nous ne pouvons pas répondre à votre demande ou vous fournir des Renseignements personnels si nous ne pouvons pas vérifier votre identité ou votre autorité pour faire la demande et confirmer que les Renseignements personnels vous concernent. Faire une demande ne vous oblige pas à créer un compte chez nous. Nous n’utiliserons les Renseignements personnels fournis dans une demande que pour vérifier l’identité du demandeur ou l’autorité de faire la demande.

Pour exercer les droits de retrait de la publicité comportementale inter-contexte, de la publicité ciblée ou du partage des Renseignements personnels tel que décrit ci-dessus, vous devrez vous retirer en fonction de la plateforme sur laquelle vous vous trouvez.  Notez que votre demande de retrait est spécifique à l’appareil et à la plateforme où vous soumettez cette demande, de sorte que vous devrez peut-être soumettre plusieurs demandes si vous avez l’intention de vous retirer de ces activités de traitement spécifiques pour plusieurs appareils et plateformes. Cliquez ici :

* pour vous désinscrire de Plugshare.com (plateforme Web)
* pour vous désinscrire de l’application iOS Plugshare
* pour vous désinscrire de l’application Android Plugshare

### Processus de vérification

Dès réception d’une demande d’accès, de rectification, de portabilité des données ou d’effacement de données de votre part, nous vous enverrons un courriel dans les 10 jours ouvrables à l’adresse courriel que nous avons pour vous dans nos dossiers. Le courriel vous demandera de répondre pour vérifier que vous êtes le consommateur qui fait la demande. À la réception de votre vérification, nous ferons correspondre vos renseignements à ceux qui se trouvent dans notre dossier. Après vérification de votre identité, nous traiterons votre demande et y répondrons dans les 45 jours civils, à moins que (a) nous ne soyons pas en mesure de vérifier votre demande, (b) si nous ne sommes pas en mesure de vous faire correspondre avec les renseignements contenus dans notre base de données, ou (c) si une exception en vertu de la loi existe, nous exemptant de nous conformer à votre demande. Si nous avons besoin de plus de temps (jusqu’à quarante-cinq \[45\] jours civils supplémentaires), nous vous informerons par écrit de la raison et de la période de prolongation.

Si nous ne sommes pas en mesure de donner suite à votre demande, la réponse que nous vous fournirons en expliquera les raisons. Pour les demandes de portabilité des données, nous sélectionnerons un format pour fournir vos Renseignements personnels qui sont facilement utilisables et qui devraientt vous permettre de transmettre les renseignements d’une entité à une autre sans entrave.

Nous ne facturons pas de frais pour traiter ou répondre à votre demande vérifiable de consommateur, à moins qu’elle ne soit excessive, répétitive ou manifestement infondée. Si nous déterminons que la demande justifie des frais, nous vous expliquerons pourquoi nous avons pris cette décision et nous vous fournirons une estimation des coûts avant de traiter votre demande.

* * *

AVIS DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ POUR CERTAINS PAYS AUTRES QUE LES ÉTATS-UNIS
====================================================================

RENSEIGNEMENTS GÉNÉRAUX
-----------------------

1. ### VOTRE CONSENTEMENT SPÉCIFIQUE AU TRAITEMENT DES CATÉGORIES « SENSIBLES » OU « SPÉCIALES » DE RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS

En vertu des lois sur la confidentialité de certains pays, certains types de Renseignements personnels sont considérés comme des catégories d’informations « sensibles » ou « spéciale ». Nous traitons rarement des catégories de données sensibles ou spéciales, sauf si cela est dans votre intérêt vital ou dans celui d’une autre personne. Dans toutes les autres circonstances, vous consentez spécifiquement à la collecte, au traitement et à la conservation de catégories sensibles ou spéciales de Renseignements personnels, comme décrit à la section 1.2 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale, et vous consentez autrement au traitement des Renseignements personnels conformément au présent Avis de confidentialité.  

2. ### FONDEMENTS JURIDIQUES DE NOTRE TRAITEMENT DES RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS

Nos fondements juridiques pour recueillir et utiliser les Renseignements personnels décrits ci-dessus dépendront des Renseignements personnels concernés et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les recueillons. D’une manière générale, nous ne recueillerons et ne traiterons vos Renseignements personnels que lorsque nous en aurons besoin pour vous fournir les Services pour lesquels vous avez passé un contrat avec nous, ou lorsque le traitement est dans notre intérêt légitime et que vos intérêts en matière de protection des données ou vos droits et libertés fondamentaux ne prévalent pas, nous nous fonderons sur votre consentement lorsque nous sommes légalement tenus de le faire.  Dans certains cas, nous pouvons également avoir une obligation légale de recueillir des Renseignements personnels auprès de vous ou avoir besoin de ces renseignements pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux ou ceux d’une autre personne.

BASE D’INTÉRÊT LÉGITIME POUR LA COLLECTE DE RENSEIGNEMENTS PERSONNELS : La collecte et le traitement de vos Renseignements personnels peuvent être nécessaires aux fins de nos intérêts légitimes. Ces objectifs d’intérêt légitime peuvent comprendre :

* prévention de la fraude;
* sécurité du réseau et de l’information;
* indication d’éventuels actes criminels ou de menaces pour la sécurité publique, y compris l’amélioration de la protection de notre communauté contre les pourriels, le harcèlement, les atteintes à la propriété intellectuelle, les crimes et les risques de sécurité de toutes sortes, et l’application des réclamations légales, y compris l’enquête sur les violations potentielles de nos Conditions d’utilisation;
* lorsque nous nous conformons à des obligations légales;
* traitement des données relatives aux employés ou aux visiteurs, aux membres, aux participants ou aux inscrits;
* exécution de la fonction ou du service que vous nous avez demandé;
* fourniture de nos Services et de leurs fonctionnalités lorsque ce traitement est nécessaire aux fins des intérêts légitimes poursuivis par nous ou par nos prestataires de services liés aux Services;
* marketing direct;
* relation pertinente et appropriée que nous entretenons avec vous;
* analyse, c’est-à-dire l’évaluation du nombre de visiteurs, des pages consultées, de l’utilisation des Sites Web, etc., afin de comprendre comment nos Sites Web, nos Produits et nos Services sont utilisés, d’optimiser les Sites Web et/ou les communications futures, et de développer de nouveaux services et de nouvelles fonctionnalités des Sites Web;
* mise à jour de vos renseignements et préférences;
* offre et amélioration de nos Sites Web, Produits et Services;
* application des réclamations légales, y compris l’enquête sur les violations potentielles de nos Conditions.

Outre les informations fournies ci-dessus, les sections suivantes s’appliquent uniquement aux résidents ou citoyens du pays ou de la région dont il est question. Aux fins des sections suivantes, sauf mention expresse, la définition de « Renseignements personnels » telle qu’utilisée ci-dessus correspond à la définition de renseignements personnels, de données personnelles ou d’un terme similaire applicable en vertu des lois de protection des données de ce pays ou de cette région. En cas de conflit entre les sections ci-dessous et les sections ci-dessus, les sections ci-dessous prévaudront.

RGPD – AVIS DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ AUX RÉSIDENTS DE L’ESPACE ÉCONOMIQUE EUROPÉEN (EEE), DU ROYAUME-UNI ET DE LA SUISSE
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### APERÇU

Les dispositions suivantes ne s’appliquent que si vous êtes un résident de l’EEE, du Royaume-Uni ou de la Suisse (désignés dans la présente section par commodité comme la « Région de l’UE »).

Pour ces résidents, tous les traitements de vos Renseignements personnels sont effectués conformément aux droits et règlements relatifs à la protection de la vie privée, en particulier, (UE) 2016/679 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 27 avril 2016, connue sous le nom de Règlement général sur la protection des données ou de Règlement général sur la protection des données du Royaume-Uni pour les résidents du Royaume-Uni (collectivement, « RGPD »), et notre traitement aura lieu conformément au RGPD. Aux fins du RGPD, nous serons le « responsable du traitement des données » des renseignements personnels (désignés et définis dans le RGPD (disponible [ici](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) comme « données personnelles ») que nous recueillons, à moins que nous ne recueillions ces renseignements pour le compte d’un « responsable du traitement des données », auquel cas nous serons un « sous-traitant des données ». Cette Politique de confidentialité ne s’applique pas aux sites Web, aux applications ou aux services qui n’affichent pas cette Politique de confidentialité ou qui n’ont pas de lien avec elle, ou qui affichent ou ont un lien avec une politique de confidentialité différente. Pour les résidents et citoyens de la région de l’UE uniquement, dans la mesure où toute définition de la présente Politique de confidentialité est en conflit avec une définition du RGPD, la définition du RGPD prévaut.

Nous fournissons une protection adéquate pour le transfert de renseignements personnels vers des pays situés en dehors de la Région UE par le biais d’une ou plusieurs des méthodes suivantes : (a) une série de contrats interentreprises basés sur ou intégrant les Clauses contractuelles types, (b) nous pouvons nous appuyer sur les décisions d’adéquation de la Commission européenne concernant certains pays, le cas échéant, (c) nous pouvons obtenir votre consentement pour ces transferts de données de la Région UE aux États-Unis vers d’autres pays, (d) nous pouvons adopter des règles d’organisation contraignantes, ou (e) dans la mesure où cela est applicable, nous pouvons nous appuyer sur les dérogations énoncées à l’article 49 du RGPD pour le transfert et la poursuite du transfert de renseignements personnels recueillis auprès de personnes de la Région UE vers les États-Unis et d’autres pays que la Région UE considère comme ne fournissant pas une protection des données adéquate. En ce qui concerne la méthode (e), nous pouvons transférer les Renseignements personnels à un tiers pour exécuter un contrat avec vous, avec votre consentement explicite ou d’une manière qui ne l’emporte pas sur vos droits et libertés. Si ces Renseignements personnels ne sont pas traités et transférés, nous ne serons pas en mesure d’exécuter le contrat avec vous ou vous n’aurez pas accès à tout ou partie des avantages et des fonctionnalités associés à votre transaction.

Nous pouvons également être amenés à transférer vos informations à d’autres sociétés du groupe ou à des prestataires de services dans des pays situés en dehors de la Région UE. Cela peut se produire si nos serveurs ou nos fournisseurs et prestataires de services sont basés en dehors de la Région UE, ou si vous utilisez nos Produits et/ou Services lorsque vous visitez des pays en dehors de ces régions.

Nos fondements juridiques pour recueillir vos Renseignements personnels sont abordés .

2. ### VOS DROITS EN MATIÈRE DE DONNÉES EN VERTU DU GDPR.

Si vous êtes soumis au RGPD, vos droits comprennent les droits suivants :

* Droit de savoir.
* Droit de correction.
* Droit de suppression.
* Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer.Vous avez le droit de vous opposer à vos Renseignements personnels utilisés de la manière suivante : (a) le traitement basé sur des intérêts légitimes ou l’exécution d’une tâche dans l’intérêt public/l’exercice de l’autorité officielle (y compris le profilage); (b) le marketing direct (y compris le profilage); et (c) le traitement à des fins de recherche scientifique/historique et de statistiques. Voir ci-dessous pour plus d’informations.
* Droits de retrait. Vous avez le droit de ne pas faire l’objet d’une décision fondée uniquement sur le traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage, qui produit des effets juridiques vous concernant ou qui vous affecte de manière significative, sauf les exceptions applicables en vertu des lois pertinentes sur la protection des données.
* Droit de déposer une plainte. Si vous résidez dans l’EEE, une liste des autorités nationales de protection des données se trouve [ici](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Si vous résidez au Royaume-Uni, vous pouvez communiquer avec le bureau du Commissaire à l’information [ici.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/-mb)
* Droit de retirer votre consentement.

AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINS AUTRES (NON AMÉRICAINS) PAYS
-----------------------------------------------------------

Ce qui suit s’ajoute aux renseignements abordés dans notre principale Politique de confidentialité.

Nous honorerons les droits suivants des personnes concernées pour tous les résidents à l’extérieur des États-Unis :

* Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité :

* notre identité et nos coordonnées;
* l’objectif spécifique de notre traitement de vos Renseignements personnels;
* la forme et la durée de notre traitement de vos Renseignements personnels;
* des informations sur notre partage et notre objectif de partage de vos Renseignements personnels;
* les responsabilités de tout tiers traitant vos Renseignements personnels; et
* les renseignements concernant toute entité juridique publique et privée avec laquelle nous avons partagé vos Renseignements personnels.

* Droit de savoir :

* décisions prises exclusivement sur la base du traitement automatisé des Renseignements personnels;
* accéder aux Renseignements personnels que nous recueillons.

* Droit de correction.
* Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer.
* Droit de retirer votre consentement.

Toute traduction de la présente Politique de confidentialité dans une langue autre que l’anglais est fournie uniquement à titre d’information. En cas de divergence, la seule version juridiquement valide et contraignante sera la version anglaise du présent document.

1. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE L’ARGENTINE

Les mesures de sécurité techniques et organisationnelles mises en œuvre par PlugShare soutiendraient également les règles de la loi argentine sur la protection des données personnelles (LPDP) 25.326, telles que l’interdiction de toute utilisation secondaire des données personnelles d’une personne concernée et l’interdiction de transférer des données personnelles vers des pays n’offrant pas un niveau de protection adéquat. PlugShare utilise un contrat de transfert/traitement des données pour aider au respect de la disposition 60-E/2016 de la PDPA, qui réglemente le transfert transfrontalier des données personnelles.

Les résidents de l’Argentine ont (a) le Droit de savoir des informations sur l’existence et le but de ces Renseignements personnels, et (b) le Droit de de correction et le Droit de restreindre ou de s’opposer au traitement de vos Renseignements personnels s’ils sont faux, inexacts ou discriminatoires.

2. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE L’AUSTRALIE

Nous pouvons utiliser et divulguer vos Renseignements personnels (telles que définies par la loi australienne) à des tiers basés en dehors de l’Australie, principalement aux États-Unis, comme décrit dans les sections 9 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale. Vous acceptez et reconnaissez que les destinataires étrangers seront soumis à la loi sur la protection des renseignements personnels de leur juridiction locale et peuvent ne pas être soumis à des obligations en matière de protection des renseignements personnels ou à des principes similaires aux principes relatifs à la protection des renseignements personnels australiens. Ils seront également soumis à une loi étrangère qui pourrait obliger la divulgation de Renseignements personnels à un tiers, tel qu’une autorité étrangère. À moins que vous ne nous informiez par écrit du contraire, nous considérerons que vous avez consenti à la divulgation par nous de Renseignements personnels à des destinataires étrangers. Vous avez la possibilité de rester anonyme lorsque vous traitez avec nous, ou de ne pas nous divulguer certains Renseignements personnels. Toutefois, cela pourrait nous empêcher de vous fournir nos Services.

Pour les résidents de l’Australie, les mises à jour de cette politique de confidentialité sont effectives si nous Obtenons votre consentement exprès ou si nous vous offrons une option de retrait lorsque des changements importants sont annoncés (par exemple, sur nos Sites Web ou par courriel).

3. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DU BRÉSIL

Les résidents du Brésil ont le Droit de savoir les informations suivantes : si la fourniture de vos Renseignements personnels est une exigence contractuelle, ou s’il y a des conséquences à ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non aux deux), des informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (voir la section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), vous avez le droit de retirer votre consentement au traitement de vos Renseignements personnels, et, vos droits d’accès aux personnes concernées (voir ci-dessous).

Les résidents du Brésil ont également : (a) le Droit de savoir, y compris d’obtenir une copie de ces renseignements; (b) le Droit de correction; (c) le Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer; (d) le Droit de suppression; (e) le Droit à la réception de renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité des entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos Renseignements personnels ont été partagés; et (f) le Droit de déposer une plainte auprès de l’autorité brésilienne de contrôle des données (ANPD).

4. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DU CANADA (Y COMPRIS LE QUÉBEC)

Notre Politique de confidentialité et nos pratiques générales sont conçues pour se conformer aux lois canadiennes sur la protection de la vie privée, y compris la Loi sur la protection des renseignements personnels et les documents électroniques (LPRPDE) et, le cas échéant, la loi sur la protection de la vie privée du secteur privé du Québec, la Protection des renseignements personnels dans le secteur privé (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Pour toute pratique de traitement de l’information qui n’est pas raisonnablement liée aux fins pour lesquelles vous avez communiqué avec PlugShare, vous disposez du Droit de retrait de ces pratiques de traitement de l’information (y compris le marketing, le profilage, la publicité comportementale, le partage avec un tiers qui n’est pas un prestataire de services).  

Les résidents canadiens disposent du Droit de retrait de notre utilisation des Renseignements personnels à des fins de marketing direct et d’autres traitements qui ne sont pas raisonnablement nécessaires pour répondre à ce pour quoi vous nous avez engagés.

5. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE HONG KONG

Nous utilisons vos Renseignements personnels aux fins de marketing direct suivantes : (a) pour communiquer avec vous au sujet de nos produits et services et de ceux de nos sociétés affiliées; et (b) pour vous envoyer d’autres avis, promotions ou autres documents de marketing concernant nos Sites Web, nos Produits et nos Services, et ceux de nos sociétés affiliées. Votre consentement à cette fin vous sera demandé au moment où vous nous soumettez des Renseignements personnels (par exemple, lors de la création d’un compte, de l’inscription à un événement, etc.

6. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DU MEXIQUE

Outre les informations présentées ci-dessus, les résidents du Mexique ont le Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les pratiques de confidentialité, y compris (a) si la fourniture de vos Renseignements personnels est une exigence contractuelle ou s’il y a des conséquences à ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non dans les deux cas), (b) des informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (ce qui est abordé à la section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (c) la durée de conservation des données (voir la section 7 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (d) le droit de retirer le consentement au traitement de vos Renseignements personnels, et, (e) vos droits d’accès en tant que personne concernée (voir ci-dessous). Vous avez également le droit de connaître l’indication expresse des Renseignements personnels sensibles à traiter.

Les résidents du Mexique ont également : (a) le Droit de savoir les Renseignements personnels que nous recueillons, y compris d’être informés des entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos Renseignements personnels ont été partagés et d’obtenir une copie de ces renseignements; (b) le Droit de correction; (c) le Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer au traitement; et (d) le Droit de suppression.

7. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE SINGAPOUR

Entre autres droits, si nous sommes présents à Singapour, vous avez le droit de faire transmettre les Renseignements personnels que nous possédons à une autre organisation.

Les personnes ou sociétés auxquelles nous divulguons et transférons vos Renseignements personnels peuvent être situées en dehors de Singapour. Nous veillerons à ce que les destinataires des Renseignements personnels transférés soient en mesure de fournir aux Renseignements personnels transférés un niveau de protection comparable aux normes de protection établies par la loi sur la protection de la vie privée de Singapour par le biais de contrats écrits de transfert de données (pour les transferts à des tiers) ou de règles d’organisation contraignantes (pour les transferts à nos sociétés affiliées et autres entités qui nous sont liées).

8. ### AVIS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE TAÏWAN

Les résidents de Taïwan disposent du Droit de recevoir des renseignements sur les Pratiques de confidentialité.

Les résidents de Taïwan ont également : (a) le Droit de savoir les Renseignements personnels que nous recueillons, y compris d’être informés des entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos Renseignements personnels ont été partagés et d’obtenir une copie de ces renseignements; (b) le Droit de correction; (c) le Droit de restreindre le traitement ou de s’y opposer au traitement; et (d) le Droit de suppression.

Outre les informations présentées ci-dessus, les résidents de Taïwan ont le Droit de savoir certaines informations sur les Renseignements personnels que nous recueillons, y compris (a) si la fourniture de vos Renseignements personnels est une exigence contractuelle ou s’il y a des conséquences à ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non dans les deux cas), (b) des informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (ce qui est abordé à la section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (c) la durée de conservation des données (voir la section 7 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (d) le droit de retirer le consentement au traitement de vos Renseignements personnels, et, (e) vos droits d’accès aux données (voir ci-dessous). Vous avez également le Droit de savoir l’indication expresse des Renseignements personnels sensibles à traiter (nous ne recueillons aucun renseignement « sensible »).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) La Colorado Privacy Act entrera en vigueur le 1er juillet 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) La Utah Consumer Privacy Act entrera en vigueur le 31 décembre 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) La Connecticut Data Privacy Act entrera en vigueur le 1er juillet 2023.

POLITIQUE DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ PLUGSHARE
======================================

DATE DE PRISE D’EFFET : 10 juillet 2023
---------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (« PlugShare » « nous », « notre » ou « nos ») a pour objectif de créer une communauté solidaire d’utilisateurs de Véhicules électriques (« VÉ ») et de fournir des informations de recharge à la pointe du secteur ainsi qu’une large gamme de produits et de services innovants pour rendre l’expérience de conduite des VÉ aussi facile et gratifiante que possible. La présente Politique de confidentialité énonce nos politiques sur la collecte, l’utilisation, la divulgation, la rétention, et le transfert des Informations personnelles (définies ci-dessous) que nous collectons à votre sujet (« vous » ou « votre/vos ») par le biais de nos interactions avec vous via nos Sites Web ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/) ou [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/), collectivement, « Sites Web »), les services correspondants et nos applications mobiles (collectivement les « Services »), ainsi que par le biais d’interactions avec des parties non affiliées telles que nos fournisseurs qui travaillent avec nous pour vous fournir nos Services.

Veuillez lire attentivement la présente Politique de confidentialité. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que nous traitions vos Informations personnelles, veuillez ne pas nous en fournir. Cependant, vous pourriez ne pas être en mesure de profiter de certaines fonctionnalités de nos Services.

Votre utilisation du Site Web et de nos Services est à tout moment également soumise à nos Conditions d’utilisation (disponibles sur [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) et mises à jour de temps à autre (les « Conditions »)).

La présente Politique de confidentialité ne s’applique pas à tout site ou service non affilié lié à ou provenant de nos Sites Web ou Services autres que ceux de nos Prestataires de services, à nos canaux ou plateformes de réseaux sociaux qui les hébergent, ou à tout site ou service recommandé ou auquel nous faisons référence par nos Sites Web ou Services ou par notre personnel.

Résidents de Californie, de Virginie, du Colorado, de l’Utah et du Connecticut : Veuillez consulter notre [Déclaration de confidentialité supplémentaire pour les résidents de certains États des États-Unis](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) concernant des informations supplémentaires sur notre traitement de vos Informations personnelles.

Résidents d’autres pays : Si vous résidez dans un pays autre que les États-Unis, veuillez consulter notre page de Déclaration de confidentialité supplémentaire pour certains pays non américains pour obtenir des informations supplémentaires sur notre traitement de vos Informations personnelles.

Nous nous efforçons constamment d’améliorer nos Services, et nous pouvons également devoir modifier la présente Politique de confidentialité de temps à autre. Notre Politique de confidentialité actuelle sera toujours disponible sur nos Sites Web. Veuillez noter la date de prise d'effet de la présente Politique de confidentialité et assurez-vous de vérifier régulièrement les mises à jour.

1\. QUELLES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES NOUS COLLECTONS
=====================================================

1.1 QUE SONT LES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES
------------------------------------------

La présente Politique de confidentialité couvre notre traitement de vos informations personnellement identifiables. « Informations personnelles » désigne généralement toute information non chiffrée qui identifie, se rapporte à, décrit, est raisonnablement capable d’être associée à, ou pourrait raisonnablement être liée à une personne particulière, comme notamment votre nom, votre adresse postale, votre adresse e-mail, votre numéro de téléphone, etc.

Les Informations personnelles n’incluent pas vos Informations personnelles qui ont été désidentifiées, anonymisées ou agrégées de la manière requise par les lois applicables afin que les informations ne puissent plus être utilisées directement ou par d’autres moyens raisonnablement disponibles pour identifier une personne (collectivement, les « Informations personnelles désidentifiées »).

1.2 CATÉGORIES D’INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES QUE NOUS COLLECTONS ET TRAITONS
--------------------------------------------------------------------------

Nous collectons plusieurs catégories d’Informations personnelles auprès de vous et à votre sujet, comme résumé dans le tableau suivant :

| Catégorie | Éléments spécifiques des informations personnelles |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiants | * prénom et nom<br>* nom d’utilisateur (qui peut inclure le prénom et le nom)<br>* adresse e-mail<br>* code postal<br>* sexe, genre<br>* identifiant personnel unique, par ex. nom ou numéro de compte ou de client, numéro de téléphone, identifiant d’appareil mobile |
| Données démographiques | * pays de résidence |
| Informations commerciales | * historique et tendances des achats de produits/services |
| Activité sur Internet ou autre réseau électronique, informations sur l’appareil | * type et fabricant du dispositif et son ID/UDID ou code similaire spécifique au dispositif<br>* système d’exploitation et plateforme<br>* résolution de l’écran<br>* nom du fournisseur d’accès à Internet ou de l’opérateur mobile, vitesse de connexion et type de connexion<br>* Adresse, protocole et informations de séquence du protocole Internet (ou IP)<br>* cookies<br>* balises pixels<br>* adresse MAC (Media Access Control) des pages que vous avez visitées<br>* identifiant publicitaire de l’appareil mobile<br>* type de navigateur, langue et version<br>* Navigation sur le site Web, session, interaction et historique de recherche, matériel et pages consultés, heure et date d’accès aux sites Web, nombre d’octets transférés, nombre de clics par visite, temps passé sur une page, données de clics et de flux de clics, requêtes effectuées, résultats de recherche sélectionnés, commentaires effectués<br>* date et URL de la dernière page Web visitée avant de visiter nos sites Web, et URL de la première page visitée après avoir quitté nos sites Web<br>* type de service demandé<br>* en-têtes de protocole de transfert hypertexte, bannières client d'application et serveur |
| Géolocalisation | * emplacement physique ou mouvements |
| Autre | * Données de charge des VÉ, marque, modèle et année du véhicule<br>* Informations que vous avez fournies volontairement dans le cadre d’une réponse à un commentaire ou d’une autre requête générale effectuée via nos sites Web<br>* Des déductions tirées de l’une des informations énumérées pour créer un profil sur un consommateur reflétant les préférences, les caractéristiques, les tendances psychologiques, les prédispositions, le comportement, les attitudes, l’intelligence, les capacités ou l’aptitude du consommateur |

1.3 OÙ NOUS COLLECTONS DES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES
----------------------------------------------------

Nous pouvons collecter des Informations personnelles directement auprès de vous par le biais de nos Services lorsque vous :

* Nous fournissez des informations personnelles en remplissant des formulaires Web sur nos sites Web ou en effectuant des transactions en magasin (marques mères, filiales et affiliées). Cela inclut les informations fournies lors de la création d’un compte en ligne, de l’achat de nos Services, de l’abonnement à nos bulletins d’information électroniques ou autres communications, de la demande d’informations auprès de nous, de l’envoi ou de la publication de documents (lorsque cela est autorisé) sur nos forums, ou de l’interaction avec l’assistance ou le service client, du signalement d’un problème avec nos Sites Web, applications mobiles ou Services, ou de toute autre communication avec nous.
* Nous contactez. Cela inclut tous les dossiers et copies de votre correspondance avec nous, comme avec nos bureaux ou notre service/assistance client ou l’envoi d’un chèque par courrier.
* Vous inscrivez à un événement ou nous informez de toute demande d’accessibilité ou autre demande d’hébergement.
* Répondez aux enquêtes que nous ou nos Prestataires de services pouvons vous demander de remplir à des fins de recherche.
* Effectuez des recherches sur les sites Web.
* Participez à des programmes de fidélité/récompenses.
* Postulez à un emploi.
* Utilisez des appareils et des réseaux pour accéder à nos Services, comme synchroniser votre VÉ avec nos Services.
* Utilisez certaines fonctionnalités sur nos sites Web et applications mobiles. Bien que les utilisateurs puissent accéder à des fonctionnalités limitées sans divulguer leurs Informations personnelles, comme la navigation dans les stations de recharge publiques sans compte, nous collectons des Informations personnelles lorsque les utilisateurs créent un compte. Les utilisateurs peuvent choisir d’utiliser uniquement leur adresse e-mail et leur mot de passe pour parcourir les chargeurs domestiques. Les utilisateurs peuvent également choisir de profiter des fonctionnalités améliorées en publiant, commentant, publiant ou partageant des informations personnelles supplémentaires avec la communauté. De manière générale, les utilisateurs choisissent la quantité d’informations qu’ils souhaitent afficher à leur sujet et peuvent se désinscrire à tout moment.

Nous pouvons également collecter des Informations personnelles auprès de parties non affiliées, notamment :

* Fournisseurs de données (par ex., sociétés qui fournissent des données démographiques et d’autres informations concernant les consommateurs)
* Sur les applications mobiles (marques mères, filiales et affiliées)
* Partenaires marketing conjoints
* Sociétés ou plateformes de publicité en ligne (par exemple, si vous liez ou connectez volontairement votre profil de réseau social à nos Services)
* Prestataires de services d’exécution et de livraison
* Sociétés de réseaux sociaux
* Autres prestataires de services
* En réponse aux opportunités d’emploi
* Actions du site Web/formulaire Web ou de l’application de l’utilisateur
* Fournisseurs de vérification d’emploi ou de vérification des antécédents
* Pour nous permettre, par le biais des paramètres de votre appareil ou de services tiers, de recevoir des données de géolocalisation afin d’afficher des informations locales (par exemple, une station de charge locale) sur nos applications mobiles.

1.4 LES INFORMATIONS COLLECTÉES PAR LE BIAIS DE TECHNOLOGIES AUTOMATISÉES
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

Lorsque vous naviguez et interagissez avec nos Services, nous pouvons également utiliser des technologies de collecte automatique de données pour collecter certaines informations à partir de votre appareil, navigateur ou d’autres activités réseau, comme décrit dans notre Politique relative aux cookies, disponible à l’adresse [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Visite du site Web et informations sur l’appareil. Nous recueillons des informations sur vos visites sur nos sites Web et l’utilisation de nos applications mobiles, y compris notamment les données de trafic, les données de géolocalisation, les journaux et autres données de communication et les ressources auxquelles vous accédez et que vous utilisez sur les sites Web. Nous collectons des informations sur votre ordinateur, votre appareil mobile et votre connexion Internet, y compris votre adresse IP, votre système d’exploitation, votre type de navigateur, vos habitudes de navigation (c.-à-d. ce sur quoi vous cliquez sur un site Web), l’URL du site Web le plus récent que vous avez visité avant de vous rendre sur nos sites Web, le temps que vous avez passé sur nos sites Web et les pages que vous avez consultées pendant que vous étiez sur nos sites Web. Nous pouvons obtenir une estimation approximative de votre localisation à partir de votre adresse IP lorsque vous visitez nos sites Web. Pour les utilisateurs de nos applications mobiles, nous pouvons également collecter et conserver un historique de vos informations de localisation précises à l’aide des technologies Wi-Fi ou Bluetooth, ainsi que des identifiants de votre appareil et des coordonnées GPS (par ex., latitude/longitude). Si vous souhaitez empêcher la collecte de vos informations de localisation, veuillez ajuster vos paramètres sur votre appareil mobile pour limiter l’accès de l’application mobile à vos informations de localisation.

Lorsque vous utilisez notre site Web, nous partageons les informations que nous recueillons auprès de vous, telles que votre adresse e-mail (sous forme hachée), votre adresse IP ou des informations sur votre navigateur ou votre système d'exploitation, avec nos partenaires d'identité/fournisseurs de services. Ces partenaires renvoient un code d'identification en ligne que nous pouvons stocker dans notre cookie propriétaire pour notre utilisation dans la publicité en ligne, intégrée à l'application et multicanal et il peut être partagé avec des sociétés de publicité pour permettre une publicité ciblée et basée sur les centres d'intérêt. Pour refuser cette utilisation, veuillez cliquer ici ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Suivi comportemental. Nous pouvons également utiliser ces technologies pour recueillir des informations sur vos activités en ligne au fil du temps et sur des sites Web tiers ou d’autres services en ligne, ou associer des Informations personnelles à d’autres informations recueillies de cette manière.

Analyse de la localisation : nos applications mobiles et nos sites Web de navigateur mobile comprennent des fonctionnalités (par ex., pour soumettre un avis du conducteur sur une installation de recharge) qui nous permettent d’identifier la localisation du conducteur et l’emplacement de l’installation de recharge où un utilisateur est actuellement situé. Nous collectons des informations telles que l’adresse IP, l’identifiant de l’appareil et la géolocalisation. Les utilisateurs de l’Application mobile peuvent choisir d’utiliser les Applications mobiles de manière anonyme ou de se connecter en tant qu’utilisateur identifié, auquel cas les données à caractère personnel fournies lors de l’inscription peuvent être utilisées.

Pour les utilisateurs des Applications mobiles, nous pouvons demander l’autorisation d’accéder à certaines informations à partir de votre appareil mobile, y compris votre liste de contacts, vos photos et vidéos, ainsi que votre microphone et votre appareil photo. Il est facultatif que vous nous donniez accès à ces informations. Cependant, certaines fonctionnalités des Applications mobiles peuvent ne pas fonctionner de manière optimale si vous décidez de ne pas nous donner votre autorisation.

Balises Web. Les pages de nos sites Web et de nos e-mails peuvent contenir de petits fichiers électroniques appelés balises Web (également appelés gifs transparents, balises pixel et gifs à pixel unique) qui nous permettent, par exemple, de compter les utilisateurs qui ont visité ces pages ou ouvert un e-mail et pour d’autres statistiques connexes du site Web (par exemple, enregistrer la popularité de certains contenus du site Web et vérifier l’intégrité du système et du serveur).

Suivi de pixels. En plus d’utiliser des cookies, les sites Web peuvent utiliser le « suivi de pixels ». Le suivi de pixels implique l’utilisation de balises pixel pour l’utilisateur et composés de quelques lignes de code informatique. Le suivi de pixels mesure l’efficacité des publicités et compile des statistiques d’utilisation agrégées et spécifiques. Nous pouvons accéder à ces balises pixel pour identifier l’activité et les intérêts qui peuvent nous permettre de mieux faire correspondre nos Produits, Services et offres à vos intérêts et besoins. Par exemple, si vous visitez nos sites Web à partir d’une publicité sur un autre site Web, la balise pixel permettra à l’annonceur de suivre que sa publicité vous a amené sur les sites Web. Si vous visitez nos sites Web et que nous vous renvoyons vers un autre site Web, nous pouvons également être en mesure de déterminer que vous avez été envoyé vers ou traité avec un site Web tiers.

GIF. Nous pouvons utiliser de minuscules images appelées GIF transparents pour suivre le comportement des utilisateurs, y compris des statistiques sur les personnes qui ouvrent nos e-mails.

Adresse IP. Nos serveurs (ou ceux de nos prestataires de services) enregistrent automatiquement certaines informations de fichier journal signalées par votre navigateur lorsque vous accédez aux sites Web. Ces journaux de serveur peuvent inclure des informations telles que les pages des sites Web que vous avez visitées, votre adresse de protocole Internet (« IP »), le type de navigateur et d’autres informations sur la manière dont vous interagissez avec les sites Web. Ces fichiers journaux sont généralement supprimés périodiquement.

Mesures et analyses tierces. Des mesures et analyses tierces, sur certaines pages ou fonctionnalités des Services pour nous aider à comprendre et analyser le trafic des visiteurs, mesurent l’efficacité promotionnelle et l’efficacité de nos fonctionnalités, offres et campagnes marketing. Nous utilisons également ces outils pour identifier les écueils, les lacunes et les domaines de nos opérations qui doivent être améliorés, et pour afficher la performance globale et le classement de notre présence en ligne. Ces outils peuvent stocker des cookies sur votre appareil à leur discrétion.

DÉCLARATION ET POLITIQUE EN MATIÈRE DE COOKIES

Les technologies que nous utilisons pour la collecte automatique de données comprennent également des cookies, comme décrit ci-dessous.

Cookies de navigateur

Les cookies de navigateur sont de petits fichiers placés sur le disque dur de votre ordinateur ou appareil mobile. Ils peuvent contenir certaines données, y compris notamment le nom du serveur qui les a placés, un identifiant sous la forme d’un numéro unique et une date d’expiration (certains cookies uniquement). Les cookies de navigateur sont gérés par le navigateur Web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) sur votre ordinateur ou appareil mobile. Différents types de cookies qui ont des finalités différentes sont utilisés sur nos sites Web.

Cookies essentiels

Les cookies essentiels sont essentiels pour vous permettre de naviguer sur nos sites Web et d’utiliser ses fonctions. Sans eux, les services tels que les paniers d’achats et la facturation électronique ne seraient pas en mesure de fonctionner.

Cookies de performance

Les cookies de performance collectent des informations sur l’utilisation de nos sites Web, telles que les pages consultées le plus souvent. Ces informations nous permettent d’optimiser nos sites Web et de simplifier la navigation. Les cookies de performance permettent également à nos sociétés affiliées et partenaires de savoir si vous avez accédé à l’une de nos pages Web depuis leur site et si votre visite a conduit à l’utilisation ou à l’achat d’un Produit ou Service depuis nos Sites Web, y compris les références pour le Produit ou Service acheté. Toutes les informations collectées par les cookies de performance sont agrégées et donc anonymes.

Cookies de fonctionnalité

Les cookies de fonctionnalité permettent à nos sites Web de mémoriser les choix que vous avez faits lorsque vous naviguez. Par exemple, nous pouvons stocker votre emplacement géographique dans un cookie afin que les sites Web correspondant à votre région soient affichés. Nous pouvons également nous souvenir de vos préférences, telles que la taille du texte, la police et d’autres aspects personnalisables des sites Web. Les cookies de fonctionnalité peuvent également être en mesure de suivre les produits ou les vidéos consultés pour éviter les répétitions. Les informations collectées par ces cookies ne peuvent pas être utilisées pour vous identifier et ne peuvent pas surveiller votre activité de navigation sur des sites Web qui ne nous appartiennent pas. Les cookies de fonctionnalité nous permettent d’afficher des publicités adaptées à vos besoins sur nos Sites Web, de comprendre quelles parties de notre contenu vous intéressent le plus et quelles catégories de Produits ou de Services vous demandez. Certains de nos prestataires de services sont autorisés à placer des cookies sur nos sites Web. Ces sociétés peuvent également vous offrir la possibilité d’empêcher l’utilisation de cookies à l’avenir.

À tout moment, vous pouvez empêcher ou refuser l’utilisation future de certains cookies en activant le paramètre approprié dans votre navigateur pour refuser d’accepter les cookies du navigateur. Cependant, si vous le faites, votre expérience sur nos sites Web peut être affectée. Par exemple, vous pourriez ne pas être en mesure d’accéder à certaines parties de nos sites Web. À moins que vous n’ayez ajusté les paramètres de votre navigateur afin qu’il refuse les cookies, notre système émettra des cookies lorsque vous dirigerez votre navigateur vers nos sites Web.

Cookies de stockage local

Certaines fonctionnalités de nos sites Web peuvent utiliser des objets stockés localement (pour collecter et stocker des informations sur vos préférences et votre navigation vers, depuis et sur nos sites Web). Les cookies de stockage local ne sont pas gérés par les mêmes paramètres de navigateur que ceux utilisés pour les cookies de navigateur.

Nous pouvons également combiner les Informations personnelles que nous collectons auprès de vous en dehors de nos Sites Web ou Services avec des Informations personnelles qui sont collectées par le biais de nos Sites Web ou Services ou par un autre moyen tel que décrit ci-dessus.

1.5 INFORMATIONS SUR LES APPAREILS, LE RÉSEAU, LA GÉOLOCALISATION ET LES VÉ
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Lorsque vous visitez ou quittez nos Sites Web ou Services en cliquant sur un lien hypertexte ou en affichant une extension sur un site Web tiers, nous recevons automatiquement l’URL du site depuis lequel vous êtes venu ou celui vers lequel vous êtes dirigé. De plus, les annonceurs reçoivent l’URL de la page sur laquelle vous vous trouvez lorsque vous cliquez sur une publicité qui peut apparaître sur nos Services. Nous recevons également l’adresse IP de votre ordinateur ou du serveur proxy que vous utilisez pour accéder à Internet, les détails de votre système d’exploitation informatique, votre type de navigateur Web, votre appareil mobile (y compris l’identifiant de votre appareil mobile fourni par votre système d’exploitation d’appareil mobile), votre système d’exploitation mobile (si vous accédez à nos sites Web ou services à l’aide d’un appareil mobile) et le nom de votre FAI ou de votre opérateur mobile.

1.6 ENQUÊTES
------------

Nous ou des parties non affiliées pouvons mener des enquêtes auprès des utilisateurs concernant nos Services. Certaines parties non affiliées peuvent cibler des publicités ou des promotions en fonction de vos réponses à l’enquête. Nous ou des parties non affiliées développons de nouveaux programmes ou produits en fonction des informations que vous partagez dans les enquêtes. Nous pouvons faire appel à des parties non affiliées pour vous fournir des incitations financières ou autres pour participer à des enquêtes. Si la remise de primes nécessite vos coordonnées, il peut vous être demandé de fournir des Informations personnelles à la partie non affiliée qui remplit l’offre incitative, qui ne sera utilisée que dans le but de fournir les incitations promises et de vérifier vos coordonnées. C’est à vous de décider si vous fournissez ces informations ou si vous souhaitez profiter d’une offre incitative. Votre consentement à l’utilisation de toute Information personnelle aux fins énoncées dans l’enquête sera explicitement demandé par la partie non affiliée qui la mène. Pour vous désinscrire de nos enquêtes, vous pouvez nous envoyer votre demande en utilisant les coordonnées ci-dessous.

2\. NATURE ET FINALITÉ DU TRAITEMENT DES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES
==================================================================

Nous utilisons les informations que nous recueillons à votre sujet ou que vous nous fournissez, y compris les Informations personnelles, pour une ou plusieurs des finalités suivantes :

* Pour vous présenter nos sites Web et applications mobiles et leur contenu.
* Pour vous fournir des informations et répondre à vos questions sur les Produits ou Services que vous nous demandez et des informations sur les nouveaux produits et services, les remises, les promotions particulières ou les événements à venir, et les fonctionnalités ou offres qui, selon nous, vous intéresseront ou concernant une promotion, un concours ou un tirage au sort auquel vous avez participé
* Pour traiter les informations de compte et les paiements de transaction, y compris notamment les frais de produit ou de service, ainsi que les paiements et remboursements pour tout produit ou service acheté (bien que nous ne recevions pas votre numéro de carte de crédit ou de débit complet).
* Pour traiter les remises, les offres, les récompenses de fidélité ou les demandes de rabais, les formulaires et les demandes et coordonner avec le fabricant, le détaillant ou le grossiste.
* Pour vous fournir des avis concernant votre compte, y compris des avis d’expiration et de renouvellement.
* Pour vous transmettre des informations ou des modifications apportées à nos Sites Web, à nos politiques, conditions ou à tout Produit ou Service que nous proposons ou fournissons, ou concernant votre compte.
* Pour traiter les Informations personnelles ou d’autres informations que vous nous soumettez.
* Pour vous permettre de participer à des fonctionnalités interactives sur nos sites Web.
* Pour améliorer nos Produits et Services et en développer de nouveaux, par exemple, en analysant les tendances des utilisateurs et en mesurant les données démographiques et les intérêts.
* Pour le fonctionnement interne du site Web, du service et du système, l’administration, la maintenance, les audits et examens internes, le diagnostic des problèmes techniques et le maintien de la sécurité.
* Pour enquêter sur toute violation de nos Conditions d’utilisation ou de la présente Politique de confidentialité.
* Pour suivre les problèmes et tendances potentiels liés à l’utilisation de nos Sites Web et Services par les Utilisateurs et personnaliser notre assistance pour mieux vous servir.
* Pour fournir des statistiques sur les niveaux d’utilisation des Sites Web et d’autres informations connexes à nos Prestataires de services.
* Pour vous informer des incidents de confidentialité des données ou vous fournir les informations légalement requises.
* Pour demander votre participation à des évaluations, des enquêtes, des groupes de discussion ou d’autres initiatives qui nous aident à recueillir des informations utilisées pour développer et améliorer nos Produits et Services.
* Pour remplir toute autre finalité pour laquelle vous fournissez des Informations personnelles.
* De toute autre manière que nous pourrions décrire et pour laquelle nous obtenons votre consentement lorsque vous fournissez les informations.

Nous utilisons des cookies, des GIF transparents, et des informations sur le fichier journal pour : (a) mémoriser les informations afin que vous n’ayez pas à les saisir à nouveau lors de votre visite ou la prochaine fois que vous visiterez les Sites Web ; (b) fournir des services personnalisés, un contenu et des informations personnalisés ; (c) surveiller l’efficacité de nos Services ; (d) surveiller les indicateurs agrégés tels que le nombre total de visiteurs, trafic, et les schémas démographiques ; (e) diagnostiquer ou résoudre les problèmes technologiques signalés par nos utilisateurs ou ingénieurs qui sont associés à certaines adresses IP ; ou, (f) vous aider à accéder efficacement à vos informations après vous être connecté.

Les données statistiques que nous collectons automatiquement nous aident à améliorer nos Sites Web et à fournir des Produits et Services meilleurs et plus personnalisés, y compris notamment en nous permettant : d’estimer la taille de notre audience/visiteur et les modèles d’utilisation, de stocker des informations sur vos préférences, de personnaliser et d’améliorer nos Sites Web, d’accélérer vos recherches ou de vous reconnaître lorsque vous revenez sur nos Sites Web.

Nous pouvons collecter et utiliser les informations de votre session de recharge de VÉ (par ex., temps de recharge, consommation d’énergie, propriété de la station et données, etc.) ainsi que la marque, le modèle et l’année de votre véhicule pour administrer votre compte, par exemple pour distinguer plusieurs véhicules ou utilisateurs partageant un seul compte, et à des fins analytiques.

Dans la mesure où vous ne consentez pas aux pratiques de traitement des informations énoncées dans les présentes, vous pouvez avoir le droit de vous désinscrire de ces pratiques. Toutes les demandes de désinscription doivent être adressées à [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Dans la mesure où les demandes de désinscription sont honorées, elles auront un effet sur le traitement futur et non sur le traitement qui a eu lieu sur la base d’un consentement préalable.

2.1 PRISE DE DÉCISION AUTOMATISÉE
---------------------------------

Nous pouvons utiliser vos Informations personnelles que vous nous fournissez et que nous obtenons d’autres sources pour mieux comprendre vos intérêts afin de pouvoir essayer de prédire quels autres Produits, Services et informations pourraient vous intéresser le plus. Cette pratique implique de prendre des décisions automatisées vous concernant en fonction de ces informations afin de nous permettre de mieux adapter nos interactions avec vous pour les rendre plus pertinentes et intéressantes. Vous pouvez vous y opposer à tout moment ou nous demander plus d’informations sur la méthodologie appliquée dans nos processus de prise de décision automatisée en nous contactant (voir la section 12 ci-dessous).

2.2 MESSAGES TEXTE
------------------

Nos Services peuvent inclure l’envoi de messages Short Message Service (« SMS »), qui peuvent envoyer jusqu’à deux messages par jour à votre appareil sans fil (sauf si vous communiquez davantage avec nous), mais la fréquence des messages peut varier.  Lorsque vous consentez expressément à recevoir des SMS de notre part et fournissez un numéro de téléphone portable, vous consentez expressément à recevoir des SMS d’information et transactionnels récurrents de notre part ou en notre nom au numéro que vous avez fourni. En consentant expressément à recevoir des SMS de notre part et en fournissant un numéro de téléphone portable, vous garantissez et déclarez que vous êtes le propriétaire du numéro de téléphone portable que vous nous fournissez. Nous pouvons utiliser vos informations pour vous contacter au sujet de votre utilisation, de vos achats, de vos retours (le cas échéant), des mises à jour du site Web, de la conduite d’enquêtes ou de communications d’information et de service, y compris des mises à jour de sécurité importantes. Après nous avoir envoyé le message SMS « STOP », nous vous enverrons un message SMS pour confirmer que vous avez été désabonné. Vous pouvez également nous envoyer votre demande par e-mail, y compris l’adresse e-mail et le numéro de téléphone que vous avez enregistrés auprès de nous, ou par tout moyen raisonnable. Après cela, vous ne recevrez plus de SMS de notre part. Si vous souhaitez vous inscrire à nouveau, il vous suffit de vous inscrire comme vous l’avez fait pour la première fois et nous commencerons à vous envoyer à nouveau des SMS. Pour obtenir de l’aide, veuillez répondre à un SMS avec AIDE. Des frais de messagerie et de données peuvent s’appliquer, en fonction de votre forfait téléphone portable. Les opérateurs ne sont pas responsables des messages retardés ou non livrés.

2.3 EXTENSIONS DE RÉSEAUX SOCIAUX
---------------------------------

Nous intégrons des interfaces ou extensions de programme d’application de réseaux sociaux (« Extensions ») à partir des réseaux sociaux, y compris Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest ou éventuellement d’autres sociétés, dans les Sites Web. Afin de vous inscrire en tant qu’utilisateur chez nous, vous pouvez avoir la possibilité de vous connecter à l’aide de votre compte Facebook ou d’un autre site de réseaux sociaux.

Par exemple, lorsque vous visitez nos sites Web, l’extension crée une connexion directe entre votre navigateur et le serveur Facebook. Cela permet à Facebook de recevoir des informations sur votre visite sur nos sites Web avec votre adresse IP. Si vous cliquez sur le bouton « J’aime » de Facebook alors que vous êtes connecté à votre compte Facebook, vous pouvez lier le contenu de nos sites Web à votre profil Facebook. Cela permet à Facebook d’attribuer votre visite sur nos sites Web à votre compte utilisateur. Veuillez noter qu’en tant que fournisseur des sites Web, nous ne recevons aucune notification concernant le contenu des données transmises ou leur utilisation par Facebook. Si vous ne souhaitez pas que Facebook attribue votre visite à nos sites Web à votre compte utilisateur Facebook, veuillez vous déconnecter de votre compte utilisateur Facebook.

Si vous vous connectez via une extension de réseau social, vous nous autorisez à accéder à certaines informations de compte à partir de ce site de réseaux sociaux, comme votre profil de réseau social public (conformément à vos paramètres de confidentialité sur le site de réseau social), votre adresse e-mail, vos intérêts, vos « j’aime », votre genre, votre anniversaire, votre historique de formation, vos relations, vos intérêts, votre ville actuelle, vos photos, votre description personnelle, votre liste d’amis, ainsi que des informations et des photos de vos amis sur les réseaux sociaux qui pourraient être des amis communs sur les réseaux sociaux avec d’autres utilisateurs. Les Extensions peuvent transférer des informations vous concernant vers la plateforme respective de l’Extension sans que vous n’agissiez. Ces informations peuvent inclure votre numéro d’identification d’utilisateur de plateforme, le site Web sur lequel vous vous trouvez, et plus encore. L’interaction avec une Extension transmettra des informations directement au réseau social de cette Extension et ces informations peuvent être visibles par d’autres personnes sur cette plateforme. Les Extensions sont contrôlés par la politique de confidentialité du site de réseaux sociaux concerné (disponible sur leur site Web), et non par notre Politique de confidentialité.

3\. COMMENT NOUS DIVULGUONS LES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES À DES PARTIES NON AFFILIÉES
=====================================================================================

3.1 TYPES DE PARTIES NON AFFILIÉES
----------------------------------

Nous pouvons divulguer vos Informations personnelles, en tout ou en partie, aux types de parties non affiliées suivants, et à une ou plusieurs des fins suivantes :

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Type de partie non affiliée | Finalité |
| Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données | stockage et transmission sécurisés de vos données |
| Prestataires de services de base de données et logiciels | gestion et suivi de vos données |
| Consultants juridiques et de conformité, tels que les conseillers juridiques externes, les auditeurs externes ou les consultants fiscaux | fourniture de services professionnels |
| Fournisseurs de gestion des identités | à des fins d’authentification |
| Fournisseurs de solutions de paiement | traitement sécurisé des paiements que vous nous fournissez |
| Fabricants, détaillants et grossistes | la soumission, le traitement et la gestion des rabais, des remises, des offres, des récompenses de fidélité, etc. |
| Fournisseurs d’exécution et d’expédition | l’exécution et la livraison des Produits, Services et marchandises |
| Fournisseurs d’enquêtes et de recherches | réalisation d’études en notre nom |
| Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de réseaux sociaux | diffusion des publicités ciblées |

Pour tout transfert d’Informations personnelles qui n’est pas raisonnablement nécessaire pour atteindre les finalités pour lesquels vous vous engagez avec PlugShare (par exemple à des fins de marketing ou d’enquête), vous avez le droit de vous désinscrire de ce traitement. Pour exercer votre droit de désinscription, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 PRESTATAIRES DE SERVICES, PARTENAIRES COMMERCIAUX ET SOUS-TRAITANTS ULTÉRIEURS
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

 Nous pouvons partager vos Informations personnelles avec des Prestataires de services qui fournissent des services en notre nom, comme indiqué ci-dessus. Ces Prestataires de services peuvent avoir accès à vos Informations personnelles afin de nous fournir ces services ou en notre nom. Si nous engageons des Prestataires de services pour l’une des raisons susmentionnées, l’utilisation de vos Informations personnelles sera liée par des obligations de confidentialité et leur utilisation des Informations personnelles sera limitée à la fourniture de leurs services. Nous pouvons stocker des Informations à caractère personnel dans des endroits hors de notre contrôle direct (par exemple, sur des serveurs ou des bases de données situés ou co-localisés avec des Prestataires de services hébergeant des données).  

3.3 PUBLICITÉ COMPORTEMENTALE TRANSVERSALE
------------------------------------------

Nous sommes tenus de divulguer si nous partageons des Informations personnelles avec un tiers engagé dans une publicité comportementale (ciblée) transversale. Au cours des douze (12) mois précédents, nous avons ou pouvons avoir divulgué les catégories suivantes d’Informations personnelles dans un contexte qui peut, en vertu de certaines lois (par ex., CPRA de Californie, RGPD ou RGPD britannique) être considéré comme une vente :

* Identifiants
* Activité sur Internet ou autre réseau similaire
* Données de géolocalisation

Vous avez la possibilité de vous désinscrire de ce partage en cliquant sur les invites de désinscription qui apparaîtront sur l’avis que vous recevez lors de votre première visite de nos applications mobiles ou de nos sites Web.

3.4 TRANSFERTS D’ENTREPRISE
---------------------------

Vous reconnaissez (et ne vous opposerez pas) à notre divulgation ou transfert de vos Informations personnelles, de vos Informations personnelles anonymisées et d’autres informations que vous nous fournissez, ainsi que les droits que vous avez accordés ou reconnus dans la présente Politique de confidentialité (collectivement, « Informations transférées ») à un acheteur ou acquéreur potentiel ou réel de notre société ou tout autre successeur dans le but d’envisager ou de réaliser une fusion, une cession, une restructuration, une réorganisation, une dissolution, un changement de contrôle ou le transfert de tout ou partie de nos actifs (chacun des éléments ci-dessus étant dénommé un « Transfert »), que ce soit dans le cadre d’une activité ou d’une faillite, d’une liquidation ou de toute autre procédure judiciaire, dans laquelle les Informations personnelles que nous détenons font partie des actifs transférés, et vous acceptez de ne pas vous opposer à une telle divulgation ou transfert. Nous ne pouvons faire aucune déclaration concernant l’utilisation ou le transfert des Informations transférées que nous pouvons avoir en cas de faillite, de réorganisation, d’insolvabilité, de redressement judiciaire ou de cession au profit des créanciers. En outre, sauf si la loi l’exige, nous ne sommes pas et ne serons pas responsables de toute violation de la sécurité par des parties non affiliées ou de toute action de parties non affiliées qui reçoivent l’une quelconque des Informations transférées qui nous est divulguée.

3.5 DIVULGATIONS REQUISES, PROTECTION DES DROITS ET SÉCURITÉ
------------------------------------------------------------

Sauf indication contraire dans la présente Politique de confidentialité, nous ne divulguerons pas vos Informations personnelles à une partie non affiliée, sauf si la loi, une ordonnance du tribunal ou une procédure judiciaire (par ex., assignation à comparaître) l’exige, y compris notamment afin de répondre à toute demande gouvernementale, réglementaire ou de licence, ou si nous pensons qu'une telle action est nécessaire pour : (a) se conformer à la loi, se conformer aux procédures judiciaires qui nous sont signifiées ou qui sont signifiées à nos sociétés affiliées, filiales, fournisseurs sous contrat, ou partenaires d’affinité, ou pour enquêter, prévenir, ou prendre des mesures concernant des activités illégales présumées ou réelles ; (b) faire appliquer nos Conditions ou notre accord client (y compris à des fins de facturation et de recouvrement) ; (c) prendre des précautions contre toute responsabilité ; (d) enquêter et nous défendre contre toute réclamation ou allégation de tiers ; (e) aider les organismes gouvernementaux chargés de l’application des lois ou répondre aux exigences de sécurité nationales ou autres ; (f) pour protéger la sécurité ou l’intégrité de nos Sites Web, de nos Services et des applications mobiles ; ou, (g) exercer ou protéger nos droits, nos biens, notre sécurité personnelle ou ceux de nos utilisateurs ou d’autres personnes. 

Nous tenterons de vous informer, lorsque cela est possible, de ces demandes, sauf si : (i) la notification est interdite par la procédure judiciaire elle-même, par une ordonnance du tribunal que nous recevons, ou par la loi applicable, ou (ii) nous pensons que la notification serait futile, inefficace, créerait un risque de blessure ou de dommage corporel ou autre pour une personne ou un groupe, ou créerait ou augmenterait un risque de fraude pour nous, nos utilisateurs, nos sites Web, nos services ou nos applications mobiles. Dans les cas où nous nous conformons à des demandes légales sans préavis pour ces raisons, nous tenterons d’informer cet utilisateur de la demande après le fait si nous déterminons de bonne foi que nous ne sommes plus légalement interdits de le faire et qu’aucun scénario de risque décrit dans ce paragraphe ne s’applique.

3.6 DIVULGATION D’INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES DÉSIDENTIFIÉES
----------------------------------------------------------

Nous pouvons partager des Informations personnelles désidentifiées (y compris notamment des données d’utilisation anonymes, des pages et URL de référence/sortie, une adresse IP, des types de plateforme, le nombre de clics, etc.) avec des parties non affiliées de quelque manière que ce soit et à quelque fin que ce soit, comme pour l’administration du système et pour surveiller l’utilisation des Sites Web, pour mesurer le nombre de visites sur nos Sites Web, le temps moyen passé, le nombre de pages consultées et pour surveiller diverses autres statistiques du Site Web afin d’améliorer le contenu.

4\.  DEMANDES « NE PAS SUIVRE »
===============================

Certains navigateurs Web (y compris Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox et Chrome) intègrent une fonctionnalité « Ne pas suivre » (Do Not Track, « DNT ») ou similaire qui signale aux sites Web qu’un utilisateur ne souhaite pas que son activité et son comportement en ligne soient suivis. Si un site Web qui répond à un signal DNT particulier reçoit le signal DNT, le navigateur peut empêcher ce site Web de collecter certaines informations sur l’utilisateur du navigateur. Tous les navigateurs n’offrent pas une option DNT et les signaux DNT ne sont pas encore uniformes. Pour cette raison, de nombreux opérateurs de sites Web, y compris PlugShare, ne répondent pas aux signaux DNT.

5\. COMMUNICATIONS PLUGSHARE, PRÉFÉRENCES ET DÉSINSCRIPTION
===========================================================

En nous fournissant votre adresse e-mail, vous consentez à ce que nous utilisions l’adresse e-mail pour vous envoyer des notifications liées au Service par e-mail, y compris notamment toute notification requise par la loi (par ex., notification d’incidents de confidentialité ou de sécurité des données), au lieu d’une communication par courrier postal. Vous acceptez également que nous puissions vous envoyer des notifications d’activité concernant nos Produits, Services, les Sites Web, les applications mobiles, vos Informations personnelles ou tout aspect de notre relation, à l’adresse e-mail que vous nous fournissez, conformément à tous les paramètres de confidentialité applicables. Nous pouvons utiliser votre adresse e-mail pour vous envoyer d’autres messages ou contenus, tels que, mais sans s’y limiter, des newsletters, des ajouts ou des modifications aux fonctionnalités du Service, ou des offres particulières. Si vous ne souhaitez pas recevoir ces e-mails, vous pouvez vous désabonner en cliquant sur Se désabonner, le cas échéant. Le fait de vous désinscrire peut vous empêcher de recevoir des e-mails concernant des mises à jour, des améliorations, des fonctionnalités particulières, des annonces ou des offres. Vous ne pouvez pas refuser les e-mails liés au Service. Si vous avez choisi de ne pas nous fournir d’e-mail ou d’autre adresse, il se peut que vous ne receviez pas nos e-mails liés au Service.

Sur la page des paramètres de votre compte utilisateur, vous pouvez accéder à certaines informations que vous nous avez fournies et, dans certains cas, les modifier ou les supprimer, telles que le nom et le mot de passe, l’adresse e-mail, l’adresse, les informations de profil utilisateur, etc. Les informations que vous pouvez consulter, mettre à jour et supprimer peuvent changer à mesure que les Produits, les Sites Web, les Services ou nos pratiques changent. Si vous avez des questions concernant la consultation ou la mise à jour des informations que nous avons sur vous, veuillez nous contacter. Cependant, lorsque vous mettez à jour des informations, nous pouvons conserver une copie des informations non révisées dans nos dossiers. Vous pouvez demander la suppression de votre compte en nous envoyant un e-mail. Il est de votre responsabilité de tenir à jour votre adresse e-mail avec nous. En fonction de l’État ou du pays dans lequel vous résidez, vous pouvez avoir des droits supplémentaires. Veuillez consulter ci-dessous pour plus d’informations.

6\. DÉVELOPPEURS UTILISANT DES SERVICES DE PLATEFORME PLUGSHARE
===============================================================

Nous collaborons avec des tiers et leur permettons d’utiliser la plateforme de développement de PlugShare pour offrir des services et des fonctionnalités en conjonction avec PlugShare. Ces développeurs tiers ont soit négocié un accord pour utiliser la technologie de plateforme PlugShare, soit accepté nos Interfaces de programmation d’application (Application Programming Interfaces, « API ») et Extensions en libre-service afin de créer des applications de plateforme logicielle (les « Applications de plateforme »). Les accords négociés et nos conditions d’utilisation de l’API et des Extensions contiennent des restrictions sur la manière dont les tiers peuvent accéder, stocker et utiliser les Informations personnelles que vous fournissez à PlugShare. Si vous choisissez d’utiliser une Application de plateforme, il vous sera demandé de confirmer l’acceptation de la politique de confidentialité et de l’accord utilisateur du développeur tiers. Pour révoquer l’autorisation accordée à une Application de plateforme, veuillez consulter vos paramètres. Notez toutefois que même si vous révoquez l’autorisation accordée à une Application de plateforme, vos connexions peuvent toujours utiliser l’Application de plateforme, de sorte que l’Application de plateforme peut toujours avoir accès à certaines informations vous concernant, tout comme vos connexions.

7\. CONSERVATION DES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES
==============================================

La période pendant laquelle nous conservons vos Informations personnelles dépend des finalités pour lesquelles nous les utilisons. Nous conserverons vos Informations personnelles aussi longtemps que votre compte sera actif, ou tant que vous êtes titulaire d’un compte enregistré ou utilisateur de nos Services, ou aussi longtemps que nous avons une autre finalité commerciale pour le faire (comme, notamment, à des fins professionnelles, fiscales ou juridiques) et, par la suite, pour une durée n’excédant pas celle requise ou autorisée par la loi, ou notre politique de conservation des dossiers, raisonnablement nécessaire à des fins de rapport interne et de rapprochement, ou pour vous fournir des commentaires ou des informations que vous pourriez demander. Cette période de conservation est soumise à notre examen et à notre modification. Nous pouvons conserver les Informations personnelles désidentifiées aussi longtemps que nous le jugeons approprié.

Après la résiliation ou la désactivation de votre compte utilisateur, nous pouvons conserver vos informations de profil et toutes les informations publiées sur les espaces publics des sites Web. Après la résiliation ou la désactivation de votre compte utilisateur, nous pouvons conserver vos Informations personnelles et d’autres données, mais nous les conserverons de manière confidentielle conformément aux Conditions, à la présente Politique de confidentialité et à la loi applicable. Nous avons le droit de supprimer toutes vos Informations personnelles et autres données après la résiliation de votre compte utilisateur sans préavis.

8\. PAS DE COLLECTE INTENTIONNELLE DE DONNÉES SUR LES ENFANTS
=============================================================

Nous ne collectons, ne sollicitons ou ne conservons pas sciemment les Informations personnelles de toute personne âgée de moins de 18 ans et nous n’autorisons pas sciemment ces personnes à s’inscrire à nos Services ou à les utiliser. Si vous avez moins de 18 ans, veuillez ne pas nous envoyer d’Informations personnelles. Si nous apprenons que nous avons recueilli des Informations personnelles auprès d’un enfant de moins de 18 ans sans vérification du consentement parental, nous déploierons des efforts commercialement raisonnables pour supprimer ces informations de notre base de données.

9\. OÙ LES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES SONT TRAITÉES ET STOCKÉES ET DROIT APPLICABLE
==================================================================================

Nous avons notre siège social aux États-Unis. Les Informations personnelles que nous ou nos Prestataires de services collectons peuvent être stockées et traitées sur des serveurs à l’intérieur ou à l’extérieur des États-Unis et partout où nous et nos Prestataires de services avons des installations dans le monde, et certaines informations peuvent être accessibles par des personnes ou des sociétés en dehors des États-Unis qui nous fournissent des services. Vous consentez à la transmission ou au transfert de vos Informations personnelles par nos Prestataires de services vers, ou à leur accès dans, des pays qui peuvent ne pas fournir des niveaux de protection des données équivalents à ceux de votre pays d’origine. Nous prendrons des mesures raisonnables pour nous assurer que vos Informations personnelles bénéficient d’un niveau de protection adéquat dans les pays dans lesquels nous les traitons.

Les lois américaines s’appliquent dans la mesure où vous résidez aux États-Unis. Dans le cas contraire, la présente Politique de confidentialité et toutes les autres questions seront interprétées conformément aux lois provinciales/étatiques et fédérales du pays dans lequel vous résidez. Les pays en dehors de votre résidence peuvent avoir des lois sur la protection de la vie privée différentes de celles de votre pays, y compris le droit des forces de l’ordre et des autorités gouvernementales d’accéder aux Informations personnelles.  Dans la mesure où nous traitons des données en dehors de votre pays, nous effectuons une analyse d’impact relative à la protection des données afin de déterminer que nos Prestataires de services peuvent offrir sensiblement le même niveau de protection que celui requis dans votre pays et conclure des contrats pour renforcer davantage les obligations de traitement approprié de vos Informations personnelles.

10\. SÉCURITÉ
=============

Nous avons mis en place des mesures de sécurité techniques et organisationnelles conçues pour protéger vos Informations personnelles contre la perte accidentelle et contre l’accès, l’utilisation, la destruction, la modification et la divulgation non autorisés. Cependant, veuillez garder à l’esprit qu’Internet n’est pas un environnement 100 % sécurisé. Il est de votre responsabilité de protéger la sécurité de vos informations de connexion, de faire preuve de prudence lors de la transmission de toute information personnelle par e-mail, messagerie instantanée et autres moyens de communication similaires, et de maintenir de bonnes pratiques de sécurité Internet. Nous ne vous enverrons jamais d’e-mail pour vous demander votre mot de passe ou d’autres informations de connexion au compte. Si vous recevez un tel e-mail, veuillez nous l’envoyer afin que nous puissions enquêter.

11\. DROITS SUPPLÉMENTAIRES DES PERSONNES CONCERNÉES POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINS PAYS DÉCRITS DANS LES DÉCLARATIONS DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ SUPPLÉMENTAIRES
=========================================================================================================================================================

Ce qui suit explique chaque droit de la personne concernée décrit dans les Déclarations de confidentialité supplémentaires :

* Droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de protection des données : Vous avez le droit de recevoir certaines informations requises par la loi au moment de la collecte ou avant, ou en réponse à votre demande.
* Droit à la suppression : Vous pouvez nous demander de supprimer toutes les Informations personnelles vous concernant que nous avons collectées auprès de vous, sous réserve de certaines exceptions.
* Droit à la rectification : Vous pouvez nous demander de rectifier toute Information personnelle inexacte que nous conservons à votre sujet.
* Droit de savoir : Vous pouvez nous demander de vous fournir des informations spécifiques sur la manière dont nous avons traité vos Informations personnelles, y compris de vous fournir une copie des Informations personnelles spécifiques que nous avons collectées à votre sujet dans un format portable.
* Droit à la non-discrimination : Vous avez le droit de ne pas faire l’objet de discrimination pour avoir exercé vos droits en tant que personne concernée. Cela signifie ne pas vous refuser des biens ou des services, vous facturer des prix ou des tarifs différents, ou fournir un niveau de qualité différent pour les produits ou services en raison de l’exercice de vos droits de personne concernée.
* Droits de désinscription : Vous pouvez demander à vous désinscrire de la Vente et du Partage de vos Informations personnelles, de la publicité comportementale ou ciblée transversale, de la prise de décision automatisée ou du profilage, dans la mesure où ces activités sont définies et restreintes en vertu des lois applicables.
* Droit de limitation ou d’opposition au traitement : Vous pouvez nous demander de supprimer ou de cesser le traitement de certaines de vos Informations personnelles, mais nous pouvons toujours stocker vos Informations personnelles.  
* Droit de limiter l’utilisation de vos informations personnelles sensibles : Vous pouvez demander à limiter l’utilisation de vos Informations personnelles sensibles aux seules fins autorisées par les lois applicables.
* Droit d'introduire une réclamation : Vous avez le droit d'introduire une réclamation auprès de votre autorité locale de protection des données si vous considérez que le traitement des Informations personnelles vous concernant enfreint vos droits.
* Droit de retrait du consentement : Dans la mesure où notre traitement de vos Informations personnelles est uniquement basé sur votre consentement, vous pouvez retirer ce consentement à tout moment.

12\. COORDONNÉES
================

PlugShare a désigné un délégué à la protection des données qui supervisera la conformité aux exigences de protection des données. Le délégué à la protection des données de PlugShare peut être contacté à l’adresse ci-dessous concernant tout problème de politique de confidentialité.

Si vous avez des questions ou des commentaires concernant la présente Politique de confidentialité ou nos pratiques de confidentialité, veuillez nous contacter à l’adresse suivante : PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, Californie 90245 États-Unis ; À l’attention de : Délégué à la protection des données ; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

DÉCLARATION DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ POUR LES RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINS ÉTATS DES ÉTATS-UNIS
==================================================================================

Si vous résidez en Californie, en Virginie, dans le Colorado, dans l’Utah ou dans le Connecticut (parfois appelé « Consommateur »), les lois de l’État vous accordent des droits supplémentaires concernant notre utilisation de vos Informations personnelles.

LOI CALIFORNIENNE « SHINE THE LIGHT »
-------------------------------------

La section 1798.83 du Code civil de Californie, connue sous le nom de loi « Shine The Light », permet à tous les utilisateurs résidant en Californie de demander et d’obtenir de notre part une liste des Informations personnelles (le cas échéant) que nous avons divulguées à des tiers à des fins de marketing direct au cours de l’année civile précédente, ainsi que les noms et adresses de ces tiers. Les demandes ne peuvent être faites qu’une fois par an et sont gratuites.

LOI CALIFORNIENNE SUR LA PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE EN LIGNE (CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT, « CALOPPA » ; CALIF. BUS. & PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, DISPONIBLE [ICI](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D-X))
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA s’applique uniquement aux sociétés qui collectent des Informations personnelles des résidents de Californie.

1. COMMENT NOUS RÉAGISSONS AUX SIGNAUX « NE PAS SUIVRE ».

Certains navigateurs web transmettent des signaux « ne pas suivre » (Do Not Track, DNT/Global Privacy Control, GPC) aux sites web et à d’autres services en ligne avec lesquels votre navigateur web communique. Actuellement, il n’existe aucune norme régissant ce que les sites web doivent faire, le cas échéant, lorsqu’ils reçoivent ces signaux. Toutefois, nous disposons actuellement de mesures pour réagir en réponse à ces signaux.

2. SUIVI COMPORTEMENTAL TIERS

Nous pouvons également utiliser ces technologies pour recueillir des informations sur vos activités en ligne au fil du temps et sur des sites Web tiers ou d’autres services en ligne, ou associer des Informations personnelles à d’autres informations recueillies de cette manière. Nous pouvons utiliser les Informations personnelles pour suivre les clics et les habitudes de navigation des utilisateurs.

LA LOI CALIFORNIENNE SUR LA PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE DES CONSOMMATEURS DE 2018 (CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT, « CCPA », DISPONIBLE [ICI](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) ET LA LOI LUI AYANT SUCCÉDÉ, LA LOI CALIFORNIENNE SUR LES DROITS À LA VIE PRIVÉE DE 2020 (CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT, « CPRA », DISPONIBLE [ICI](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf-qUfM)). 
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Le tableau ci-dessous détaille la manière dont nous divulguons les informations personnelles que nous avons recueillies à votre sujet :

| Catégorie | Catégories de tiers non affiliés auxquels nous divulguons des informations personnelles | Catégories de tiers non affiliés à qui nous vendons ou partageons des informations personnelles |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiants | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Fournisseurs de gestion des identités<br><br>Fournisseurs de solutions de paiement<br><br>Fournisseurs d’enquêtes et de recherches<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de réseaux sociaux | S.O. |
| Données démographiques | Fournisseurs d’enquêtes et de recherches | S.O. |
| Informations commerciales | S.O. | S.O. |
| Activité sur Internet ou autre réseau électronique, informations sur l’appareil | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de base de données et logiciels<br><br>Fournisseurs de gestion des identités<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de réseaux sociaux | S.O. |
| Géolocalisation | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de base de données et logiciels<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de réseaux sociaux | S.O. |
| Autre | Fournisseurs de stockage ou d’hébergement de données<br><br>Prestataires de services de base de données et logiciels<br><br>Fournisseurs d’enquêtes et de recherches<br><br>Partenaires publicitaires, y compris les fournisseurs de réseaux sociaux | Fabricants, détaillants et grossistes |

Vous pouvez nous contacter pour exercer les droits suivants en vertu de la CCPA et de la CPRA (veuillez consulter la section 11 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale pour la description de ces droits) :

1. Droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de protection des données.
2. Droit de savoir ce qui suit :

* Les catégories d’Informations personnelles que nous avons recueillies à votre sujet.
* Les catégories de sources des Informations personnelles que nous avons recueillies à votre sujet.
* Notre finalité professionnelle ou commerciale de la collecte de ces Informations personnelles.
* Les catégories de tiers avec lesquels nous partageons ces Informations personnelles.
* Les informations personnelles spécifiques que nous avons recueillies à votre sujet (également appelées demande de portabilité des données) et vous en fournir une copie au format électronique ou papier.
* Si nous avons divulgué vos Informations personnelles à des fins professionnelles, une liste indiquant les divulgations à des fins professionnelles, identifiant les catégories d’Informations personnelles que chaque catégorie de destinataire a obtenues.

3. Droit à la suppression.
4. Droit à la rectification.
5. Droit de refuser la publicité comportementale transversale, la vente ou le partage d’Informations personnelles, le traitement d’Informations personnelles pour le profilage et la prise de décision automatisée.
6. Droit de limiter l’utilisation de vos informations personnelles sensibles. Veuillez noter que nous n’utilisons pas d’informations personnelles sensibles à des fins qui ne sont pas autorisées par la CCPA et la CPRA.

LOI SUR LA PROTECTION DES DONNÉES DES CONSOMMATEURS DE VIRGINIE (VIRGINIA CONSUMER DATA PROTECTION ACT \[VCDPA\]), LOI SUR LA PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE DU COLORADO (COLORADO PRIVACY ACT \[CPA\])[\[1\]](#ftnt1), LOI SUR LA PROTECTION DE LA VIE PRIVÉE DES CONSOMMATEURS DE L'UTAH (UTAH CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT \[UCPA\])[\[2\]](#ftnt2) ET LOI SUR LA CONFIDENTIALITÉ DES DONNÉES DU CONNECTICUT (CONNECTICUT DATA PRIVACY ACT \[CDPA\])[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Vous pouvez nous contacter pour exercer les droits suivants en vertu de ces lois spécifiques à l’État :

1. Droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de protection des données.
2. Droit de savoir.
3. Droit à la suppression.
4. Droit à la rectification.
5. Droit de refuser la publicité ciblée ou la vente des Informations personnelles.
6. Droit de refuser le profilage (traitement automatisé des Informations personnelles à des fins d’analyses ou de prévisions des caractéristiques d’une personne ou de son comportement futur, donnant lieu à des décisions qui affectent ses droits substantiels).  
7. Les consommateurs de Virginie, du Colorado et du Connecticut ont également le droit de faire appel de nos décisions sur leurs demandes de personnes concernées en nous contactant par la même méthode pour soumettre une demande. Veuillez joindre une copie de notre décision sur votre demande de personne concernée ou y faire référence spécifiquement, afin que nous puissions traiter votre appel de manière adéquate. Nous répondrons à votre appel conformément à la loi applicable.

NEVADA
------

Comme décrit ci-dessus, nous pouvons vendre vos identifiants ou d’autres informations d’identification que nous collectons à partir de nos Sites Web et Services en ligne à des parties non affiliées à des fins de suivi du comportement intertextuel au sens de la loi du Nevada. Vous avez le droit de refuser de vendre ou de concéder sous licence ces catégories d’informations personnelles vous concernant à des parties non affiliées.

EXERCICE DES DROITS
-------------------

Pour exercer les droits d’accès, de correction, de portabilité des données et de suppression décrits ci-dessus, veuillez nous soumettre une demande par le biais de notre formulaire en ligne disponible [ici](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Seulement vous ou une personne que vous autorisez à agir en votre nom pouvez faire une demande liée à vos Informations personnelles. Vous pouvez également faire une demande au nom de votre enfant mineur. Si nous recevons une demande d’une personne d’exercer vos droits en votre nom, nous demanderons une copie du document signé donnant l’autorisation de soumettre une telle demande en votre nom et nous vous contacterons directement pour confirmer cette autorisation. Vous ne pouvez faire une demande d’accès ou de portabilité des données que deux fois au cours d’une période de 12 mois. La demande du Consommateur vérifiable doit :

* Fournir suffisamment d’informations qui nous permettent de vérifier raisonnablement que vous êtes la personne au sujet de laquelle nous avons recueilli des Informations personnelles ou qu’un représentant autorisé a fait la demande.
* Décrire votre demande avec suffisamment de détails pour nous permettre de la comprendre, de l’évaluer et d’y répondre correctement.

Nous ne pouvons pas répondre à votre demande ou vous fournir des Informations personnelles si nous ne pouvons pas vérifier votre identité ou votre autorité pour faire la demande et confirmer que les Informations personnelles vous concernent. Faire une demande ne vous oblige pas à créer un compte chez nous. Nous n’utiliserons les Informations personnelles fournies dans une demande que pour vérifier l’identité ou l’autorité du demandeur à faire la demande.

Pour exercer les droits de refuser la publicité comportementale ou ciblée transversale, ou le partage d’Informations personnelles tel que décrit ci-dessus, vous devrez vous désinscrire en fonction de la plateforme sur laquelle vous êtes.  Veuillez noter que votre demande de désinscription est spécifique à l’appareil ou à la plateforme à partir desquels vous soumettez cette demande. Vous devrez donc soumettre plusieurs demandes si vous souhaitez refuser ces activités de traitement spécifiques pour plusieurs appareils et plateformes. Veuillez cliquer :

* ici pour vous désinscrire de Plugshare.com (plateforme web)
* ici pour vous désinscrire de l’application Plugshare pour iOS
* ici pour vous désinscrire de l’application Plugshare pour Android

### Processus de vérification

Dès réception d’une demande d’accès aux données, de leur correction, de leur portabilité ou de leur suppression de votre part, nous vous enverrons un e-mail dans les 10 jours ouvrables à l’adresse e-mail que nous avons pour vous. L’e-mail vous demandera de répondre pour vérifier que vous êtes le Consommateur qui fait la demande. Dès réception de votre vérification, nous ferons correspondre vos informations à celles qui figurent dans notre dossier. Après vérification de votre identité, nous procéderons au traitement de votre demande et y répondrons dans les 45 jours civils, sauf si (a) nous ne sommes pas en mesure de vérifier votre demande, (b) si nous ne sommes pas en mesure de vous faire correspondre avec les informations de notre base de données, ou (c) si une exception en vertu de la loi existe nous exonérant de nous conformer à votre demande. Si nous avons besoin de plus de temps (jusqu’à quarante-cinq (45) jours civils supplémentaires), nous vous informerons par écrit de la raison et de la période de prolongation.

Si nous ne sommes pas en mesure de donner suite à votre demande, la réponse que nous fournirons expliquera les raisons de cette fin de non-recevoir. Pour les demandes de portabilité des données, nous sélectionnerons un format pour fournir vos Informations personnelles qui est facilement utilisable et devrait vous permettre de transmettre les informations d’une entité à une autre sans entrave.

Nous ne facturons pas de frais pour traiter ou répondre à votre demande de Consommateur vérifiable, sauf si elle est excessive, répétitive ou manifestement infondée. Si nous déterminons que la demande nécessite des frais, nous vous indiquerons pourquoi nous avons pris cette décision et vous fournirons une estimation des coûts avant de répondre à votre demande.

* * *

DÉCLARATION DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ POUR CERTAINS PAYS AUTRES QUE LES ÉTATS-UNIS
===========================================================================

INFORMATIONS GÉNÉRALES
----------------------

1. ### VOTRE CONSENTEMENT SPÉCIFIQUE AU TRAITEMENT DE CATÉGORIES « SENSIBLES » OU « PARTICULIÈRES » D’INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES

En vertu des lois sur la protection de la vie privée de certains pays, certains types d’informations personnelles sont considérés comme des catégories d’informations « sensibles » ou « particulières ». Nous traitons rarement des catégories de données sensibles ou particulières, sauf si cela est dans votre intérêt vital ou celui d’une autre personne. Dans toutes les autres circonstances, vous consentez spécifiquement à la collecte, au traitement et à la conservation de catégories sensibles ou particulières d’Informations personnelles, comme décrit dans la section 1.2 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale, et vous consentez autrement au traitement des Informations personnelles conformément à la présente Déclaration de confidentialité.  

2. ### NOS BASES JURIDIQUES POUR LE TRAITEMENT DES INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES

Nos bases juridiques pour la collecte et l’utilisation des Informations personnelles décrites ci-dessus dépendront des Informations personnelles concernées et du contexte spécifique dans lequel nous les collectons. De manière générale, nous ne collecterons et traiterons vos Informations personnelles que lorsque nous aurons besoin des Informations personnelles pour vous fournir les Services pour lesquels vous avez conclu un contrat avec nous, ou lorsque le traitement est dans notre intérêt légitime et non outrepassé par vos intérêts en matière de protection des données ou vos droits et libertés fondamentaux, nous nous fonderons sur votre consentement lorsque nous sommes légalement tenus de le faire. Dans certains cas, nous pouvons également avoir l’obligation légale de recueillir des Informations personnelles auprès de vous ou avoir besoin des Informations personnelles pour protéger vos intérêts vitaux ou ceux d’une autre personne.

BASE D’INTÉRÊT LÉGITIME POUR LA COLLECTE D’INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES : La collecte et le traitement de vos Informations personnelles peuvent être nécessaires aux fins de nos intérêts légitimes. Ces objectifs d’intérêt légitime peuvent inclure :

* la prévention de la fraude
* assurer la sécurité du réseau et des informations
* indiquer d’éventuels actes criminels ou menaces pour la sécurité publique, y compris l’amélioration de la protection de notre communauté contre le spam, le harcèlement, la violation de la propriété intellectuelle, la criminalité et les risques de sécurité de toutes sortes, et l’application de réclamations légales, y compris l’enquête sur les violations potentielles de nos Conditions d’utilisation
* lorsque nous respectons les obligations légales
* le traitement des données des employés ou des visiteurs, des membres, des participants ou des inscrits
* l’exécution de la fonction ou du service que vous nous avez demandé
* vous fournir nos Services et leur fonctionnalité lorsque ce traitement est nécessaire aux fins des intérêts légitimes que nous ou nos prestataires de services poursuivons en lien avec les Services
* le marketing direct
* la relation pertinente et appropriée que nous entretenons avec vous
* l’analyse, par ex., évaluer le nombre de visiteurs, les pages consultées, l’utilisation des Sites Web, etc., afin de comprendre comment nos Sites Web, Produits et Services sont utilisés, d’optimiser les Sites Web ou les communications futures, et de développer de nouveaux services et fonctionnalités du Site Web
* la mise à jour de vos informations et préférences
* proposer et améliorer nos Sites Web, Produits et Services
* l’application des réclamations légales, y compris l’enquête sur les violations potentielles de nos Conditions

Outre les informations fournies ci-dessus, les sections suivantes s’appliquent uniquement aux résidents ou citoyens du pays ou de la région discutés. Aux fins des sections suivantes, sauf mention contraire, la définition de « Informations personnelles » telle qu’utilisée ci-dessus aura la définition d’informations personnelles, de données à caractère personnel ou d’un terme similaire applicable en vertu des lois sur la confidentialité des données de ce pays ou de cette région. En cas de conflit et dans la mesure d’un conflit entre les sections ci-dessous et les sections ci-dessus, les sections ci-dessous prévaudront.

RGPD – DÉCLARATION DE CONFIDENTIALITÉ AUX RÉSIDENTS DE LA ZONE ÉCONOMIQUE EUROPÉENNE (EEA), DU ROYAUME UNI ET DE LA SUISSE
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### APERÇU

Les dispositions suivantes s’appliquent uniquement si vous résidez dans l’EEE, au Royaume-Uni ou en Suisse (désignée dans la présente section par commodité comme la « Région UE »).

Pour ces résidents, tout traitement de vos Informations personnelles est effectué conformément aux droits et réglementations en matière de confidentialité, en particulier (UE) 2016/679 du Parlement européen et du Conseil du 27 avril 2016, connu sous le nom de Règlement général sur la protection des données ou Règlement général sur la protection des données du Royaume-Uni pour les résidents du Royaume-Uni (collectivement, le « RGPD »), et notre traitement aura lieu conformément au RGPD. Aux fins du RGPD, nous serons le « responsable du traitement » des Informations personnelles (désignées et définies dans le RGPD (disponible [ici](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) comme les « données à caractère personnel ») que nous collectons, à moins que nous ne recueillions ces informations pour le compte d’un « responsable du traitement », auquel cas nous serons un « sous-traitant ». La présente Politique de confidentialité ne s’applique pas aux sites Web, applications ou services qui n’affichent pas ou ne sont pas liés à la présente Politique de confidentialité ou qui affichent ou sont liés à une autre politique de confidentialité. Pour les résidents et citoyens de la Région UE uniquement, dans la mesure où une définition de la présente Politique de confidentialité est en conflit avec une définition en vertu du RGPD, la définition du RGPD prévaudra.

Nous fournissons une protection adéquate pour le transfert d’Informations personnelles vers des pays en dehors de la Région UE par l’une ou plusieurs des méthodes suivantes : (a) une série d’accords intersociétés basés sur ou incorporant les Clauses contractuelles types, (b) nous pouvons nous appuyer sur les décisions d’adéquation de la Commission européenne concernant certains pays, le cas échéant, (c) nous pouvons obtenir votre consentement pour ces transferts de données de la Région UE vers les États-Unis vers d’autres pays, (d) nous pouvons adopter des règles d’entreprise contraignantes, ou (e) dans la mesure applicable, nous pouvons nous fonder sur des dérogations telles qu’énoncées à l’article 49 du RGPD pour le transfert et le transfert ultérieur des Informations personnelles recueillies auprès de personnes physiques dans la Région UE vers les États-Unis et d’autres pays que la Région UE considère comme ne fournissant pas une protection adéquate des données. En ce qui concerne la méthode (e), nous pouvons transférer des Informations personnelles à un tiers pour exécuter un contrat avec vous, avec votre consentement explicite ou d’une manière qui ne l’emporte pas sur vos droits et libertés. Si ces Informations personnelles ne sont pas traitées et transférées, nous ne serons pas en mesure d’exécuter le contrat avec vous ou vous n’aurez pas accès à tout ou partie des avantages et fonctionnalités associés à votre transaction.

Nous pouvons également avoir besoin de transférer vos informations à d’autres sociétés du groupe ou prestataires de services dans des pays en dehors de la Région UE. Cela peut se produire si nos serveurs ou fournisseurs et prestataires de services sont basés en dehors de la Région UE, ou si vous utilisez nos Produits ou Services lorsque vous visitez des pays en dehors de ces zones.

Nos bases juridiques pour la collecte de vos informations personnelles sont discutées .

2. ### VOS DROITS EN MATIÈRE DE DONNÉES EN VERTU DU RGPD.

Si vous êtes soumis au RGPD, vos droits comprennent le droit de :

* Droit de savoir.
* Droit à la rectification.
* Droit à la suppression.
* Droit de limitation ou d’opposition au traitement. Vous avez le droit de vous opposer à vos Informations personnelles utilisées de la manière suivante : (a) traitement basé sur des intérêts légitimes ou l’exécution d’une tâche dans l’intérêt public/exercice de l’autorité officielle (y compris le profilage) ; (b) marketing direct (y compris le profilage) ; et (c) traitement à des fins de recherche scientifique/historique et de statistiques. Voir ci-dessous pour plus d’informations.
* Droit de désinscription. Vous avez le droit de ne pas faire l’objet d’une décision basée uniquement sur un traitement automatisé, y compris le profilage, qui produit des effets juridiques vous concernant ou qui vous affecte de manière significative de manière similaire, sauf les exceptions applicables en vertu des lois pertinentes sur la protection des données.
* Droit d'introduire une réclamation. Si vous résidez dans l’EEE, une liste des autorités nationales chargées de la protection des données est disponible [ici](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Si vous résidez au Royaume-Uni, vous pouvez contacter le Bureau du commissaire à l’information (Commissioner’s Office) [ici.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Droit de retrait du consentement.

DÉCLARATIONS AUX RÉSIDENTS DE CERTAINS AUTRES PAYS (HORS ÉTATS-UNIS)
--------------------------------------------------------------------

Les disposition de la section suivante viennent s’ajouter aux informations abordées dans notre Politique de confidentialité principale.

Nous respecterons les droits suivants des personnes concernées pour tous les résidents en dehors des États-Unis :

* Droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de protection des données :

* Notre identité et nos coordonnées,
* La finalité spécifique de notre traitement de vos Informations personnelles,
* La forme et la durée de notre traitement de vos Informations personnelles,
* Les informations sur notre partage et la finalité de notre partage de vos Informations personnelles,
* Les responsabilités de tout tiers traitant vos Informations personnelles, et
* Les informations concernant les entités juridiques publiques et privées avec lesquelles nous avons partagé vos Informations personnelles.  

* Droit de savoir :

* Décisions prises exclusivement sur la base du traitement automatisé des Informations personnelles.
* Accéder aux informations sur les Informations personnelles que nous collectons.  

* Droit à la rectification.
* Droit de limitation ou d’opposition au traitement.  
* Droit de retrait du consentement.

Toute traduction de la présente Politique de confidentialité dans une langue autre que l’anglais est fournie uniquement à des fins d’information. En cas de divergences, la seule version juridiquement valide et contraignante sera la version anglaise du présent document.

1. ### DÉCLARATIONS AUX RÉSIDENTS D’ARGENTINE

Les mesures de sécurité techniques et organisationnelles mises en œuvre par PlugShare soutiendraient également les règles de la Loi sur la protection des données à caractère personnel (Personal Data Protection Act, PDPA) 25.326 de l’Argentine, telles que l’interdiction de toute utilisation secondaire des données à caractère personnel d’une personne concernée et l’interdiction du transfert de données à caractère personnel vers des pays qui n’offrent pas un niveau de protection adéquat. PlugShare utilise un accord de transfert/traitement de données pour faciliter la conformité à la disposition 60-E/2016 de la PDPA, qui réglemente le transfert transfrontalier de données à caractère personnel.

Les résidents de l’Argentine ont (a) le droit de connaître des informations sur l’existence et la finalité de ces Informations personnelles, et (b) le droit de rectifier et de limiter ou de s’opposer au traitement de leurs Informations personnelles si elles sont fausses, inexactes ou discriminatoires.

2. ### DÉCLARATIONS AUX RÉSIDENTS D’AUSTRALIE

Nous pouvons utiliser et divulguer vos Informations personnelles (telles que définies par la loi australienne) à des tiers basés en dehors de l’Australie, principalement aux États-Unis, comme décrit dans la section 9 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale. Vous acceptez et reconnaissez que les destinataires étrangers seront soumis à la loi sur la protection de la vie privée de leur pays et ne pourront être soumis à aucune obligation de protection de la vie privée ni à aucun principe similaire aux Principes australiens de protection de la vie privée. Ils seront également soumis à une loi étrangère qui pourrait contraindre la divulgation d’Informations personnelles à un tiers, tel qu’une autorité étrangère. À moins que vous ne nous notifiiez le contraire par écrit, vous serez réputé avoir consenti à la divulgation par nous des Informations personnelles à des destinataires étrangers. Vous avez la possibilité de rester anonyme lorsque vous traitez avec nous, ou de ne pas nous divulguer certaines Informations personnelles. Toutefois, cela peut signifier que nous ne pourrons pas être en mesure de vous fournir nos services.

Pour les résidents d’Australie, les mises à jour de la présente Politique de confidentialité prennent effet si nous obtenons votre consentement exprès ou si nous fournissons une option de désinscription lorsque des changements importants sont annoncés (par ex., sur nos Sites Web ou par e-mail).

3. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DU BRÉSIL

Les résidents du Brésil ont le droit de connaître les informations suivantes : si votre fourniture de vos Informations personnelles est une exigence contractuelle, ou s’il y a des conséquences à ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non aux deux), les informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (voir section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), vous avez le droit de retirer votre consentement au traitement de vos Informations personnelles, et, vos droits d’accès aux personnes concernées (voir ci-dessous).

Les résidents du Brésil ont également le droit de : (a) le droit de savoir, y compris d’obtenir une copie de ces informations ; (b) le droit à la rectification ; (c) le droit de limiter ou de s’opposer au traitement ; (d) le droit à la suppression ; (e) le droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de confidentialité concernant les entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos informations personnelles ont été partagées ; et (f) le droit d'introduire une réclamation auprès de l’autorité brésilienne de contrôle des données (l’ANPD).

4. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DU CANADA (Y COMPRIS LE QUÉBEC)

Notre Politique de confidentialité et nos pratiques générales sont conçues pour se conformer aux lois canadiennes sur la protection de la vie privée, y compris la Loi sur la protection des renseignements personnels et les documents électroniques (Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, PIPEDA), et, le cas échéant, la Loi sur la protection de la vie privée du Québec, la Protection des renseignements personnels dans le secteur privé (Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector, RSQ, c. P-39.1). Pour toutes les pratiques de traitement des informations qui ne sont pas raisonnablement liées aux finalités pour lesquelles vous avez contacté PlugShare, vous avez le droit de vous désinscrire de ces pratiques de traitement des informations (y compris le marketing, le profilage, la publicité comportementale, le partage avec un tiers qui n’est pas un prestataire de services).  

Les résidents canadiens ont le droit de refuser notre utilisation des Informations personnelles à des fins de marketing direct et d’autres traitements qui ne sont pas raisonnablement nécessaires pour répondre à ce pour quoi vous nous avez engagés.

5. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DE HONG KONG

Nous utilisons vos Informations personnelles aux fins de marketing direct suivantes : (a) pour communiquer avec vous au sujet de nos produits et services et de ceux de nos sociétés affiliées ; et (b) pour vous envoyer d’autres déclarations, promotions ou autres documents marketing concernant nos Sites Web, Produits et Services, et ceux de nos sociétés affiliées. Votre consentement à cette fin sera demandé au moment de votre soumission d’Informations personnelles (par ex., lors de la création du compte, de l’inscription à l’événement, etc.) à nous.

6. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DU MEXIQUE

En plus des informations présentées ci-dessus, les résidents du Mexique ont le droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de confidentialité, y compris (a) si votre fourniture de vos Informations personnelles est une exigence contractuelle ou s’il y a une conséquence pour ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non aux deux), (b) les informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (qui est abordée dans la section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (c) la durée de conservation (voir la section 7 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (d) le droit de retirer votre consentement au traitement de vos Informations personnelles, et, (e) vos droits d’accès aux personnes concernées (voir ci-dessous). Vous avez également le droit de connaître l’indication expresse des Informations personnelles sensibles à traiter.

Les résidents du Mexique ont également : (a) le droit de connaître les informations personnelles que nous collectons, y compris d’être informés des entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos informations personnelles ont été partagées et d’obtenir une copie de ces informations ; (b) le droit de rectification ; (c) le droit de limiter ou de s’opposer au traitement ; et (d) le droit de suppression.

7. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DE SINGAPOUR

Entre autres droits, si nous sommes présents à Singapour, vous avez le droit de faire transmettre vos Informations personnelles que nous possédons à une autre organisation.

Les personnes ou sociétés auxquelles nous divulguons et transférons vos Informations personnelles peuvent être situées en dehors de Singapour. Nous veillerons à ce que les destinataires des Informations personnelles transférées soient en mesure de fournir aux Informations personnelles transférées un niveau de protection comparable aux normes de protection énoncées en vertu de la loi de Singapour sur la protection de la vie privée par l’utilisation d’accords écrits de transfert de données (pour les transferts à des tiers) ou de règles d’entreprise contraignantes (pour les transferts à nos sociétés affiliées et à d’autres entités qui nous sont liées).

8. ### DÉCLARATION AUX RÉSIDENTS DE TAÏWAN

Les résidents de Taïwan ont le droit de recevoir des informations sur les pratiques de confidentialité.

Les résidents de Taïwan ont également : (a) le droit de connaître les informations personnelles que nous collectons, y compris d’être informés des entités publiques et privées avec lesquelles vos informations personnelles ont été partagées et d’obtenir une copie de ces informations ; (b) le droit de rectification ; (c) le droit de limiter ou de s’opposer au traitement ; et (d) le droit de suppression.

En plus des informations présentées ci-dessus, les résidents de Taïwan ont le droit de connaitre certaines informations sur les Informations personnelles que nous collectons, y compris (a) si votre fourniture de vos Informations personnelles est une exigence contractuelle ou s’il y a une conséquence pour ne pas fournir ces données (la réponse est non aux deux), (b) les informations concernant toute prise de décision automatisée (y compris le profilage) que nous faisons (qui est abordée dans la section 2.1 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (c) la durée de conservation (voir la section 7 de notre Politique de confidentialité principale), (d) le droit de retirer votre consentement au traitement de vos Informations personnelles, et, (e) vos droits d’accès aux personnes concernées (voir ci-dessous). Vous avez également le droit de connaître l’indication expresse des Informations personnelles sensibles à traiter (nous ne collectons aucune information « sensible »).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) La Loi sur la protection de la vie privée du Colorado entre en vigueur le 1er juillet 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) La Loi sur la protection de la vie privée de l’Utah entre en vigueur le 31 décembre 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) La Loi sur la protection de la vie privée du Connecticut entre en vigueur le 1er juillet 2023.

INFORMATIVA SULLA PRIVACY PLUGSHARE
===================================

DATA DI ENTRATA IN VIGORE: 10 luglio 2023
-----------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (“PlugShare”, “noi”, “ci” o “nostro”) ha l’obiettivo di creare una comunità di supporto per utenti di veicoli elettrici (“VE”) e di fornire informazioni sulla ricarica e una vasta gamma di prodotti e servizi di primo livello e innovativi per rendere l’esperienza di guida dei veicoli elettrici il più facile e gratificante possibile. La presente Informativa illustra le nostre politiche in materia di raccolta, uso, divulgazione, ritenzione, e trasferimento di dati personali (definiti di seguito) che raccogliamo sull’utente (“utente” o “suo”) attraverso le nostre interazioni con l’utente tramite i nostri Siti web ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); o [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); collettivamente, “Siti web”), i servizi correlati e le nostre applicazioni mobili (collettivamente “Servizi”), nonché attraverso le interazioni con parti non affiliate come i nostri fornitori che collaborano con noi per fornire i nostri Servizi all’utente.

Si prega di leggere attentamente il presente documento. Se l’utente non desidera che trattiamo i suoi dati personali, non ci fornisca alcuna informazione; tuttavia, in tal caso potrebbe non essere in grado di sfruttare alcune funzionalità dei nostri Servizi.

L’utilizzo del Sito web e dei nostri Servizi è sempre soggetto ai nostri Termini di utilizzo (disponibili all’indirizzo [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) e come di volta in volta aggiornati (i “Termini”).

La presente Informativa sulla privacy non si applica a siti o servizi non affiliati collegati a o dai nostri Siti web o Servizi diversi da quelli dei nostri Fornitori di servizi, ai nostri canali o piattaforme di social media che li ospitano, o a qualsiasi sito o servizio raccomandato o a cui si fa riferimento dai nostri Siti web o Servizi o dal nostro personale.

Residenti in California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah e Connecticut: Si prega di consultare la nostra [Informativa integrativa sulla privacy per i residenti di alcuni Stati USA](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) per informazioni sul trattamento dei dati personali.

Residenti di altri Paesi: Se l'utente è residente in un paese diverso dagli Stati Uniti, è pregato di consultare la pagina del sito web Informazioni integrative sulla privacy per alcuni paesi al di fuori degli Stati Uniti per ulteriori informazioni sul trattamento dei suoi dati personali da parte nostra.

Lavoriamo costantemente per migliorare i nostri Servizi, e potremmo dover modificare la presente Informativa sulla privacy di tanto in tanto. La nostra attuale Informativa sulla privacy sarà sempre disponibile sui nostri Siti web. Si prega di notare la data di entrata in vigore sulla presente Informativa sulla privacy e di verificare periodicamente la presenza di aggiornamenti.

1\. CHE TIPO DI DATI RACCOGLIAMO
================================

1.1 COSA SI INTENDE PER DATI PERSONALI?
---------------------------------------

La presente Informativa sulla privacy riguarda il trattamento da parte nostra di informazioni di identificazione personale degli utenti. Per “Dati personali” si intende generalmente qualsiasi informazione non crittografata che identifica, si riferisce a, descrive, è ragionevolmente in grado di essere associata a, o potrebbe ragionevolmente essere collegata a una particolare persona come, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, il nome dell’utente, il suo indirizzo postale, l’indirizzo e-mail, il numero di telefono, ecc. .

I dati personali non includono informazioni personali che sono state rese anonime o aggregate nei modi previsti dalle leggi applicabili, in modo che non possano più essere utilizzate direttamente o attraverso altri mezzi ragionevolmente disponibili per identificare un individuo (collettivamente, “Dati personali deidentificati”).

1.2 CATEGORIE DI DATI PERSONALI CHE RACCOGLIAMO E TRATTIAMO
-----------------------------------------------------------

Raccogliamo diverse categorie di dati personali da e sull’utente, come riassunto nella seguente tabella:

| Categoria | Dati personali specifici |
| --- | --- |
| Identificativi | * nome e cognome<br>* nome utente (che può includere nome e cognome)<br>* indirizzo e-mail<br>* codice postale<br>* sesso, sesso<br>* identificativo personale univoco, ad es., nome o numero del cliente o dell’account, numero di telefono, identificativo del dispositivo mobile |
| Dati demografici | * paese di residenza |
| Informazioni commerciali | * cronologia e tendenze di acquisto di prodotti/servizi |
| Attività in Internet o altra rete elettronica; informazioni sul dispositivo | * tipo e produttore del dispositivo e relativo ID/UDID o codice specifico del dispositivo simile<br>* sistema operativo e piattaforma<br>* risoluzione dello schermo<br>* nome, velocità e tipo di connessione del provider di servizi Internet o del gestore di telefonia mobile<br>* Informazioni su indirizzo, protocollo e sequenza del protocollo Internet (o IP)<br>* cookie<br>* tag pixel<br>* Indirizzo MAC (Media Access Control) delle pagine visitate<br>* identificativo pubblicitario del dispositivo mobile<br>* tipo, lingua e versione del browser<br>* Navigazione, sessione, interazione e cronologia di ricerca del sito web, materiale e pagine visualizzati, ora e data di accesso ai siti web, numero di byte trasferiti, numero di clic per visita, tempo trascorso su una pagina, dati click-through e clickstream, query effettuate, risultati di ricerca selezionati, commenti fatti<br>* data e URL dell’ultima pagina web visitata prima di visitare i nostri Siti web, e URL della prima pagina visitata dopo aver lasciato i nostri Siti web<br>* tipo di Servizio richiesto<br>* intestazioni del protocollo di trasferimento ipertesto, banner del client applicativo e del server |
| Geolocalizzazione | * posizione fisica e/o movimenti |
| Altro | * Dati di ricarica del veicolo, marca, modello e anno<br>* Informazioni fornite volontariamente dall’utente nell’ambito di una risposta di feedback o di altre richieste generali effettuate tramite i nostri Siti web<br>* Inferenze tratte da una qualsiasi delle informazioni elencate per creare un profilo su un consumatore che rifletta le sue preferenze, caratteristiche, tendenze psicologiche, predisposizioni, comportamento, atteggiamenti, intelligenza, capacità o attitudine del consumatore |

1.3 MODALITÀ DI RACCOLTA DEI DATI PERSONALI
-------------------------------------------

Possiamo raccogliere dati personali direttamente dall’utente tramite i nostri Servizi quando l’utente:

* ci fornisce dati personali compilando moduli web sui nostri Siti web o effettuando transazioni nei negozi (marchi della società madre, controllata e affiliata). Ciò include le informazioni fornite durante la creazione di un account online, l’acquisto dei nostri Servizi, l’iscrizione alle nostre newsletter elettroniche o ad altre comunicazioni, la richiesta di informazioni da parte nostra, l’invio o la pubblicazione di materiale (ove consentito) sui nostri forum, o l’interazione con l’assistenza clienti o il servizio, la segnalazione di un problema con i nostri Siti web, le applicazioni mobili o i Servizi o la comunicazione in altro modo con noi.
* Ci contatta. Ciò include tutte le registrazioni e le copie della sua corrispondenza con noi, ad esempio con i nostri uffici o con il servizio clienti/assistenza o l'invio di un assegno.
* Si registra a un evento o ci informa di qualsiasi richiesta di accessibilità o di altre sistemazioni.
* Risponde ai sondaggi che noi o i nostri Fornitori di servizi potremmo chiedergli di completare per scopi di ricerca.
* Esegue query di ricerca sui siti web.
* Partecipa a programmi di fidelizzazione/premi.
* Presenta una candidatura per un impiego.
* Utilizza dispositivi e reti per accedere ai nostri Servizi, come la sincronizzazione del proprio veicolo con i nostri Servizi.
* Utilizza determinate funzionalità sui nostri Siti web e applicazioni mobili. Sebbene gli utenti possano accedere a funzioni limitate senza divulgare loro dati personali, come la navigazione in stazioni di ricarica pubbliche senza un account, raccogliamo dati personali quando gli utenti registrano un account. Gli utenti possono scegliere di utilizzare solo la propria e-mail e password per navigare sui caricabatterie domestici. Gli utenti possono anche scegliere di sfruttare le funzionalità avanzate postando, commentando, pubblicando o condividendo ulteriori dati personali con la comunità. In generale, gli utenti scelgono quante informazioni desiderano visualizzare su se stessi e possono scegliere di non partecipare in qualsiasi momento.

Possiamo anche raccogliere dati personali da parti non affiliate, tra cui:

* fornitori di dati (ad es. società che forniscono dati demografici e altre informazioni riguardanti i consumatori)
* sulle applicazioni mobili (marchi della società madre, sussidiaria e affiliata)
* partner di marketing congiunti
* aziende o piattaforme pubblicitarie online (ad es., se l’utente collega volontariamente o collega il suo profilo sui social media ai nostri Servizi)
* fornitori di servizi di esecuzione e consegna
* aziende di social media
* altri fornitori di servizi
* rispondere a opportunità di impiego
* azioni del sito web/modulo web o dell’app dell’utente
* fornitori per la verifica della referenze lavorative o il controllo dei precedenti
* Consente, tramite le proprie impostazioni del dispositivo o i servizi di terze parti, di ricevere dati di geolocalizzazione al fine di mostrare informazioni locali (ad esempio, una stazione di ricarica locale) sulle nostre applicazioni mobili.

1.4 INFORMAZIONI RACCOLTE ATTRAVERSO TECNOLOGIE AUTOMATIZZATE
-------------------------------------------------------------

Mentre l’utente naviga e interagisce con i nostri Servizi, possiamo anche utilizzare tecnologie di raccolta automatica dei dati per raccogliere determinate informazioni dal suo dispositivo, browser o altre attività di rete come descritto nella nostra Informativa sui cookie, disponibile all’indirizzo [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Visita al sito web e informazioni sul dispositivo. Raccogliamo i dettagli delle visite dell’utente ai nostri Siti web e dell’uso delle nostre App mobili, inclusi, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, dati sul traffico, dati di geolocalizzazione, registri e altri dati di comunicazione e le risorse a cui l’utente accede e che utilizza sui Siti web. Raccogliamo informazioni sul computer, sul dispositivo mobile e sulla connessione a Internet dell’utente, tra cui l’indirizzo IP, il sistema operativo, il tipo di browser, i modelli di clickstream (ovvero, su cosa clicca su un sito web), l’URL del sito web più recente visitato prima di accedere ai nostri Siti web, la quantità di tempo che l’utente ha trascorso sui nostri Siti web e le pagine visualizzate durante la visita ai nostri Siti web. Possiamo ricavare una stima approssimativa della posizione dell’utente dal suo indirizzo IP quando visita i nostri Siti web. Per gli utenti delle nostre App mobili, possiamo anche raccogliere e mantenere una cronologia delle loro informazioni precise sulla posizione utilizzando tecnologie Wi-Fi e/o Bluetooth, nonché gli identificativi del loro dispositivo e le coordinate GPS (ad es. latitudine/longitudine). Se l’utente desidera impedire la raccolta delle informazioni sulla sua posizione, deve modificare le impostazioni nel suo dispositivo mobile per limitare l’accesso dell’App mobile alle informazioni sulla posizione.

Quando utilizzi il nostro sito Web, condividiamo le informazioni che raccogliamo da te, come la tua e-mail (in formato hash), l'indirizzo IP o le informazioni sul tuo browser o sistema operativo, con i nostri partner di identità/fornitori di servizi. Questi partner restituiscono un codice di identificazione online che possiamo memorizzare nel nostro cookie di prima parte per il nostro utilizzo nella pubblicità online, in-app e multicanale e può essere condiviso con società pubblicitarie per consentire pubblicità mirata e basata sugli interessi. Per negare il consenso a questo utilizzo, fare clic qui ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Monitoraggio comportamentale. Possiamo anche utilizzare queste tecnologie per raccogliere informazioni sulle attività online dell’utente nel tempo e su siti web di terze parti o altri servizi online, o associare i dati personali dell’utente ad altre informazioni raccolte in questo modo.

Analisi della posizione: le nostre App mobili e i Siti web del browser mobile includono funzionalità (ad es., per l’invio di una revisione di un conducente di una stazione di ricarica) che ci consentono di identificare la posizione di un conducente e la posizione della stazione di ricarica in cui si trova attualmente un utente. Raccogliamo informazioni quali indirizzo IP, ID del dispositivo e geolocalizzazione. Gli utenti dell’App mobile possono scegliere di utilizzare le App mobili in forma anonima o di accedere come utente identificato, nel qual caso possono essere utilizzati i dati personali forniti al momento della registrazione.

Per gli utenti delle App mobili, potremmo chiedere l’autorizzazione ad accedere a determinate informazioni dal dispositivo mobile dell’utente, tra cui l’elenco dei contatti, le foto e i video, il microfono e la fotocamera. È facoltativo che l’utente ci fornisca l’accesso a tali informazioni. Tuttavia, in caso contrario alcune funzionalità delle App mobili potrebbero non funzionare in modo ottimale.

Web Beacon. Le pagine dei nostri Siti web e delle nostre e-mail possono contenere piccoli file elettronici noti come web beacon (chiamati anche clear gif, pixel tag e single pixel gif) che ci consentono, ad esempio, di contare gli utenti che hanno visitato tali pagine o aperto un’e-mail e per altre statistiche correlate al sito web (ad es., registrando la popolarità di determinati contenuti del sito web e verificando l’integrità del sistema e del server).

Tracciamento dei pixel. Oltre a utilizzare i cookie, i Siti web possono utilizzare il “tracciamento dei pixel”. Il tracciamento dei pixel prevede l’uso di pixel tag non visibili all’utente e costituiti da alcune righe di codice del computer. Il tracciamento dei pixel misura l’efficacia degli annunci pubblicitari e compila statistiche di utilizzo aggregate e specifiche. Possiamo accedere a questi pixel tag per identificare attività e interessi che possono consentirci di abbinare meglio i nostri Prodotti, Servizi e offerte agli interessi e alle esigenze dell’utente. Ad esempio, se l’utente visita i nostri Siti web da una pubblicità su un altro sito web, il pixel tag consentirà all’inserzionista di tenere traccia che la sua pubblicità ha portato l’utente sui Siti web. Se l’utente visita i nostri Siti web e noi lo colleghiamo a un altro sito web, potremmo anche essere in grado di determinare che l’utente è stato inviato e/o collegato a un sito web di terze parti.

GIF. Possiamo utilizzare minuscole immagini note come GIF trasparenti per monitorare il comportamento degli utenti, comprese le statistiche su chi apre le nostre e-mail.

Indirizzo IP. I nostri server (o quelli dei nostri fornitori di servizi) registrano automaticamente determinate informazioni sui file di registro riportate dal browser dell’utente quando accede ai Siti web. Questi registri del server possono includere informazioni quali le pagine dei Siti web visitati, l’indirizzo del protocollo Internet (“IP”), il tipo di browser e altre informazioni su come l’utente interagisce con i Siti web. Questi file di registro vengono generalmente eliminati periodicamente.

Metriche e analisi di terze parti. Metriche e analisi di terze parti, su determinate pagine o caratteristiche dei Servizi per aiutarci a comprendere e analizzare il traffico dei visitatori, misurare l’efficacia promozionale e l’efficacia delle nostre caratteristiche, offerte e campagne di marketing. Utilizziamo questi strumenti anche per identificare lacune, carenze e aree delle nostre operazioni che necessitano di miglioramenti, e per visualizzare le prestazioni complessive e la classificazione della nostra presenza online. Questi strumenti possono memorizzare cookie sul dispositivo dell’utente a loro discrezione.

INFORMATIVA E POLITICA SUI COOKIE

Le tecnologie che utilizziamo per la raccolta automatica dei dati includono anche i cookie, come descritto di seguito.

Cookie del browser

I cookie del browser sono piccoli file collocati sul disco rigido del computer o del dispositivo mobile dell’utente. Possono contenere determinati dati, tra cui, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, il nome del server che lo ha inserito, un identificativo sotto forma di numero univoco e una data di scadenza (solo alcuni cookie). I cookie del browser sono gestiti dal browser web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, ecc.) sul computer o sul dispositivo mobile dell’utente. I nostri Siti web utilizzano diverse tipologie di cookie che hanno scopi diversi.

Cookie essenziali

I cookie essenziali sono necessari per consentire all’utente di navigare nei nostri Siti web e utilizzarne le funzioni. Senza di essi, servizi come il carrello degli acquisti e la fatturazione elettronica non potrebbero funzionare.

Cookie di prestazione

I cookie di prestazione raccolgono informazioni sull’uso dei nostri Siti web, ad esempio quali pagine vengono consultate più spesso. Queste informazioni ci consentono di ottimizzare i nostri Siti web e semplificare la navigazione. I cookie di prestazione consentono inoltre ai nostri affiliati e partner di scoprire se l’utente ha effettuato l’accesso a una delle pagine del nostro Sito web dal loro sito e se la sua visita ha portato all’uso o all’acquisto di un Prodotto o Servizio dai nostri Siti web, compresi i riferimenti per il Prodotto o Servizio acquistato. Tutte le informazioni raccolte dai cookie di prestazione sono aggregate e, quindi, anonime.

Cookie di funzionalità

I cookie di funzionalità consentono ai nostri Siti web di ricordare le scelte effettuate durante la navigazione. Ad esempio, possiamo memorizzare la posizione geografica dell’utente in un cookie in modo che vengano visualizzati i Siti web corrispondenti alla sua area. Possiamo anche ricordare le preferenze dell’utente, come la dimensione del testo, il carattere e altri aspetti personalizzabili dei Siti web. I cookie di funzionalità possono anche essere in grado di tenere traccia dei prodotti o dei video consultati per evitare ripetizioni. Le informazioni raccolte da questi cookie non possono essere utilizzate per identificare l’utente e non possono monitorare la sua attività di navigazione su siti web che non appartengono a noi. I cookie di funzionalità ci consentono di visualizzare pubblicità su misura per l’utente sui nostri Siti web, per comprendere quali parti dei nostri contenuti sono più interessanti per l’utente e quali categorie di Prodotti o Servizi richiede. Alcuni dei nostri fornitori di servizi sono autorizzati a inserire cookie sui nostri Siti web. Tali società possono inoltre fornire all’utente la possibilità di impedire l’uso dei cookie in futuro.

In qualsiasi momento, l’utente può impedire o rifiutare l’uso futuro di alcuni cookie attivando l’impostazione appropriata nel browser per rifiutare di accettare i cookie del browser. Tuttavia, in tal caso, l’esperienza dell’utente sui nostri Siti web potrebbe risentirne; ad esempio, l’utente potrebbe non essere in grado di accedere a determinate parti dei nostri Siti web. A meno che l’utente non abbia modificato le impostazioni del browser in modo che rifiuti i cookie, il nostro sistema collocherà i cookie quando l’utente indirizza il browser ai nostri Siti web.

Cookie di archiviazione locale

Alcune funzionalità dei nostri Siti web possono utilizzare oggetti memorizzati localmente (per raccogliere e memorizzare informazioni sulle preferenze e sulla navigazione dell’utente verso, da e sui nostri Siti web. I cookie di archiviazione locale non sono gestiti dalle stesse impostazioni del browser utilizzate per i cookie del browser.

Possiamo anche combinare i dati personali che raccogliamo dall’utente al di fuori dei nostri Siti web o Servizi con quelli che vengono raccolti attraverso i nostri Siti web o Servizi o con altri mezzi come descritto sopra.

1.5 INFORMAZIONI SUL DISPOSITIVO, SULLA RETE, SULLA GEOLOCALIZZAZIONE E SUL VEICOLO ELETTRICO
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Quando l’utente visita o esce dai nostri Siti web o Servizi facendo clic su un collegamento ipertestuale o visualizzando un plug-in su un sito web di terze parti, riceviamo automaticamente l’URL del sito da cui proviene l’utente o quello a cui viene indirizzato. Inoltre, gli inserzionisti ricevono l’URL della pagina su cui si trova quando l’utente fa clic su qualsiasi annuncio che potrebbe apparire sui nostri Servizi. Riceviamo anche l’indirizzo del protocollo Internet (“IP”) del computer dell’utente o del server proxy che utilizza per accedere a Internet, i dettagli del sistema operativo del suo computer, il tipo di browser Web, il dispositivo mobile (incluso l’identificativo del dispositivo mobile fornito dal sistema operativo del dispositivo mobile), il sistema operativo mobile (se si accede ai nostri siti Web o servizi utilizzando un dispositivo mobile) e il nome dell’ISP dell’utente o del suo gestore di telefonia mobile.

1.6 SONDAGGI
------------

Noi o terze parti non affiliate possiamo condurre sondaggi sugli utenti in merito ai nostri Servizi. Alcune terze parti non affiliate possono indirizzare all’utente pubblicità o promozioni in base alle sue risposte ai sondaggi. Noi o le parti parti non affiliate sviluppiamo nuovi programmi o prodotti in base alle informazioni che l’utente condivide nei sondaggi. Possiamo utilizzare terze parti non affiliate per fornire incentivi finanziari o di altro tipo all’utente per partecipare ai sondaggi. Se l’erogazione degli incentivi richiede le informazioni di contatto dell’utente, all’utente potrebbe essere chiesto di fornire gli stessi alla terza parte non affiliata che realizza l’offerta di incentivi; le quali informazioni saranno utilizzate solo allo scopo di fornire gli incentivi promessi e verificare le informazioni di contatto dell’utente. Spetta all’utente decidere se fornire tali informazioni o se desidera approfittare di un’offerta di incentivi. Il consenso dell’utente all’uso di qualsiasi dato personale per le finalità stabilite nel sondaggio sarà esplicitamente richiesto dalla terza parte non affiliata che lo conduce. Per scegliere di non partecipare ai nostri sondaggi, l’utente può inviarci la sua richiesta utilizzando le informazioni di contatto riportate di seguito.

2\. NATURA E FINALITÀ DEL TRATTAMENTO DEI DATI PERSONALI
========================================================

Utilizziamo le informazioni che raccogliamo sull’utente o che l’utente ci fornisce, compresi ii dati personali, per uno o più delle seguenti finalità:

* Presentare i nostri Siti web e le applicazioni mobili e i relativi contenuti all’utente.
* Fornire all’utente informazioni e rispondere alle sue domande sui Prodotti o Servizi che ci richiede e informazioni su nuovi prodotti e servizi, sconti, promozioni speciali o eventi imminenti, e caratteristiche o offerte che riteniamo possano essere di suo interesse o riguardanti una promozione, un concorso o una lotteria a cui ha partecipato
* Elaborare le informazioni sull’account e i pagamenti delle transazioni, tra cui, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, le tariffe per i Prodotti e/o i Servizi, nonché i pagamenti e i rimborsi per qualsiasi Prodotto o Servizio acquistato (anche se non riceviamo il numero completo della carta di credito o debito dell’utente).
* Elaborare sconti, offerte, premi fedeltà e/o richieste di sconti, moduli e applicazioni e coordinarci con il produttore, il rivenditore e/o il grossista.
* Fornire all’utente avvisi sul suo account, inclusi avvisi di scadenza e rinnovo.
* Notificare all’utente informazioni relative o modifiche ai nostri Siti web, alle nostre politiche, termini o a qualsiasi Prodotto o Servizio che offriamo o forniamo, o riguardanti il suo account.
* Trattare dati personali o altre informazioni che l’utente ci invia.
* Consentire all’utente di partecipare a funzioni interattive sui nostri Siti web.
* Sviluppare e migliorare i nostri Prodotti e Servizi e svilupparne di nuovi, ad esempio analizzando le tendenze degli utenti e misurando dati demografici e interessi.
* Per il funzionamento interno del sito Web, del Servizio e del sistema, l'amministrazione, la manutenzione, le verifiche e le revisioni interne, la diagnosi dei problemi tecnici e il mantenimento della sicurezza.
* Indagare su qualsiasi violazione dei nostri Termini di utilizzo o della presente Informativa sulla privacy.
* Monitorare potenziali problemi e tendenze con l’uso dei nostri Siti web e Servizi da parte degli utenti e personalizzare il nostro supporto per servirvi meglio.
* Fornire statistiche sui livelli di utilizzo dei Siti web e altre informazioni correlate ai nostri Fornitori di servizi.
* Notificare all’utente incidenti relativi alla privacy dei dati o fornire le informazioni richieste dalla legge.
* Richiedere la partecipazione dell’utente a valutazioni, recensioni, sondaggi, focus group o altre iniziative che ci aiutano a raccogliere informazioni utilizzate per sviluppare e migliorare i nostri Prodotti e Servizi.
* Adempiere a qualsiasi altro scopo per il quale l’utente fornisce dati personali.
* In qualsiasi altro modo possiamo descrivere e per cui otteniamo il consenso dell’utente quando fornisce le informazioni.

Utilizziamo cookie, clear gif e informazioni sui file di log per: (a) ricordare le informazioni in modo che l'utente non debba reinserirle durante la visita o la volta successiva che visita i Siti web; (b) fornire contenuti e informazioni personalizzati; (c) monitorare l'efficacia dei nostri Servizi; (d) monitorare le metriche aggregate come il numero totale di visitatori, il traffico e i modelli demografici; (e) diagnosticare o risolvere i problemi tecnologici segnalati dai nostri utenti o tecnici che sono associati a determinati indirizzi IP; e/o (f) aiutare l'utente ad accedere in modo efficiente alle proprie informazioni dopo l'accesso.

I dati statistici che raccogliamo automaticamente ci aiutano a migliorare i nostri Siti web e a fornire Prodotti e Servizi migliori e più personalizzati, tra cui, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, consentendoci di: stimare le dimensioni del nostro pubblico/visitatore e i modelli di utilizzo, memorizzare informazioni sulle preferenze dell’utente, consentirci di personalizzare e migliorare i nostri Siti web, accelerare le ricerche e/o riconoscere l’utente quando torna ai nostri Siti web.

Possiamo raccogliere e utilizzare le informazioni della sessione di ricarica del veicolo elettronico dell’utente (ad es., tempo di ricarica, consumo energetico, proprietà e dati della stazione, ecc.) e la marca, il modello e l’anno del veicolo dell’utente per amministrare il suo account, ad esempio per distinguere tra più veicoli o utenti che condividono un singolo account e per scopi analitici.

Nella misura in cui l’utente non acconsente alle pratiche di trattamento delle informazioni qui stabilite, potrebbe avere il diritto di scegliere di rifiutare le stesse. Tutte le richieste di opt-out devono essere indirizzate a [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Nella misura in cui le richieste di opt-out siano rispettate, avranno effetto sul trattamento futuro e non sul trattamento che si è verificato in base al previo consenso.

2.1 PROCESSO DECISIONALE AUTOMATIZZATO
--------------------------------------

Possiamo utilizzare i dati personali dell’utente che ci fornisce e che otteniamo da altre fonti per comprendere meglio i suoi interessi, in modo da poter cercare di prevedere quali altri Prodotti, Servizi e informazioni potrebbero essere di suo interesse. Questa pratica prevede di prendere decisioni automatizzate sull’utente in base a queste informazioni al fine di consentirci di personalizzare meglio le nostre interazioni per renderle più pertinenti e interessanti per l’utente. L’utente può opporsi a ciò in qualsiasi momento o chiederci ulteriori informazioni sulla metodologia applicata nei nostri processi decisionali automatizzati contattandoci (si veda la sezione 12 di seguito).

2.2 MESSAGGI DI TESTO
---------------------

I nostri Servizi possono includere l’invio di messaggi SMS (Short Message Service), che possono includere fino a due messaggi al giorno al dispositivo wireless (a meno che l’utente non comunichi ulteriormente con noi), ma la frequenza dei messaggi può variare.  Quando l’utente acconsente espressamente a ricevere messaggi di testo da noi e fornisce un numero di cellulare, accetta di ricevere testi informativi e transazionali ricorrenti da o per conto nostro al numero fornito. Acconsentendo espressamente a ricevere messaggi SMS da noi e fornendo un numero di cellulare, l’utente garantisce e dichiara di essere il proprietario del numero di cellulare che ci fornisce. Possiamo utilizzare le informazioni dell’utente per contattarlo in merito all’utilizzo, agli acquisti, ai resi (se disponibili), agli aggiornamenti del Sito web, alla conduzione di sondaggi o alle comunicazioni informative e relative ai servizi, inclusi importanti aggiornamenti di sicurezza. Dopo averci inviato il messaggio SMS “STOP”,  invieremo all’utente un messaggio SMS per confermare che ha annullato l’iscrizione. In alternativa, l'utente può inoltrare la propria richiesta via e-mail, indicando l'indirizzo e-mail e il numero di telefono registrati presso di noi, o con qualsiasi mezzo ragionevole. Successivamente, non riceverà più messaggi SMS da parte nostra. Se l’utente vuole iscriversi di nuovo, è sufficiente che si iscriva come la prima volta e noi ricominceremo a inviargli messaggi SMS. Per ricevere aiuto, rispondere a un messaggio con HELP. Potrebbero essere applicate tariffe per messaggi e dati, a seconda del piano telefonico dell’utente. Le compagnie telefoniche non sono responsabili per messaggi ritardati o non consegnati.

2.3 PLUG-IN PER SOCIAL MEDIA
----------------------------

Integriamo nei Siti web interfacce di programmi applicativi di social media o plug-in (“Plug-in”) da social network, tra cui Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest e/o eventualmente altre società. Per registrarsi come utente, l'utente può avere la possibilità di accedere utilizzando il login di Facebook o di un altro sito di social media.

Ad esempio, quando l’utente visita i nostri Siti web, il plug-in crea una connessione diretta tra il browser e il server Facebook. Ciò consente a Facebook di ricevere informazioni sulla sua visita ai nostri Siti web con il suo indirizzo IP. Se l’utente clicca sul pulsante “Mi piace” di Facebook mentre è connesso al proprio account Facebook, l’utente può collegare i contenuti dei nostri siti web al proprio profilo Facebook. Ciò consente a Facebook di assegnare la sua visita ai nostri Siti web al suo account utente. Si prega di notare che, in qualità di fornitore dei siti web, non riceviamo alcuna notifica sul contenuto dei dati trasmessi o sul loro utilizzo da parte di Facebook. Se l’utente non desidera che Facebook assegni la sua visita ai nostri Siti web al suo account utente Facebook, deve uscire dal suo account utente Facebook.

Se l'utente accede tramite un Plug-in di social media, ci autorizza ad accedere a determinate informazioni sull'account di quel sito di social media, come il suo profilo pubblico sui social media (compatibilmente con le impostazioni sulla privacy del sito di social media), il suo indirizzo e-mail, i suoi interessi, i suoi like, il suo sesso, il suo compleanno, la sua storia formativa, le sue relazioni, i suoi interessi, la sua città attuale, le sue foto, la sua descrizione personale, la sua lista di amici e le informazioni e le foto dei suoi amici del sito di social media che potrebbero essere amici comuni di altri utenti del sito di social media. I plug-in possono trasferire informazioni sull’utente alla rispettiva piattaforma del plug-in senza alcuna azione da parte dell’utente. Queste informazioni possono includere il numero di identificazione utente della piattaforma, il sito web su cui ci si trova e altro ancora. L’interazione con un plug-in trasmetterà le informazioni direttamente al social network di tale plug-in e tali informazioni potrebbero essere visibili ad altri su tale piattaforma. I plug-in sono controllati dall’informativa sulla privacy del rispettivo sito di social media (disponibile sul loro sito web) e non dalla nostra Informativa sulla privacy.

3\. COME DIVULGHIAMO I DATI PERSONALI A TERZI
=============================================

3.1 TIPOLOGIE DI TERZI
----------------------

Possiamo o divulghiamo i dati personali dell’utente, in tutto o in parte, ai seguenti tipi di terze parti e per una o più delle seguenti finalità:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Tipologie di terzi | Scopo |
| Fornitori di archiviazione o di hosting dei dati | archiviazione e trasmissione sicura dei dati dell’utente |
| Fornitori di servizi di database e software | gestione e monitoraggio dei dati dell’utente |
| Consulenti legali e di conformità, come consulenti esterni, revisori esterni o consulenti fiscali | Fornitura di servizi professionali a noi |
| Fornitori di servizi di gestione delle identità | scopi di autenticazione |
| Fornitori di soluzioni di pagamento | elaborazione sicura dei pagamenti che l’utente ci fornisce |
| Produttori, rivenditori e grossisti | invio, elaborazione e gestione di sconti, offerte, premi fedeltà e simili |
| Fornitori di servizi di esecuzione e spedizione | evasione e consegna di Prodotti, Servizi e merce |
| Fornitori di sondaggi e ricerche | esecuzione di studi per nostro conto |
| Partner pubblicitari, compresi i fornitori di social media | fornire pubblicità mirata |

Per qualsiasi trasferimento di dati personali che non sia ragionevolmente necessario per raggiungere gli scopi per i quali l’utente sta interagendo con PlugShare (ad es., per scopi di marketing o di indagine), l’utente ha il diritto di rinunciare a tale trattamento. Per esercitare il suo diritto di rinuncia, può contattarci all’indirizzo [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 FORNITORI DI SERVIZI, PARTNER COMMERCIALI E SUBAPPALTATORI
--------------------------------------------------------------

 Possiamo condividere i dati personali dell’utente con Fornitori di servizi che svolgono servizi per nostro conto, come discusso sopra. Questi Fornitori di servizi possono avere accesso ai dati personali dell’utente al fine di fornire tali servizi a noi o per nostro conto. Se incarichiamo Fornitori di servizi per uno qualsiasi dei suddetti, l’uso dei dati personali dell’utente sarà vincolato da obblighi di riservatezza e il loro utilizzo di tali dati sarà limitato alla fornitura dei loro servizi a noi. Possiamo archiviare i dati personali in luoghi al di fuori del nostro controllo diretto (ad es., su server o database situati o co-ubicati con i Fornitori di servizi di hosting dei dati).  

3.3 PUBBLICITÀ COMPORTAMENTALE INTERCONTESTUALE
-----------------------------------------------

Siamo tenuti a divulgare se condividiamo dati personali con una terza parte impegnata in pubblicità comportamentale (mirata) intercontestuale. Nei dodici (12) mesi precedenti, abbiamo o potremmo aver divulgato le seguenti categorie di dati personali in un contesto che, ai sensi di alcune leggi (ad es., CPRA, GDPR o GDPR del Regno Unito della California) può essere considerato una vendita:

* Identificativi
* Attività Internet o altre attività di rete simili
* Dati di geolocalizzazione

L’utente ha la possibilità di rinunciare a questa condivisione facendo clic sui prompt di esclusione che appariranno sull’avviso che riceve quando visita per la prima volta le nostre applicazioni mobili o i nostri Siti web.

3.4 TRASFERIMENTI AZIENDALI
---------------------------

L’utente riconosce (e non si opporrà) alla nostra divulgazione o trasferimento dei suoi dati personali, dati personali deidentificati, e altre informazioni che ci fornisce, nonché i diritti concessi o riconosciuti nella presente Informativa sulla privacy (collettivamente, “Informazioni trasferite”) a un potenziale o effettivo acquirente o acquirente della nostra società o altro successore allo scopo di valutare o eseguire una fusione, cessione, ristrutturazione, riorganizzazione, dissoluzione, cambiamento nel controllo, o trasferimento di alcune o di tutte le nostre attività (ciascuno dei precedenti indicato come “Cessione”), sia nel corso dell'attività che come parte del fallimento, liquidazione o altro procedimento giudiziario, in cui i dati personali da noi detenuti sono tra i beni trasferiti, e l’utente accetta di non opporsi a tale divulgazione e/o trasferimento. Non possiamo rilasciare alcuna dichiarazione in merito all’uso o al trasferimento delle Informazioni trasferite che potremmo avere in caso di fallimento, riorganizzazione, insolvenza, amministrazione controllata o cessione a beneficio dei creditori. Inoltre, salvo quanto richiesto dalla legge, non siamo e non saremo responsabili per alcuna violazione della sicurezza da parte di terze parti o per qualsiasi azione di terze parti che ricevono qualsiasi Informazione trasferita che ci viene divulgata.

3.5 DIVULGAZIONI RICHIESTE; PROTEZIONE DEI DIRITTI; SICUREZZA
-------------------------------------------------------------

Salvo quanto diversamente descritto nella presente Informativa sulla privacy, non divulgheremo dati personali dell’utente a parti non affiliate, a meno che non sia richiesto dalla legge, da un’ordinanza di un tribunale, procedimento legale (ad es. citazione), tra cui, ma non solo, per rispondere a qualsiasi richiesta governativa, regolatoria o di licenza, o se riteniamo che tale azione sia necessaria per: (a) rispettare la legge, rispettare i procedimenti legali notificati a noi o alle nostre affiliate, controllate, fornitori a contratto, o partner commerciali, o indagare, prevenire, o intraprendere azioni in merito ad attività illecite sospette o effettive; (b) far rispettare i nostri Termini o il contratto con il cliente (anche ai fini della fatturazione e della riscossione); (c) adottare precauzioni contro la responsabilità; (d) indagare e difenderci da eventuali rivendicazioni o accuse di terzi; (e) assistere le forze dell’ordine governative o soddisfare requisiti di sicurezza nazionali o di altro tipo; (f) proteggere la sicurezza o l’integrità dei nostri Siti web, il nostro, Servizi, e applicazioni mobili; o, (g) esercitare o proteggere i diritti, proprietà, o la nostra sicurezza personale, i nostri utenti o altri. 

Cercheremo di notificare all’utente, ove possibile, tali richieste a meno che: (i) la comunicazione sia vietata dal processo legale stesso, dall’ordinanza del tribunale che riceviamo o dalla legge applicabile, o (ii) riteniamo che la comunicazione sarebbe futile, inefficace, crei un rischio di lesioni o danni fisici o di altro tipo a un individuo o gruppo, o crei o aumenti un rischio di frode per noi, i nostri utenti, i nostri Siti web, Servizi o applicazioni mobili. Nei casi in cui rispettiamo le richieste legali senza preavviso per questi motivi, cercheremo di informare l’utente della richiesta dopo aver accertato in buona fede che non siamo più legalmente vietati di farlo e che non si applicano scenari di rischio descritti in questo paragrafo.

3.6 DIVULGAZIONE DI DATI PERSONALI DE-IDENTIFICATI
--------------------------------------------------

Possiamo condividere i Dati personali deidentificati (inclusi, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, dati di utilizzo anonimi, pagine e URL di riferimento/uscita, indirizzo IP, tipi di piattaforma, numero di clic, ecc.) con parti non affiliate in qualsiasi modo che scegliamo e per qualsiasi scopo, ad esempio per l’amministrazione del sistema e per monitorare l’utilizzo dei Siti web; per misurare il numero di visite ai nostri Siti web, il tempo medio trascorso, il numero di pagine visualizzate; e monitorare varie altre statistiche del Sito web per migliorare il contenuto.

4\.  RICHIESTE “DO NOT TRACK”
=============================

Alcuni browser web (tra cui Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox e Chrome) incorporano una funzione “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) o simile che segnala ai siti web che un utente non desidera che la propria attività e il proprio comportamento online siano monitorati. Se un sito web che risponde a un particolare segnale DNT riceve il segnale DNT, il browser può impedire a tale sito web di raccogliere determinate informazioni sull’utente del browser. Non tutti i browser offrono un'opzione DNT e i segnali DNT non sono ancora uniformi. Per questo motivo, molti operatori di siti web, tra cui PlugShare, non rispondono ai segnali DNT.

5\. COMUNICAZIONI, PREFERENZE E DISATTIVAZIONE PLUG-SHARE
=========================================================

Fornendoci il proprio indirizzo e-mail, l’utente acconsente all’utilizzo da parte nostra dell’indirizzo e-mail per inviargli avvisi relativi al Servizio, inclusi, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, eventuali avvisi richiesti dalla legge (ad es., avviso relativo alla privacy dei dati o a incidenti di sicurezza), al posto della comunicazione via posta. L’utente accetta inoltre che possiamo inviargli notifiche di attività riguardanti i nostri Prodotti, Servizi, Siti web, le applicazioni mobili, i suoi dati personali o qualsiasi aspetto del nostro rapporto, all’indirizzo e-mail che ci fornisce, in conformità con le impostazioni sulla privacy applicabili. Possiamo utilizzare l’indirizzo e-mail dell’utente per inviargli altri messaggi o contenuti, come, a titolo esemplificativo ma non esaustivo, newsletter, aggiunte o modifiche alle funzioni del Servizio o offerte speciali. Se l’utente non desidera ricevere tali messaggi e-mail, può scegliere di non ricerverli facendo clic su Annulla iscrizione, ove disponibile. La disattivazione può impedire la ricezione di messaggi e-mail relativi ad aggiornamenti, miglioramenti, funzioni speciali, annunci o offerte. L’utente non può scegliere di non ricevere e-mail relative al Servizio. Se l’utente ha scelto di non fornirci un’e-mail o un altro indirizzo, potrebbe non ricevere le nostre e-mail relative al Servizio.

Attraverso la pagina delle impostazioni dell’account, l’utente può accedere e, in alcuni casi, modificare o eliminare determinate informazioni che ci ha fornito, come nome e password, indirizzo e-mail, indirizzo, informazioni del profilo utente, ecc. Le informazioni che l’utente può visualizzare, aggiornare ed eliminare possono cambiare man mano che i Prodotti, i Siti web, i Servizi o le nostre pratiche cambiano. In caso di domande sulla visualizzazione o l’aggiornamento delle informazioni che abbiamo in archivio, l’utente è pregato di contattarci. Quando l’utente aggiorna le informazioni, tuttavia, possiamo conservare una copia delle informazioni non aggiornate nei nostri archivi. L'utente può richiedere la cancellazione del proprio account inviando un'e-mail. È responsabilità dell'utente mantenere il proprio indirizzo e-mail aggiornato con noi. A seconda dello stato o del Paese di residenza dell’utente potrebbero essere concessi diritti aggiuntivi. Per ulteriori informazioni, si veda di seguito.

6\. SVILUPPATORI CHE UTILIZZANO SERVIZI DI PIATTAFORMA PLUG-SHARE
=================================================================

Collaboriamo con e consentiamo a terze parti di utilizzare la piattaforma per sviluppatori di PlugShare per offrire servizi e funzionalità in combinazione con PlugShare. Questi sviluppatori terzi hanno negoziato un accordo per utilizzare la tecnologia della piattaforma PlugShare o hanno accettato le nostre interfacce di programmazione delle applicazioni self-service (Application Programming Interfaces, “API”) e i termini del plug-in al fine di creare applicazioni della piattaforma software (“Applicazioni della piattaforma”). Sia gli accordi negoziati che i nostri termini di utilizzo delle API e dei plug-in contengono restrizioni su come le terze parti possono accedere, archiviare e utilizzare i dati personali forniti a PlugShare. Se l’utente sceglie di utilizzare un’Applicazione della Piattaforma, gli sarà chiesto di confermare l’accettazione dell’informativa sulla privacy e del consenso dell’utente dello sviluppatore terzo. Per revocare l’autorizzazione concessa a un’Applicazione della piattaforma, l’utente deve visitare le sue impostazioni. Si noti, tuttavia, che anche se l'utente revoca l'autorizzazione concessa a un'applicazione della piattaforma, le sue connessioni possono continuare a utilizzare l'applicazione della piattaforma, la quale può continuare ad avere accesso a determinate informazioni sull'utente, proprio come le sue connessioni.

7\. CONSERVAZIONE DEI DATI PERSONALI
====================================

Il periodo di tempo per il quale conserviamo i dati personali dell’utente dipende dalle finalità per cui li utilizziamo. Conserveremo i dati personali dell'utente per tutto il tempo in cui il suo account sarà attivo, o per tutto il tempo in cui l'utente sarà un titolare di account registrato o un utente dei nostri Servizi o per tutto il tempo in cui avremo un altro scopo commerciale per farlo (ad esempio, ma non solo, per scopi commerciali, fiscali o legali) e, successivamente, per un periodo non superiore a quello richiesto o consentito dalla legge, o dalla nostra politica di conservazione dei dati, ragionevolmente necessario per scopi di reporting interno e riconciliazione, o per fornire all'utente un feedback o informazioni che potrebbe richiedere. Tale periodo di conservazione è soggetto alla nostra revisione e modifica. Possiamo conservare i dati personali deidentificati per tutto il tempo che riteniamo opportuno.

Dopo la cessazione o la disattivazione dell’account utente, possiamo conservare le informazioni del profilo dell’utente e tutte le informazioni pubblicate nelle aree pubbliche dei Siti web. In seguito alla risoluzione o alla disattivazione dell’account utente, possiamo conservare i dati personali e altri dati dell’utente, ma li manterremo riservati in conformità ai Termini, alla presente Informativa sulla privacy e come richiesto dalla legge applicabile. Abbiamo il diritto di eliminare tutti i dati personali e altri dati dell’utente dopo la cancellazione del suo account utente senza preavviso.

8\. NESSUNA RACCOLTA INTENZIONALE DI DATI DI MINORI
===================================================

Non raccogliamo, sollecitiamo o conserviamo consapevolmente dati personali da persone di età inferiore ai 18 anni né consentiamo consapevolmente a tali persone di registrarsi o utilizzare i nostri Servizi. Se l’utente ha meno di 18 anni dii età, non deve inviarci alcun dato personale. Nel caso in cui venissimo a conoscenza di aver raccolto dati personali da un minore di 18 anni senza la verifica del consenso dei genitori, compiremo ogni sforzo commercialmente ragionevole per eliminare tali informazioni dal nostro database.

9\. DOVE VENGONO TRATTATI E CONSERVATI I DATI PERSONALI; LEGGE APPLICABILE
==========================================================================

La nostra sede centrale è situata negli Stati Uniti. I dati personali che noi o i nostri Fornitori di servizi raccogliamo possono essere archiviati ed elaborati in server all’interno o all’esterno degli Stati Uniti e ovunque noi e i nostri Fornitori di servizi abbiamo strutture in tutto il mondo, e alcune informazioni possono essere accessibili a persone o società al di fuori degli Stati Uniti che ci forniscono servizi. L’utente acconsente alla trasmissione e/o al trasferimento da parte nostra e dei nostri Fornitori di servizi dei suoi dati personali a, o all’accesso ad esse in, giurisdizioni che potrebbero non fornire livelli di protezione dei dati equivalenti a quelli della sua giurisdizione di residenza. Adotteremo misure ragionevoli per garantire che i suoi dati personali ricevano un livello adeguato di protezione nelle giurisdizioni in cui li trattiamo.

Le leggi statunitensi si applicano nella misura in cui l’utente è residente negli Stati Uniti. In caso contrario, la presente Informativa sulla privacy e tutte le altre questioni saranno interpretate in conformità con le leggi della provincia/stato e federali della giurisdizione in cui risiede l’utente. Le giurisdizioni al di fuori della residenza dell’utente possono avere leggi sulla privacy diverse da quelle dell’utente, incluso il diritto delle forze dell’ordine e delle autorità governative di accedere ai dati personali.  Nella misura in cui trattiamo i dati al di fuori del Paese di residenza dell’utente, effettuiamo una valutazione dell’impatto sulla privacy per determinare che i nostri Fornitori di servizi possano offrire sostanzialmente lo stesso livello di protezione richiesto nella sua giurisdizione e stipulino contratti per rafforzare ulteriormente gli obblighi di trattamento appropriato dei suoi dati personali.

10\. SICUREZZA
==============

Abbiamo implementato misure di sicurezza tecniche e organizzative progettate per proteggere i dati personali da perdita accidentale e da accesso, uso, distruzione, alterazione e divulgazione non autorizzati. Tuttavia, si tenga presente che Internet non è un ambiente sicuro al 100%. È responsabilità dell'utente proteggere la sicurezza dei propri dati di accesso, prestare attenzione quando si trasmettono informazioni personali tramite e-mail, messaggistica istantanea e altri mezzi di comunicazione simili, e adottare buone pratiche di sicurezza su Internet. Non invieremo mai un’e-mail all’utente per chiedergli la password o altre informazioni di accesso al suo account. Se l’utente riceve un’e-mail simile, è pregato di inoltrarcela in modo da consentirci di indagare.

11\. DIRITTI AGGIUNTIVI DELL’INTERESSATO PER I RESIDENTI IN DETERMINATE GIURISDIZIONI DESCRITTI NELLE INFORMATIVE INTEGRATIVE SULLA PRIVACY
===========================================================================================================================================

Le seguenti disposizioni illustrano ogni diritto dell’interessato descritto nelle Informative integrative sulla privacy:

* diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy: l’utente ha il diritto di ricevere alcune informazioni richieste dalla legge in corrispondenza o prima del punto di raccolta o in risposta alla sua richiesta.
* Diritto alla cancellazione: l'utente può richiedere la cancellazione di qualsiasi dato personale che lo riguarda e che abbiamo raccolto da lui, fatte salve alcune eccezioni.
* Diritto di rettifica: l’utente può richiedere la rettifica di eventuali dati personali inesatte che conserviamo su di lui.
* Diritto di sapere: L’utente può richiedere che gli forniamo informazioni specifiche su come abbiamo gestito i suoi dati personali, tra cui la fornitura di una copia dei dati personali specifici che abbiamo raccolto su di lui in un formato portatile.
* Diritto alla non discriminazione: l’utente ha il diritto di non essere discriminato per aver esercitato i suoi diritti in qualità di interessato. Ciò significa non negare all’utente beni o servizi, addebitargli prezzi o tariffe diversi o fornire un livello di qualità differente per prodotti o servizi a seguito dell’esercizio dei suoi diritti di interessato.
* Diritti di rinuncia: l’utente può richiedere di rinunciare alla vendita e alla condivisione dei propri dati personali, alla pubblicità comportamentale o mirata in più contesti, al processo decisionale automatizzato o alla profilazione, nella misura in cui tali attività siano definite e limitate ai sensi delle leggi applicabili.
* Diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento: l’utente può richiederci di sopprimere o interrompere il trattamento di alcuni dei suoi dati personali, ma possiamo comunque archiviarli.  
* Diritto di limitare l’uso dei suoi dati personali sensibili: l’utente può richiedere di limitare l’uso dei propri dati personali sensibili solo alle finalità autorizzate dalle leggi applicabili.
* Diritto di presentare un reclamo: l’utente ha il diritto di presentare un reclamo all’autorità locale preposta alla protezione dei dati, se ritiene che il trattamento dei dati personali che lo riguardano violi i propri diritti.
* Diritto di revocare il consenso: nella misura in cui il nostro trattamento dei dati personali dell’utente si basa esclusivamente sul consenso dell’utente, l’utente può revocare tale consenso in qualsiasi momento.

12\. INFORMAZIONI DI CONTATTO
=============================

PlugShare ha designato un Responsabile della protezione dei dati come individuo che supervisionerà la conformità ai requisiti sulla privacy. Il Responsabile della protezione dei dati di PlugShare può essere contattato all’indirizzo riportato di seguito per qualsiasi problema relativo all’informativa sulla privacy.

In caso di domande o commenti sulla presente Informativa sulla privacy o sulle nostre pratiche sulla privacy, si prega di contattarci all’indirizzo: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 Stati Uniti; Attn: Responsabile della protezione dei dati; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

INFORMATIVA SULLA PRIVACY PER I RESIDENTI DI ALCUNI STATI DEGLI STATI UNITI
===========================================================================

Se l’utente è residente in California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah o Connecticut (occasionalmente indicato nel presente documento come “Consumatore”), le leggi statali gli concedono ulteriori diritti in merito al nostro utilizzo dei suoi dati personali.

LEGGE SHINE THE LIGHT DELLA CALIFORNIA
--------------------------------------

La Sezione 1798.83 del Codice civile della California, nota come legge “Shine The Light”, consente a qualsiasi utente residente in California di richiedere e ottenere da noi un elenco di quali dati personali (se presenti) abbiamo divulgato a terzi per scopi di marketing diretto nell’anno solare precedente e i nomi e gli indirizzi di tali terzi. Le richieste possono essere effettuate solo una volta all’anno e sono gratuite.

LEGGE SULLA PROTEZIONE DELLA PRIVACY ONLINE DELLA CALIFORNIA (“CALOPPA”; CALIF. BUS. E PROF. CODICE § 22575-22578, DISPONIBILE [QUI](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D))
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA si applica solo alle società che raccolgono dati personali dei residenti in California.

1. COME RISPONDIAMO AI SEGNALI “DO NOT TRACK”.

Alcuni browser web trasmettono segnali “do not track” (DNT/GPC) ai siti web e ad altri servizi on-line con cui il browser web comunica. Al momento non esiste uno standard che disciplini le azioni che i siti web devono intraprendere quando ricevono questi segnali; tuttavia, attualmente disponiamo di misure per intervenire in risposta a questi segnali.

2. MONITORAGGIO COMPORTAMENTALE DI TERZE PARTI

Possiamo anche utilizzare queste tecnologie per raccogliere informazioni sulle attività online dell’utente nel tempo e su siti web di terze parti o altri servizi online, o associare i dati personali dell’utente ad altre informazioni raccolte in questo modo. Possiamo utilizzare i dati personali per tracciare i modelli di navigazione e clic degli utenti.

CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT DEL 2018 (“CCPA”, DISPONIBILE [QUI](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) E IL SUO SUCCESSORE, IL CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT DEL 2020 (“CPRA”, DISPONIBILE [QUI](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)). 
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

La tabella seguente descrive in dettaglio come divulghiamo i dati personali che abbiamo raccolto sull’utente:

| Categoria | Categorie di terze parti a cui divulghiamo dati personali | Categorie di terze parti a cui vendiamo o con cui condividiamo dati personali |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificativi | Fornitori di archiviazione o di hosting dei dati<br><br>Fornitori di servizi di gestione delle identità<br><br>Fornitori di soluzioni di pagamento<br><br>Fornitori di sondaggi e ricerche<br><br>Partner pubblicitari, compresi i fornitori di social media | n/a |
| Dati demografici | Fornitori di sondaggi e ricerche | n/a |
| Informazioni commerciali | n/a | n/a |
| Attività in Internet o altra rete elettronica; informazioni sul dispositivo | Fornitori di archiviazione o di hosting dei dati<br><br>Fornitori di servizi di database e software<br><br>Fornitori di servizi di gestione delle identità<br><br>Partner pubblicitari, compresi i fornitori di social media | n/a |
| Geolocalizzazione | Fornitori di archiviazione o di hosting dei dati<br><br>Fornitori di servizi di database e software<br><br>Partner pubblicitari, compresi i fornitori di social media | n/a |
| Altro | Fornitori di archiviazione o di hosting dei dati<br><br>Fornitori di servizi di database e software<br><br>Fornitori di sondaggi e ricerche<br><br>Partner pubblicitari, compresi i fornitori di social media | Produttori, rivenditori e grossisti |

L’utente può contattarci per esercitare i seguenti diritti ai sensi del CCPA e del CPRA (per le descrizioni di tali diritti, vedere la sezione 11 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale):

1. Diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy.
2. Diritto di sapere quanto segue:

* le categorie di dati personali che abbiamo raccolto sull’utente.
* Le categorie di fonti dei dati personali che abbiamo raccolto sull’utente.
* Il nostro scopo commerciale o aziendale per la raccolta di tali dati personali.
* Le categorie di terze parti con cui condividiamo tali dati personali.
* I dati personali specifici che abbiamo raccolto sull’utente (chiamata anche richiesta di portabilità dei dati) e la trasmissione di una copia in formato elettronico o cartaceo.
* Se abbiamo divulgato i suoi dati personali per uno scopo commerciale, un elenco delle divulgazioni per uno scopo commerciale, identificando le categorie di dati personali che ciascuna categoria di destinatari ha ottenuto.

3. Diritto alla cancellazione.
4. Diritto di rettifica.
5. Diritto di rinunciare alla pubblicità comportamentale intercontestuale, alla vendita o alla condivisione di dati personali, al trattamento di dati personali per la profilazione e al processo decisionale automatizzato.
6. Diritto di limitare l’uso dei dati personali sensibili dell’utente. Si noti che non utilizziamo i dati personali sensibili dell’utente per scopi non autorizzati dal CCPA e dal CPRA.

LEGGE SULLA PROTEZIONE DEI DATI DEI CONSUMATORI DELLA VIRGINIA (VCDPA), LEGGE SULLA PRIVACY DEL COLORADO (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), LEGGE SULLA PRIVACY DEI CONSUMATORI DELLO UTAH (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2), E LEGGE SULLA PRIVACY DEI DATI DEL CONNECTICUT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

L’utente può contattarci per esercitare i seguenti diritti ai sensi di queste leggi specifiche dello stato:

1. Diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy.
2. Diritto di sapere.
3. Diritto alla cancellazione.
4. Diritto di rettifica.
5. Diritto di rinunciare alla pubblicità mirata o la vendita di dati personali.
6. Diritto di rinunciare alla profilazione (trattamento automatizzato dei dati personali allo scopo di analizzare o prevedere le caratteristiche o il comportamento futuro di un individuo, con conseguenti decisioni che incidono sui diritti sostanziali di una persona).  
7. I consumatori di Virginia, Colorado e Connecticut hanno anche il diritto di fare ricorso contro le nostre decisioni sulle loro richieste di interessati contattandoci tramite lo stesso metodo per inviare una richiesta. Si prega di allegare una copia o un altro riferimento specifico alla nostra decisione sulla richiesta dell'interessato, in modo da poter rispondere adeguatamente al ricorso. Risponderemo al ricorso dell’utente in conformità con la legge applicabile.

NEVADA
------

Come descritto in precedenza, potremmo vendere gli identificativi dell'utente o altre informazioni di identificazione raccolte dai nostri Siti web e Servizi online a parti non affiliate per scopi di tracciamento del comportamento trasversale ai sensi della legge del Nevada. L’utente ha il diritto di rinunciare alla vendita o alla concessione in licenza di tali categorie di dati personali a terze parti.

ESERCIZIO DEI DIRITTI
---------------------

Per esercitare i diritti di accesso, correzione, portabilità dei dati e cancellazione sopra descritti, è possibile inviarci una richiesta utilizzando il nostro modulo web disponibile [q](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form)[ui](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Solo l’utente o una persona autorizzata ad agire per suo conto può presentare una richiesta relativa ai suoi dati personali. L’utente può anche presentare una richiesta per conto di suo/a figlio/a minorenne. Se riceviamo una richiesta da parte di una persona per l’esercizio di un diritto per conto dell’utente, richiederemo una copia del permesso firmato rilasciato dall’utente che autorizza a presentare tali richieste per suo conto e lo contatteremo per una conferma diretta di tale autorizzazione. L’utente può effettuare una richiesta di accesso o portabilità dei dati solo due volte entro un periodo di 12 mesi. La richiesta verificabile del Consumatore deve:

* fornire informazioni sufficienti che ci consentano di verificare ragionevolmente che l’utente sia la persona di cui abbiamo raccolto i dati personali o che un rappresentante autorizzato abbia fatto la richiesta.
* Descrivere la richiesta dell’utente con dettagli sufficienti che ci consentano di comprenderla, valutarla e rispondervi correttamente.

Non possiamo rispondere alla richiesta dell’utente o fornirgli dati personali se non possiamo verificare la sua identità o autorità per effettuare la richiesta e confermare che i dati personali si riferiscono a lui. Effettuare una richiesta non richiede la creazione di un account con noi. Utilizzeremo i dati personali forniti in una richiesta solo per verificare l’identità o l’autorità del richiedente per effettuare la stessa.

Per esercitare il diritto di rinunciare alla pubblicità comportamentale intercontestuale, la pubblicità mirata o la condivisione dei dati personali come sopra descritto, l’utente dovrà operare tale rinuncia in base alla piattaforma su cui si trova.  Si noti che la richiesta di rinuncia è specifica per il dispositivo e la piattaforma in cui viene presentata, quindi potrebbe essere necessario presentare più richieste se si intende rinunciare a queste attività di trattamento specifiche per più dispositivi e piattaforme. Fare clic:

* qui per rinunciare a Plugshare.com (piattaforma web)
* qui per rinunciare all’app Plugshare per iOS
* qui per rinunciare all’app Android Plugshare

### Processo di verifica

Una volta ricevuta una richiesta di accesso, correzione, portabilità o cancellazione dei dati da parte dell’utente, gli invieremo un messaggio di posta elettronica entro 10 giorni lavorativi all'indirizzo di posta elettronica che abbiamo in archivio. L’e-mail chiederà all’utente di rispondere per verificare che sia il Cliente che effettua la richiesta. Al ricevimento della verifica, abbineremo le informazioni dell’utente a quelle contenute nel nostro archivio. Una volta verificata l'identità dell'utente, procederemo all'elaborazione della richiesta e risponderemo entro 45 giorni di calendario, a meno che (a) non siamo in grado di verificare la richiesta, (b) non siamo in grado di abbinare l'utente alle informazioni presenti nel nostro database, o (c) esiste un'eccezione prevista dalla legge che ci esenta dal soddisfare la richiesta. Se abbiamo bisogno di più tempo (fino a quarantacinque (45) giorni di calendario aggiuntivi), informeremo l’utente per iscritto del motivo e del periodo di estensione.

Se non siamo in grado di soddisfare la richiesta dell’utente, la risposta che gli forniremo ne spiegherà i motivi. Per le richieste di portabilità dei dati, selezioneremo un formato per fornire i dati personali dell’utente che sia prontamente utilizzabile e che consenta di trasmettere le informazioni da un’entità a un’altra senza ostacoli.

Non addebitiamo alcuna commissione per elaborare o rispondere alla richiesta verificabile del Cliente, a meno che non sia eccessiva, ripetitiva o manifestamente infondata. Se stabiliamo che la richiesta richiede una commissione, spiegheremo perché abbiamo preso tale decisione e forniremo all’utente una stima dei costi prima di completare la sua richiesta.

* * *

INFORMATIVE SULLA PRIVACY PER ALCUNI PAESI NON STATUNITENSI
===========================================================

INFORMAZIONI GENERALI
---------------------

1. ### IL CONSENSO SPECIFICO DELL’UTENTE AL TRATTAMENTO DI CATEGORIE “SENSIBILI” O “SPECIALI” DI DATI PERSONALI

Ai sensi delle leggi sulla privacy di alcuni Paesi, alcune tipologie di dati personali sono considerati categorie di informazioni “sensibili” o “speciali”. Raramente trattiamo dati sensibili o categorie speciali, a meno che non si tratti di interessi vitali dell'utente o di un'altra persona. Per tutte le altre circostanze, l'utente acconsente specificamente alla raccolta, al trattamento e alla conservazione da parte nostra di categorie sensibili o speciali di dati personali come descritto nella sezione 1.2 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale e acconsente altrimenti al trattamento di dati personali in conformità con la presente Informativa sulla privacy.  

2. ### LE NOSTRE BASI GIURIDICHE PER IL TRATTAMENTO DEI DATI PERSONALI

Le nostre basi giuridiche per la raccolta e l’utilizzo dei dati personali sopra descritti dipenderanno dalla tipologia di dati interessati e dal contesto specifico in cui li raccogliamo. In generale, raccoglieremo e tratteremo i dati personali dell’utente solo laddove abbiamo bisogno degli stessi per eseguire i Servizi per i quali l’utente ha stipulato un contratto con noi, o qualora il trattamento sia nei nostri legittimi interessi e non prevalga sui suoi interessi di protezione dei dati o sui suoi diritti e libertà fondamentali, faremo affidamento sul consenso dell’utente, laddove siamo legalmente tenuti a farlo. In alcuni casi, potremmo anche avere l’obbligo legale di raccogliere dati personali dall’utente o potremmo altrimenti aver bisogno dei suoi dati personali per proteggere i suoi interessi vitali o quelli di un’altra persona.

BASE GIURIDICA DEL LEGITTIMO INTERESSE PER LA RACCOLTA DI DATI PERSONALI: La raccolta e il trattamento dei dati personali dell’utente possono essere necessari ai fini dei nostri legittimi interessi. Tali scopi di interesse legittimo possono includere:

* prevenire frodi
* garantire la sicurezza della rete e delle informazioni
* indicare possibili atti criminali o minacce alla sicurezza pubblica, incluso il miglioramento della protezione della nostra comunità contro spam, molestie, violazione della proprietà intellettuale, crimine e rischi per la sicurezza di qualsiasi tipo, e far valere rivendicazioni legali, compresa l’indagine su potenziali violazioni dei nostri Termini di utilizzo
* adempiere ad obblighi legali
* elaborare dati di dipendenti o visitatori, membri, partecipanti o iscritti
* eseguire la funzione o il servizio richiesto dall’utente
* fornire i nostri Servizi e la loro funzionalità all’utente, laddove tale trattamento sia necessario ai fini dei legittimi interessi perseguiti da noi o dai nostri fornitori in relazione ai Servizi
* marketing diretto
* il rapporto pertinente e appropriato che abbiamo con l’utente
* analisi, ad es. valutare il numero di visitatori, le visualizzazioni delle pagine, l’uso dei Siti web, ecc., al fine di comprendere come vengono utilizzati i nostri Siti, Prodotti e Servizi, ottimizzare i Siti e/o le comunicazioni future e sviluppare nuovi servizi e funzionalità dei Siti
* aggiornare le informazioni e preferenze dell’utente
* offrire e migliorare i nostri Siti web, Prodotti e Servizi
* far valere rivendicazioni legali, compresa l’indagine su potenziali violazioni dei nostri Termini

Oltre alle informazioni fornite sopra, le seguenti sezioni si applicano solo ai residenti o ai cittadini del Paese o della regione discussi. Ai fini delle seguenti sezioni, se non specificamente menzionato, la definizione di “dati personali” come sopra utilizzata avrà il significato di informazioni personali, dati personali o termini simili, come applicabile ai sensi delle leggi sulla privacy dei dati di quel Paese o regione. In caso di conflitto tra le sezioni precedenti e quelle di seguito, queste ultime prevarranno.

GDPR – INFORMATIVA SULLA PRIVACY PER I RESIDENTI DELLO SPAZIO ECONOMICO EUROPEO (SEE), DEL REGNO UNITO E DELLA SVIZZERA
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### PANORAMICA

Le seguenti disposizioni si applicano solo se l’utente è residente nel SEE, nel Regno Unito o in Svizzera (indicati nella presente sezione per comodità come la “Regione UE”).

Per tali residenti, tutti i trattamenti dei loro dati personali avvengono nel rispetto dei diritti e delle normative sulla privacy, in particolare il Regolamento (UE) 2016/679 del Parlamento europeo e del Consiglio del 27 aprile 2016, noto come Regolamento generale sulla protezione dei dati o il Regolamento generale sulla protezione dei dati del Regno Unito per i residenti di tale paese (collettivamente, "GDPR"), e il nostro trattamento avverrà in conformità con il GDPR. Ai fini del GDPR, noi saremo il “titolare del trattamento” delle informazioni personali (indicati e definiti nel GDPR (disponibile [qui](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/-OIcjXVNa2lpkHu)) come “dati personali”) che raccogliamo, a meno che non raccogliamo tali informazioni per conto di un “titolare del trattamento”, nel qual caso saremo un “responsabile del trattamento”. La presente Informativa sulla privacy non si applica a siti web, applicazioni o servizi che non visualizzano o non rimandano alla presente informativa o che visualizzano o rimandano a un'informativa sulla privacy distinta. Solo per i residenti e i cittadini della Regione UE, nella misura in cui qualsiasi definizione nella presente Informativa sulla privacy sia in conflitto con una definizione ai sensi del GDPR, prevarrà la definizione del GDPR.

Forniamo un’adeguata protezione per il trasferimento dei dati personali in Paesi al di fuori della Regione UE tramite uno o più dei seguenti metodi: (a) una serie di accordi interaziendali basati su o che incorporano le Clausole contrattuali tipo, (b) possiamo fare affidamento sulle decisioni di adeguatezza della Commissione europea su alcuni Paesi, come applicabile, (c) possiamo ottenere il consenso dell’utente per questi trasferimenti di dati dalla Regione UE agli Stati Uniti ad altri Paesi, (d) possiamo adottare norme vincolanti d'impresa, o (e) nella misura applicabile, possiamo fare affidamento su deroghe come stabilito nell’articolo 49 del GDPR per il trasferimento e il successivo trasferimento di dati personali raccolti da individui nella Regione UE negli Stati Uniti e in altri Paesi che la Regione UE ritiene non fornire un’adeguata protezione dei dati. Per quanto riguarda il metodo (e), possiamo trasferire dati personali a terzi per eseguire un contratto con l’utente, con il suo esplicito consenso o in un modo che non prevalga sui suoi diritti e libertà. Se questi dati personali non vengono trattati e trasferiti, non saremo in grado di stipulare il contratto con l’utente o l’utente non avrà accesso a nessuno o a tutti i benefici e le funzionalità associati alla propria transazione.

Potremmo anche dover trasferire le informazioni dell’utente ad altre società del gruppo o fornitori di servizi in Paesi al di fuori della regione UE. Ciò può accadere se i nostri server o fornitori e fornitori di servizi hanno sede al di fuori della regione UE, o se l’utente utilizza i nostri Prodotti e/o Servizi mentre visita Paesi al di fuori di queste aree.

Le nostre basi giuridiche per la raccolta dei dati personali dell’utente sono illustrate nella sezione .

2. ### I DIRITTI SUI DATI DELL’UTENTE AI SENSI DEL GDPR.

Se l’utente è soggetto al GDPR, i suoi diritti includono i seguenti:

* diritto di sapere.
* Diritto di rettifica.
* Diritto alla cancellazione.
* Diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento. L'utente ha il diritto di opporsi ai seguenti utilizzi dei propri dati personali: (a) trattamento basato su legittimi interessi o sull'esecuzione di un compito di interesse pubblico/esercizio di pubblici poteri (compresa la profilazione); (b) marketing diretto (compresa la profilazione); e (c) trattamento a fini di ricerca scientifica/storica e statistica. Si veda di seguito per maggiori informazioni.
* Diritto di rinuncia. L’utente ha il diritto di non essere soggetto a una decisione basata esclusivamente sul trattamento automatizzato, compresa la profilazione, che produca effetti legali che lo riguardano o che influisca in modo analogo in modo significativo sull’utente, fatte salve le eccezioni applicabili ai sensi delle leggi sulla protezione dei dati pertinenti.
* Diritto di presentare un reclamo. Se l’utente risiede all’interno del SEE, un elenco delle Autorità nazionali per la protezione dei dati è disponibile [qui](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Se risiede nel Regno Unito, può contattare l’Ufficio del Commissario per le informazioni [qui.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Diritto di revocare il consenso.

AVVISI AI RESIDENTI IN ALTRI PAESI (AL DI FUORI DEGLI STATI UNITI)
------------------------------------------------------------------

Quanto segue in questa Sezione è in aggiunta alle informazioni presentate nella nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale.

Rispetteremo i seguenti diritti degli interessati per tutti i residenti al di fuori degli Stati Uniti:

* diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche in materia di privacy:

* La nostra identità e le informazioni di contatto,
* Lo scopo specifico del nostro trattamento dei dati personali dell’utente,
* La forma e la durata del trattamento dei dati personali dell’utente,
* Le informazioni sulla nostra condivisione e sullo scopo della condivisione dei dati personali dell’utente,
* Le responsabilità di eventuali terze parti che trattano i dati personali dell’utente, e,
* Le informazioni relative a qualsiasi entità legale pubblica e privata con cui abbiamo condiviso i dati personali dell’utente.  

* Diritto di sapere:

* Le decisioni prese esclusivamente sulla base del trattamento automatizzato di dati personali.
* L’accesso alle informazioni sui dati personali che raccogliamo.  

* Diritto di rettifica.
* Diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento.
* Diritto di revocare il consenso.

Qualsiasi traduzione della presente Informativa sulla privacy in una lingua diversa dall’inglese è fornita esclusivamente a scopo informativo. In caso di discrepanze, l’unica versione legalmente valida e vincolante sarà la versione inglese del presente documento.

1. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI IN ARGENTINA

Le misure di sicurezza tecniche e organizzative implementate da PlugShare supporterebbero anche le norme della legge argentina sulla protezione dei dati personali (PDPA) 25.326, come il divieto di qualsiasi uso secondario dei dati personali di un interessato e il divieto di trasferire i dati personali in paesi che non offrono un livello di protezione adeguato. PlugShare utilizza un accordo sul trasferimento/trattamento dei dati per contribuire alla conformità con la disposizione PDPA 60-E/2016, che regola il trasferimento transfrontaliero di dati personali.

I residenti in Argentina hanno (a) il diritto di conoscere l’esistenza e lo scopo di tali dati personali, e (b) il diritto di rettifica e il diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento dei loro dati personali se sono falsi, inaccurati o discriminatori.

2. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI IN AUSTRALIA

Possiamo utilizzare e divulgare i dati personali dell'utente (come definiti dalla legge australiana) a terzi con sede al di fuori dell'Australia, principalmente negli Stati Uniti, come descritto nella sezione 9 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale. L’utente accetta e riconosce che i destinatari esteri saranno soggetti alla legge sulla privacy della loro giurisdizione locale e non possono essere soggetti ad alcun obbligo sulla privacy o a principi simili ai Principi sulla privacy australiani. Essi saranno inoltre soggetti a una legge straniera che potrebbe obbligare la divulgazione di dati personali a terzi, come un’autorità estera. A meno che l’utente non ci comunichi per iscritto il contrario, sarà tenuto ad acconsentire alla divulgazione da parte nostra di dati personali a destinatari esteri. L’utente ha la possibilità di rimanere anonimo quando tratta con noi o di non divulgarci determinati dati personali. Tuttavia, ciò può significare che potremmo non essere in grado di fornire i nostri Servizi all’utente.

Per i residenti in Australia, gli aggiornamenti alla presente Informativa sulla privacy sono efficaci, se otteniamo il consenso esplicito dell’utente o se forniamo un’opzione di rinuncia quando vengono annunciate modifiche sostanziali (ad es., sui nostri Siti web o via e-mail).

3. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI IN BRASILE

I residenti in Brasile hanno il diritto di conoscere le seguenti informazioni: se la trasmissione a noi dei loro dati personali è un requisito contrattuale, o se vi sono conseguenze nel non fornire tali dati (la risposta è no a entrambi), informazioni relative a qualsiasi processo decisionale automatizzato (inclusa la profilazione) che eseguiamo (si veda la sezione 2.1 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale). L’utente ha il diritto di revocare il consenso al trattamento dei suoi dati personali, e, i diritti di accesso dell’interessato (si veda di seguito).

I residenti in Brasile sono titolari dei seguenti diritti: (a) il diritto di sapere se trattiamo loro dati personali, incluso quello di ottenere una copia di tali informazioni; (b) il diritto di rettifica; (c) il diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento; (d) il diritto di cancellazione; (e) il diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy relative alle entità pubbliche e private con cui i dati personali sono stati condivisi; e (f) il diritto di presentare un reclamo all’autorità di controllo dei dati brasiliana (ANPD).

4. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI IN CANADA (INCLUSO IL QUEBEC)

La nostra Informativa sulla privacy e le nostre pratiche generali sono concepite per rispettare le leggi canadesi sulla privacy, tra cui il Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) e, ove applicabile, la legge sulla privacy del settore privato del Quebec, denominata Protezione delle dati personali nel settore privato (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Per qualsiasi pratica di gestione delle informazioni che non sia ragionevolmente correlata agli scopi per cui l’utente ha contattato PlugShare, l’utente ha il diritto di rinunciare a tali pratiche (tra cui marketing, profilazione, pubblicità comportamentale, condivisione con una terza parte che non è un fornitore di servizi).  

I residenti canadesi hanno il diritto di rifiutare il nostro utilizzo dei loro dati personali per scopi di marketing diretto e altri trattamenti che non sono ragionevolmente necessari per rispondere a ciò per cui ci hanno contattato.

5. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI A HONG KONG

Utilizziamo i dati personali dell’utente per i seguenti scopi di marketing diretto: (a) per comunicare con l’utente in merito ai nostri prodotti e servizi e (b) per inviargli ulteriori avvisi, promozioni o altri materiali di marketing riguardanti i nostri Siti web, Prodotti e Servizi e quelli delle nostre affiliate. Il consenso dell’utente a tale scopo sarà richiesto al momento dell’invio dei dati personali a noi (ad es., alla creazione dell’account, alla registrazione dell’evento, ecc.).

6. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI IN MESSICO

Oltre alle informazioni presentate sopra, i residenti in Messico hanno il diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy, incluso (a) se la fornitura a noi dei loro dati personali è un requisito contrattuale o se vi sono conseguenze nel non fornire tali dati (la risposta è no a entrambe), (b) informazioni riguardanti qualsiasi processo decisionale automatizzato (inclusa la profilazione) che eseguiamo (che è discusso nella sezione 2.1 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale), (c) per quanto tempo vengono conservati i dati (vedere la sezione 7 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale), (d) il diritto di revocare il consenso al trattamento dei loro dati personali, e, (e) i diritti di accesso dell’interessato (si veda di seguito). L'utente ha inoltre il diritto di conoscere l'indicazione esplicita dei dati personali sensibili che saranno oggetto di trattamento.

I residenti in Messico hanno inoltre: (a) il diritto di conoscere i dati personali che raccogliamo, incluso essere informati sulle entità pubbliche e private con cui gli stessi sono stati condivisi e ottenere una copia di tali informazioni; (b) il diritto di rettifica; (c) il diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento; e (d) il diritto di cancellazione.

7. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI A SINGAPORE

Tra gli altri diritti, se siamo presenti a Singapore, l’utente ha il diritto di far trasmettere i propri dati personali in nostro possesso a un’altra organizzazione.

Le persone o le società a cui divulghiamo e trasferiamo i dati personali dell’utente possono trovarsi al di fuori di Singapore. Ci assicureremo che i destinatari dei dati personali trasferiti siano in grado di garantire agli stessi uno standard di protezione paragonabile a quelli stabiliti dalla legge sulla privacy di Singapore tramite l’uso di accordi scritti sul trasferimento dei dati (per i trasferimenti a terzi) o tramite norme vincolanti d'impresa (per i trasferimenti alle nostre collegate e ad altre entità a noi correlate).

8. ### AVVISO AI RESIDENTI A TAIWAN

I residenti di Taiwan hanno il diritto di ricevere informazioni sulle pratiche sulla privacy.

I residenti di Taiwan hanno inoltre: (a) il diritto di conoscere i dati personali che raccogliamo, incluso essere informati sulle entità pubbliche e private con cui gli stessi sono stati condivisi e ottenere una copia di tali informazioni; (b) il diritto di rettifica; (c) il diritto di limitare o opporsi al trattamento; e (d) il diritto di cancellazione.

Oltre alle informazioni presentate sopra, i residenti a Taiwan hanno il diritto di conoscere talune informazioni riguardo ai dati personali che raccogliamo, incluso (a) se la fornitura a noi dei loro dati personali è un requisito contrattuale o se vi sono conseguenze nel non fornire tali dati (la risposta è no a entrambe), (b) informazioni riguardanti qualsiasi processo decisionale automatizzato (inclusa la profilazione) che eseguiamo (che è discusso nella sezione 2.1 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale), (c) per quanto tempo vengono conservati i dati (vedere la sezione 7 della nostra Informativa sulla privacy principale), (d) il diritto di revocare il consenso al trattamento dei loro dati personali, e, (e) i diritti di accesso dell’interessato (si veda di seguito). L'utente ha inoltre il diritto di conoscere l'indicazione esplicita dei dati personali sensibili che saranno oggetto di trattamento (non raccogliamo informazioni “sensibili”).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) Il Colorado Privacy Act entra in vigore il 1° luglio 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) Lo Utah Consumer Privacy Act entra in vigore il 31 dicembre 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) Il Connecticut Data Privacy Act entra in vigore il 1° luglio 2023.

PRIVACYBELEID PLUGSHARE
=======================

INGANGSDATUM: 10 juli 2023
--------------------------

PlugShare, LLC (“PlugShare” “wij”, “ons” of “onze”) heeft als doel het creëren van een ondersteunende gemeenschap van gebruikers van elektrische voertuigen (“EV”) en het leveren van toonaangevende oplaadinformatie en een breed scala aan innovatieve producten en diensten om de EV-rijervaring zo gemakkelijk en lonend mogelijk te maken. Dit Privacybeleid beschrijft ons beleid inzake de/het verzameling, gebruik, openbaarmaking, bewaring, en overdracht van de Persoonlijke informatie (hieronder gedefinieerd) die we over u verzamelen (“u” of “uw”) via onze interacties met u via onze Websites ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); of [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); gezamenlijk, “Websites”), overeenkomstige diensten en onze mobiele applicaties (gezamenlijk “Diensten”), evenals via interacties met niet-gelieerde partijen zoals onze leveranciers die met ons samenwerken om onze Diensten aan u te leveren.

Lees dit Privacybeleid zorgvuldig door. Als u niet wilt dat wij uw Persoonlijke informatie verwerken, geef ons dan geen informatie; het is echter mogelijk dat u dan niet kunt profiteren van bepaalde functies van onze Diensten.

Uw gebruik van de website en onze Diensten is te allen tijde ook onderworpen aan onze Gebruiksvoorwaarden (beschikbaar op [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) en zoals van tijd tot tijd bijgewerkt (de “Voorwaarden”)).

Dit Privacybeleid is niet van toepassing op niet-gelieerde websites of diensten gekoppeld aan of vanaf onze Websites of Diensten behalve op die van onze dienstverleners, op onze sociale-mediakanalen of -platforms die deze presenteren, of op enige website of dienst aanbevolen of waarnaar wordt verwezen door onze Websites of Diensten of door ons personeel.

Inwoners van Californië, Virginia, Colorado, Utah en Connecticut: Raadpleeg onze [Aanvullende privacyverklaring voor inwoners van bepaalde Amerikaanse staten](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) met betrekking tot aanvullende informatie over onze verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie.

Inwoners van andere landen: Als u inwoner bent van een ander land dan de Verenigde Staten, raadpleeg dan onze websitepagina Aanvullende privacyverklaringen voor bepaalde niet-Amerikaanse landen voor aanvullende informatie over onze verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie.

We werken voortdurend aan het verbeteren van onze Diensten en het kan zijn dat we dit Privacybeleid ook van tijd tot tijd moeten wijzigen. Ons huidige Privacybeleid staat altijd op onze Websites. Let op de ingangsdatum van dit Privacybeleid en controleer regelmatig of er herzieningen zijn.

1\. WELKE PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE WE VERZAMELEN
===============================================

1.1 WAT IS PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE
----------------------------------

Dit Privacybeleid dekt onze behandeling van uw persoonlijk identificeerbare informatie. “Persoonlijke informatie” betekent over het algemeen alle niet-gecodeerde informatie die uw naam, postadres, e-mailadres, telefoonnummer enz. identificeert, er betrekking op heeft, beschrijft, of er redelijkerwijs mee in verband kan worden gebracht, of redelijkerwijs kan worden gekoppeld aan een bepaalde persoon, zoals, maar niet beperkt tot, uw naam, postadres, e-mailadres, telefoonnummer enz.

Persoonlijke informatie omvat niet uw Persoonlijke informatie die is gedeïdentificeerd, geanonimiseerd of geaggregeerd op manieren die vereist zijn krachtens de toepasselijke wetgeving, zodat de informatie niet langer direct of via andere redelijkerwijs beschikbare middelen kan worden gebruikt om iemand te identificeren (gezamenlijk “Gedeïdentificeerde Persoonlijke informatie”).

1.2 CATEGORIEËN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE DIE WE VERZAMELEN EN VERWERKEN
----------------------------------------------------------------------

We verzamelen verschillende categorieën Persoonlijke informatie van en over u, zoals samengevat in de volgende tabel:

| Categorie | Specifieke onderdelen Persoonlijke informatie |
| --- | --- |
| Identificatoren | * voor- en achternaam<br>* gebruikersnaam (waaronder eventueel voor- en achternaam)<br>* e-mailadres<br>* postcode<br>* geslacht, gender<br>* unieke persoonlijke identificatiecode, bijv. klant- of accountnaam of -nummer, telefoonnummer, identificatiecode mobiel apparaat |
| Demografisch | * land van verblijf |
| Commerciële informatie | * aankoopgeschiedenis en tendensen inzake producten/diensten |
| Internet- of andere elektronische netwerkactiviteit; apparaatinformatie | * soort en fabrikant van het apparaat en de ID/UDID of een soortgelijke apparaatspecifieke code<br>* besturingssysteem en platform<br>* schermresolutie<br>* naam, verbindingssnelheid en soort verbinding van internetaanbieder of mobiele aanbieder<br>* Internet-protocol (of IP)-adres, protocol en sequentie-informatie<br>* cookies<br>* pixel tags<br>* Media Access Control (MAC)-adres van pagina’s die u hebt bezocht<br>* advertentie-identificator mobiel apparaat<br>* browsertype, -taal en -versie<br>* Website browsen, sessie, interactie en zoekgeschiedenis, materiaal en bekeken pagina’s, tijd en datum van toegang tot de Websites, aantal overgedragen bytes, aantal klikken per bezoek, tijd besteed op een pagina, doorklik- en klikstroomgegevens, gemaakte zoekopdrachten, geselecteerde zoekresultaten, gemaakte opmerkingen<br>* datumstempel en URL van de laatste webpagina die u hebt bezocht voordat u onze Websites hebt bezocht, en URL van de eerste pagina die u hebt bezocht nadat u onze Websites hebt verlaten<br>* soort aangevraagde dienst<br>* kopteksten van hypertekstoverdrachtprotocollen, toepassing klant- en serverbanners |
| Geolocatie | * fysieke locatie en/of bewegingen |
| Overig | * EV-oplaadgegevens, merk, model en jaar van het voertuig<br>* informatie die u vrijwillig verstrekt als onderdeel van een reactie op commentaar of andere algemene vraag die via onze Websites wordt gesteld<br>* conclusies die worden getrokken uit de vermelde informatie om een profiel te creëren over een consument dat de voorkeuren, kenmerken, psychologische tendensen, aanleg, gedrag, mentaliteit, intelligentie, capaciteiten of bekwaamheid van de consument weerspiegelt |

1.3 WAAR WE PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE VERZAMELEN
----------------------------------------------

We kunnen Persoonlijke informatie rechtstreeks van u verzamelen via onze Diensten wanneer u:

* Persoonlijke informatie aan ons verstrekt door webformulieren op onze Websites in te vullen of transacties uit te voeren in winkels (merken van moeder-, dochterondernemingen en gelieerde bedrijven). Dit omvat informatie die wordt verstrekt bij het aanmaken van een online account, het kopen van onze Diensten, het abonneren op onze e-nieuwsbrieven of andere communicatie, het opvragen van informatie bij ons, het indienen of plaatsen van materiaal (indien toegestaan) op onze forums, of het communiceren met klantenondersteuning of -dienst, het melden van een probleem met onze Websites, mobiele applicaties of Diensten, of het anderszins communiceren met ons.
* contact met ons opneemt. Dit omvat alle documenten en kopieën van uw correspondentie met ons, bijvoorbeeld met onze kantoren of klantendienst/-ondersteuning of het insturen van een cheque.
* zich aanmeldt voor een evenement of ons informeert over eventuele toegankelijkheids- of andere accommodatieverzoeken.
* reageert op enquêtes die wij of onze dienstverleners u kunnen vragen in te vullen voor onderzoeksdoeleinden.
* zoekopdrachten uitvoert op de Websites.
* deelneemt aan loyaliteits-/beloningsprogramma’s.
* solliciteert naar een baan.
* apparaten en netwerken gebruikt om toegang te krijgen tot onze Diensten, zoals het synchroniseren van uw EV met onze Diensten.
* bepaalde functies gebruikt op onze Websites en mobiele applicaties. Hoewel gebruikers toegang hebben tot beperkte functies zonder hun Persoonlijke informatie bekend te maken, zoals het browsen door openbare oplaadstations zonder een account, verzamelen we Persoonlijke informatie wanneer gebruikers een account registreren. Gebruikers kunnen ervoor kiezen om alleen hun e-mail en wachtwoord te gebruiken om thuisopladers te doorzoeken. Gebruikers kunnen er ook voor kiezen om te profiteren van de verbeterde mogelijkheden door aanvullende Persoonlijke informatie te plaatsen, te becommentariëren, te publiceren of door te geven aan de gemeenschap. Over het algemeen kiezen gebruikers hoeveel informatie ze over zichzelf willen weergeven en kunnen ze zich op elk moment afmelden.

We kunnen ook Persoonlijke informatie verzamelen van niet-gelieerde partijen, waaronder:

* gegevensleveranciers (bijv. bedrijven die demografische gegevens en andere informatie over consumenten verstrekken)
* op mobiele applicaties (merken van moeder- en dochterondernemingen en filialen)
* gezamenlijke marketingpartners
* online advertentiebedrijven of platforms (bijvoorbeeld als u vrijwillig uw sociale-mediaprofiel koppelt aan of verbindt met onze Diensten)
* dienstverleners voor uitvoering en levering
* sociale-mediabedrijven
* andere dienstverleners
* reageren op werkgelegenheidskansen
* acties op de website/het webformulier of de app van de gebruiker
* leveranciers van arbeidsverificatie of antecedentenonderzoek
* ons toestaan om via uw apparaatinstellingen of diensten van derden geolocatiegegevens te ontvangen om lokale informatie (bijvoorbeeld een lokaal oplaadstation) op onze mobiele toepassingen te tonen.

1.4 INFORMATIE VERZAMELD VIA GEAUTOMATISEERDE TECHNOLOGIEËN
-----------------------------------------------------------

Terwijl u door onze Diensten navigeert en ermee communiceert, kunnen we ook technologieën voor automatische gegevensverzameling gebruiken om bepaalde informatie van uw apparaat, browser of andere netwerkactiviteiten te verzamelen, zoals beschreven in ons Cookiebeleid, beschikbaar op [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Websitebezoek en apparaatinformatie. We verzamelen gegevens over uw bezoeken aan onze Websites en het gebruik van onze mobiele apps, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, verkeersgegevens, geolocatiegegevens, logboeken en andere communicatiegegevens en de hulpbronnen die u opent en gebruikt op de Websites. We verzamelen informatie over uw computer, mobiele apparaat en internetverbinding, waaronder uw IP-adres, besturingssysteem, soort browser, klikstroompatronen (d.w.z. waar u op klikt op een website), de URL van de meest recente website die u hebt bezocht voordat u naar onze Websites kwam, de hoeveelheid tijd die u op onze Websites hebt doorgebracht en de pagina’s die u op onze Websites hebt bekeken. We kunnen een ruwe schatting van uw locatie afleiden van uw IP-adres wanneer u onze Websites bezoekt. Voor gebruikers van onze mobiele apps kunnen we ook de geschiedenis van uw exacte locatiegegevens verzamelen en bijhouden met behulp van wifi- en/of Bluetooth-technologieën, evenals uw apparaat-ID’s en GPS-coördinaten (bijv. breedtegraad/lengtegraad). Als u het verzamelen van uw locatiegegevens wilt voorkomen, pas dan uw instellingen aan op uw mobiele apparaat om de toegang van de mobiele app tot uw locatiegegevens te beperken.

Wanneer u onze website gebruikt, delen we informatie die we van u verzamelen, zoals uw e-mail (in gehashte vorm), IP-adres of informatie over uw browser of besturingssysteem, met onze identiteitspartners/serviceproviders. Deze partners sturen een online identificatiecode terug die we kunnen opslaan in onze first-party cookie voor ons gebruik in online, in-app en cross-channel advertenties en deze kan worden gedeeld met advertentiebedrijven om op interesses gebaseerde en gerichte advertenties mogelijk te maken. Klik hier ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)) om u af te melden voor dit gebruik.

Gedragstracering. We kunnen deze technologieën ook gebruiken om informatie te verzamelen over uw online activiteiten in de loop der tijd en op websites van derden of andere online diensten, of om Persoonlijke informatie te koppelen aan andere informatie die op deze manier wordt verzameld.

Locatieanalyse: onze mobiele apps en mobiele browserwebsites bevatten functionaliteit (bijv. voor het indienen van een bestuurdersbeoordeling van een oplaadpunt) waarmee we de locatie van een bestuurder en de locatie van het oplaadpunt waar een gebruiker zich momenteel bevindt, kunnen vaststellen. We verzamelen informatie zoals IP-adres, apparaat-ID en geolocatie. Gebruikers van de mobiele app kunnen ervoor kiezen om de mobiele apps anoniem te gebruiken of om in te loggen als een geïdentificeerde gebruiker, in welk geval de persoonsgegevens die bij de registratie zijn verstrekt, kunnen worden gebruikt.

Voor gebruikers van de mobiele apps kunnen we toestemming vragen voor toegang tot bepaalde informatie vanaf uw mobiele apparaat, waaronder uw contactlijst, foto’s en video’s, en microfoon en camera. Het is optioneel dat u ons toegang geeft tot deze informatie. Bepaalde functies van de mobiele apps werken echter eventueel niet optimaal als u besluit om ons geen toestemming te geven.

Webbakens. Pagina’s van onze Websites en onze e-mails kunnen kleine elektronische bestanden bevatten die bekend staan als webbakens (ook wel ‘clear gifs’, ‘pixeltags’ en ‘single-pixel gifs’ genoemd) die ons bijvoorbeeld in staat stellen om gebruikers te tellen die deze pagina’s hebben bezocht of een e-mail hebben geopend en voor andere gerelateerde websitestatistieken (bijvoorbeeld het vastleggen van de populariteit van bepaalde website-inhoud en het verifiëren van de integriteit van het systeem en de server).

Pixels volgen. Naast het gebruik van cookies kunnen de Websites gebruikmaken van “pixels volgen”. Pixels volgen omvat het gebruik van pixeltags die niet zichtbaar zijn voor de gebruiker en bestaan uit een paar regels computercode. Pixels volgen meet de effectiviteit van advertenties en stelt geaggregeerde en specifieke gebruiksstatistieken samen. We kunnen toegang krijgen tot deze pixeltags om activiteiten en interesses te identificeren die ons in staat kunnen stellen onze Producten, Diensten en aanbiedingen beter af te stemmen op uw interesses en behoeften. Als u bijvoorbeeld onze Websites bezoekt vanuit een advertentie op een andere website, stelt de pixeltag de adverteerder in staat om bij te houden dat zijn advertentie u naar de Websites heeft gebracht. Als u onze Websites bezoekt en we u naar een andere website doorkoppelen, kunnen we eventueel ook vaststellen dat u bent gestuurd naar en/of transacties hebt uitgevoerd met een website van derden.

GIF (Graphics Interchange Format). We kunnen kleine afbeeldingen gebruiken die bekend staan als transparante GIF’s om het gedrag van gebruikers bij te houden, inclusief statistieken over wie onze e-mails opent.

IP-adres. Onze servers (of die van onze dienstverleners) registreren automatisch bepaalde logbestandinformatie die door uw browser wordt gerapporteerd wanneer u de Websites bezoekt. Deze serverlogboeken kunnen informatie bevatten zoals welke pagina’s van de Websites u hebt bezocht, uw internetprotocol (“IP”)-adres, soort browser en andere informatie over hoe u met de Websites omgaat. Deze logbestanden worden over het algemeen periodisch verwijderd.

Statistieken en analyses van derden. Statistieken en analyses van derden, op bepaalde pagina’s of functies van de Diensten voor meer inzicht in en analyse van het bezoekersverkeer en om de promotionele effectiviteit en werkzaamheid van onze functies, aanbiedingen en marketingcampagnes te meten. We gebruiken deze hulpmiddelen ook om valkuilen, tekortkomingen en gebieden van onze activiteiten vast te stellen die moeten worden verbeterd, en om de algemene prestaties en rangorde van onze online aanwezigheid te bekijken. Deze hulpmiddelen kunnen naar eigen goeddunken cookies op uw apparaat opslaan.

COOKIEVERKLARING EN -BELEID

De technologieën die we gebruiken voor automatische gegevensverzameling omvatten ook cookies, zoals hieronder beschreven.

Browsercookies

Browsercookies zijn kleine bestanden die op de harde schijf van uw computer of mobiele apparaat worden geplaatst. Ze kunnen bepaalde gegevens bevatten, waaronder, maar niet beperkt tot, de naam van de server die ze daar heeft geplaatst, een identificatie in de vorm van een uniek nummer en een vervaldatum (alleen sommige cookies). Browsercookies worden beheerd door de webbrowser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome enz.) op uw computer of mobiele apparaat. Op onze Websites worden verschillende soorten cookies gebruikt die verschillende doeleinden hebben.

Essentiële cookies

Essentiële cookies zijn essentieel om u in staat te stellen onze Websites te bezoeken en de functies ervan te gebruiken. Zonder deze cookies zouden diensten zoals winkelmandjes en elektronische facturering niet kunnen werken.

Prestatiecookies

Prestatiecookies verzamelen informatie over het gebruik van onze Websites, zoals welke pagina’s het vaakst worden geraadpleegd. Deze informatie stelt ons in staat om onze Websites te optimaliseren en het browsen (bladeren) te vereenvoudigen. Prestatiecookies stellen onze gelieerde ondernemingen en partners ook in staat om te weten te komen of u een van onze websitepagina’s hebt geopend vanaf hun website en of uw bezoek heeft geleid tot het gebruik of de aankoop van een product of dienst van onze Websites, inclusief de referenties voor het gekochte product of de gekochte dienst. Alle informatie die door prestatiecookies wordt verzameld, is samengevoegd en daarom anoniem.

Functionaliteitscookies

Functionaliteitscookies stellen onze Websites in staat om de keuzes te onthouden die u hebt gemaakt tijdens het browsen. We kunnen bijvoorbeeld uw geografische locatie opslaan in een cookie, zodat de Websites die overeenkomen met uw gebied worden weergegeven. We kunnen ook uw voorkeuren onthouden, zoals de tekstgrootte, het lettertype en andere aanpasbare aspecten van de Websites. Functionaliteitscookies kunnen ook de geraadpleegde producten of video’s bijhouden om herhaling te voorkomen. De informatie die door deze cookies wordt verzameld kan niet worden gebruikt om u te identificeren en kan uw surfactiviteit op websites die niet van ons zijn, niet volgen. Functionaliteitscookies stellen ons in staat om advertenties weer te geven die op u zijn afgestemd op onze Websites, om te begrijpen welke delen van onze inhoud u het meest interesseren en welke product- of dienstcategorieën u aanvraagt. Sommige van onze dienstverleners mogen cookies op onze Websites plaatsen. Deze bedrijven kunnen u ook de mogelijkheid bieden om het gebruik van cookies in de toekomst te voorkomen.

U kunt op elk moment het toekomstige gebruik van bepaalde cookies voorkomen of weigeren door de juiste instelling in uw browser te activeren voor het weigeren van het accepteren van browsercookies. Als u dit echter doet, kan dit invloed hebben op uw ervaring op onze Websites; u kunt bijvoorbeeld misschien geen toegang krijgen tot bepaalde delen van onze Websites. Tenzij u uw browserinstelling zodanig hebt aangepast dat cookies worden geweigerd, geeft ons systeem cookies uit wanneer u uw browser naar onze Websites leidt.

Cookies voor lokale opslag

Bepaalde functies van onze Websites kunnen lokaal opgeslagen objecten gebruiken om informatie over uw voorkeuren en navigatie naar, van en op onze Websites te verzamelen en op te slaan. Lokale opslagcookies worden niet beheerd door dezelfde browserinstellingen als worden gebruikt voor browsercookies.

We kunnen de Persoonlijke informatie die we van u verzamelen buiten onze Websites of Diensten ook combineren met Persoonlijke informatie die wordt verzameld via onze Websites of Diensten of op een andere manier zoals hierboven beschreven.

1.5 APPARAAT-, NETWERK-, GEOLOCATIE- EN EV-INFORMATIE
-----------------------------------------------------

Wanneer u onze Websites of Diensten bezoekt of verlaat door op een hyperkoppeling te klikken of een plug-in op een website van derden te bekijken, ontvangen we automatisch de URL van de website waar u vandaan kwam of de website waar u naartoe wordt geleid. Adverteerders ontvangen ook de URL van de pagina waarop u zich bevindt wanneer u klikt op een advertentie die op onze Diensten kan verschijnen. We ontvangen ook het internetprotocol (“IP”)-adres van uw computer of de proxyserver die u gebruikt om toegang te krijgen tot het internet, de gegevens van uw computerbesturingssysteem, uw soort webbrowser, uw mobiele apparaat (inclusief uw mobiele apparaat-ID verstrekt door het besturingssysteem van uw mobiele apparaat), uw mobiele besturingssysteem (als u onze Websites of diensten bezoekt via een mobiel apparaat) en de naam van uw ISP (Internet Service Provider) of uw mobiele aanbieder.

1.6 ENQUÊTES
------------

Wij of niet-gelieerde partijen kunnen gebruikersenquêtes uitvoeren met betrekking tot onze Diensten. Sommige niet-gelieerde partijen kunnen advertenties of promoties op u richten op basis van uw antwoorden op de enquête. Wij of niet-gelieerde partijen ontwikkelen nieuwe programma’s of producten op basis van de informatie die u meedeelt in de enquêtes. We kunnen niet-gelieerde partijen gebruiken om u financiële of andere stimulansen te bieden om deel te nemen aan enquêtes. Als de levering van een stimulans uw contactgegevens vereist, kunt u worden gevraagd om Persoonlijke informatie te verstrekken aan de niet-gelieerde partij die het stimulansaanbod uitvoert, die alleen zal worden gebruikt voor het leveren van de beloofde stimulansen en het verifiëren van uw contactgegevens. U beslist zelf of u deze informatie verstrekt of dat u gebruik wilt maken van een stimulans-aanbieding. Uw toestemming voor het gebruik van Persoonlijke informatie voor de doeleinden die in de enquête worden uiteengezet, wordt uitdrukkelijk gevraagd door de niet-gelieerde partij die deze uitvoert. Om u af te melden voor onze enquêtes, kunt u uw verzoek naar ons sturen via de onderstaande contactgegevens.

2\. AARD EN DOEL VAN DE VERWERKING VAN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE
==============================================================

We gebruiken informatie die we over u verzamelen of die u aan ons verstrekt, inclusief Persoonlijke informatie, voor een of meer van de volgende doeleinden:

* om onze Websites en mobiele applicaties en de inhoud ervan aan u te presenteren.
* om u informatie te verstrekken en te reageren op uw vragen over Producten of Diensten die u van ons aanvraagt en informatie over nieuwe producten en diensten, kortingen, speciale promoties of aanstaande evenementen, en functies of aanbiedingen waarvan wij denken dat ze interessant voor u zijn of met betrekking tot een promotie, wedstrijd of loterij waaraan u hebt deelgenomen
* om rekeninginformatie en transactiebetalingen te verwerken, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, product- en/of dienstverleningskosten, en betalingen en terugbetalingen voor gekochte Producten of Diensten (hoewel we niet uw volledige creditkaart- of betaalkaartnummer ontvangen).
* om kortingen, aanbiedingen, loyaliteitsbeloningen en/of kortingsverzoeken, -formulieren en -aanvragen te verwerken en te coördineren met de fabrikant, detailhandelaar en/of groothandelaar.
* om u kennisgevingen te verstrekken over uw account, inclusief kennisgevingen over afloop en verlenging.
* om u op de hoogte te stellen van informatie met betrekking tot of wijzigingen in onze Websites, onze beleidslijnen, voorwaarden of Producten of Diensten die we aanbieden of leveren, of met betrekking tot uw account.
* om Persoonlijke informatie of andere informatie die u ons verstrekt te verwerken.
* om u in staat te stellen deel te nemen aan interactieve functies op onze Websites.
* om onze Producten en Diensten te verbeteren en nieuwe te ontwikkelen, bijvoorbeeld door gebruikerstendensen te analyseren en demografische gegevens en interesses te meten.
* voor interne website-, dienst- en systeemwerking, administratie, onderhoud, interne audits en beoordelingen, het diagnosticeren van technische problemen en het handhaven van beveiliging.
* om elke schending van onze gebruiksvoorwaarden of dit Privacybeleid te onderzoeken.
* om potentiële problemen en tendensen bij het gebruik van onze Websites en Diensten door gebruikers te volgen en onze ondersteuning aan te passen om u beter van dienst te zijn.
* om statistieken te verstrekken over de gebruiksniveaus van de Websites en andere gerelateerde informatie aan onze dienstverleners.
* om u op de hoogte te stellen van incidenten met betrekking tot gegevensbescherming of om u wettelijk vereiste informatie te verstrekken.
* om uw deelname aan classificaties, beoordelingen, enquêtes, focusgroepen of andere initiatieven te verzoeken die ons helpen informatie te verzamelen die wordt gebruikt om onze Producten en Diensten te ontwikkelen en te verbeteren.
* om enig ander doel te vervullen waarvoor u Persoonlijke informatie verstrekt.
* op elke andere manier die we kunnen beschrijven en waarvoor we uw toestemming verkrijgen wanneer u de informatie verstrekt.

We gebruiken cookies, transparante gifs en logbestandsinformatie om: (a) informatie te onthouden zodat u deze niet opnieuw hoeft in te voeren tijdens uw bezoek of de volgende keer dat u de Websites bezoekt; (b) aangepaste, gepersonaliseerde inhoud en informatie te aan bieden; (c) de effectiviteit van onze Diensten te controleren; (d) geaggregeerde statistieken zoals het totale aantal bezoekers, verkeer, en demografische patronen bij te houden; (e) technologische problemen te diagnosticeren of op te lossen die door onze gebruikers of technici worden gemeld en die verband houden met bepaalde IP-adressen; en/of, (f) u te helpen efficiënt toegang te krijgen tot uw informatie nadat u zich hebt aangemeld.

Statistische gegevens die we automatisch verzamelen helpen ons om onze Websites te verbeteren en betere, meer gepersonaliseerde Producten en Diensten te leveren, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, door ons in staat te stellen: de omvang en gebruikspatronen van ons publiek/onze bezoekers te schatten, informatie over uw voorkeuren op te slaan, ons in staat te stellen onze Websites aan te passen en te verbeteren, uw zoekopdrachten te versnellen en/of u te herkennen wanneer u terugkeert naar onze Websites.

We kunnen informatie over uw EV-oplaadsessie verzamelen en gebruiken (bijv. oplaadtijd, energieverbruik, eigenaarschap en gegevens van het station enz.) en het merk, model en jaar van uw voertuig om uw account te beheren, bijvoorbeeld om onderscheid te maken tussen meerdere voertuigen of gebruikers die één account delen, en voor analytische doeleinden.

Voor zover u niet instemt met de hierin uiteengezette praktijken voor informatieverwerking, hebt u wellicht het recht om u af te melden voor dergelijke praktijken. Alle afmeldingsverzoeken moeten worden gericht aan [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Voor zover afmeldingsverzoeken worden gehonoreerd, hebben ze effect op toekomstige verwerking en niet op verwerking die heeft plaatsgevonden op basis van eerdere toestemming.

2.1 GEAUTOMATISEERDE BESLUITVORMING
-----------------------------------

We kunnen uw Persoonlijke informatie die u ons verstrekt en die we uit andere bronnen verkrijgen gebruiken om uw interesses beter te begrijpen, zodat we kunnen proberen te voorspellen in welke andere Producten, Diensten en informatie u het meest geïnteresseerd bent. Deze praktijk omvat het nemen van geautomatiseerde beslissingen over u op basis van deze informatie om ons beter in staat te stellen onze interacties met u aan te passen om ze relevanter en interessanter te maken. U kunt te allen tijde bezwaar maken tegen het feit dat wij dit doen of ons vragen om meer informatie over de methodologie die wordt toegepast in onze geautomatiseerde besluitvormingsprocessen door contact met ons op te nemen (zie sectie 12 hieronder).

2.2 TEKSTBERICHTEN
------------------

Onze Diensten kunnen het verzenden van Short Message Service (“SMS”)-berichten omvatten, die maximaal twee berichten per dag op uw draadloze apparaat kunnen afleveren (tenzij u verder met ons communiceert), maar de berichtfrequentie kan variëren.  Wanneer u uitdrukkelijk instemt met het ontvangen van sms-berichten van ons en een mobiel telefoonnummer opgeeft, stemt u uitdrukkelijk in met het ontvangen van terugkerende informatieve en transactionele teksten van of namens ons op het nummer dat u hebt opgegeven. Door uitdrukkelijk in te stemmen met het ontvangen van sms-berichten van ons en het verstrekken van een mobiel telefoonnummer, garandeert en verklaart u dat u de eigenaar bent van het mobiele telefoonnummer dat u aan ons verstrekt. We kunnen uw informatie gebruiken om contact met u op te nemen over uw gebruik, aankopen, retourzendingen (indien beschikbaar), websiteherzieningen, enquêtes of informatieve en dienstengerelateerde communicatie, waaronder belangrijke beveiligingsberichten. Nadat u het sms-bericht “STOP” naar ons hebt verzonden, sturen we u een sms-bericht om te bevestigen dat u zich hebt afgemeld. U kunt uw verzoek ook per e-mail bij ons indienen, met vermelding van het e-mailadres en telefoonnummer dat u bij ons hebt geregistreerd, of op een andere redelijke manier. Hierna ontvangt u geen sms-berichten meer van ons. Als u zich opnieuw wilt aanmelden, meld u dan gewoon aan zoals u dat de eerste keer hebt gedaan en dan sturen we u weer sms-berichten. Voor assistentie kunt u een tekst beantwoorden met HELP. Er kunnen tarieven voor berichten en gegevens van toepassing zijn, afhankelijk van uw mobiele telefoonabonnement. Aanbieders zijn niet aansprakelijk voor vertraagde of niet-geleverde berichten.

2.3 PLUG-INS VOOR SOCIALE MEDIA
-------------------------------

We integreren interfaces of plug-ins voor sociale media (“Plug-ins)”) van sociale netwerken, waaronder Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest en/of eventueel andere bedrijven, in de Websites. Om u als gebruiker bij ons te registreren, kunt u de optie hebben om u aan te melden met uw Facebook- of andere login voor sociale-mediawebsites.

Wanneer u bijvoorbeeld onze Websites bezoekt, creëert de plug-in een directe verbinding tussen uw browser en de Facebook-server. Hierdoor kan Facebook informatie ontvangen over uw bezoek aan onze Websites met uw IP-adres. Als u op de knop “Vind ik leuk” van Facebook klikt terwijl u bent ingelogd op uw Facebook-account, kunt u de inhoud van onze Websites koppelen aan uw Facebook-profiel. Dit stelt Facebook in staat om uw bezoek aan onze Websites toe te wijzen aan uw gebruikersaccount. Houd er rekening mee dat we als aanbieder van de Websites geen kennisgeving ontvangen over de inhoud van de verzonden gegevens of het gebruik ervan door Facebook. Als u niet wilt dat Facebook uw bezoek aan onze Websites toewijst aan uw Facebook-gebruikersaccount, log dan uit bij uw Facebook-gebruikersaccount.

Als u inlogt via een Plug-in van sociale media, geeft u ons toestemming om toegang te krijgen tot bepaalde accountinformatie vanaf die sociale-mediawebsite, zoals uw openbare sociale-mediaprofiel (in overeenstemming met uw privacy-instellingen op de sociale-mediawebsite), uw e-mailadres, interesses, vind-ik-leuk-waarderingen, gender, verjaardag, opleidingsgeschiedenis, relaties, interesses, huidige plaats, foto’s, persoonlijke beschrijving, lijst met vrienden en informatie over en foto’s van uw vrienden op de sociale- mediawebsite die gemeenschappelijke vrienden met andere gebruikers kunnen zijn op de sociale-mediawebsite. Plug-ins kunnen informatie over u overdragen naar het respectieve platform van de plug-in zonder dat u actie hoeft te ondernemen. Deze informatie kan het gebruikersidentificatienummer van uw platform omvatten, op welke website u zich bevindt en dergelijke. Interactie met een plug-in verzendt informatie rechtstreeks naar het sociale netwerk van die plug-in en die informatie kan zichtbaar zijn voor anderen op dat platform. Plug-ins worden beheerd door het privacybeleid van de respectieve sociale-mediawebsite (beschikbaar op hun website) en niet door ons Privacybeleid.

3\. HOE WE PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE BEKENDMAKEN AAN NIET-GELIEERDE PARTIJEN
==========================================================================

3.1 SOORTEN NIET-GELIEERDE PARTIJEN
-----------------------------------

We kunnen uw Persoonlijke informatie, geheel of gedeeltelijk, bekendmaken aan de volgende soorten niet-gelieerde partijen, en voor een of meer van de volgende doeleinden:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Soort niet-gelieerde partij | Doel |
| Leveranciers van gegevensopslag of -presentatie | veilige opslag en overdracht van uw gegevens |
| Gegevensbestand- en softwaredienstverleners | het beheren en volgen van uw gegevens |
| Juridische en nalevingsadviseurs, zoals externe adviseurs, externe auditors of belastingadviseurs | het leveren van professionele diensten aan ons |
| Aanbieders van identiteitsbeheer | verificatiedoeleinden |
| Aanbieders van betalingsoplossingen | het veilig verwerken van betalingen die u aan ons verstrekt |
| Fabrikanten, detailhandelaren en groothandelaren | het indienen, verwerken en beheren van kortingen, rabatten, aanbiedingen, loyaliteitsbeloningen en dergelijke |
| Leveranciers van uitvoering en verzending | uitvoering en levering van Producten, Diensten en koopwaar |
| Aanbieders van enquêtes en onderzoek | het uitvoeren van onderzoeken namens ons |
| Reclamepartners, waaronder aanbieders van sociale media | het leveren van gerichte advertenties |

Voor elke overdracht van Persoonlijke informatie die redelijkerwijs niet noodzakelijk is om de doeleinden te bereiken waarvoor u communiceert met PlugShare (zoals voor marketing- of enquêtedoeleinden) hebt u het recht om u af te melden voor een dergelijke verwerking. Neem om uw recht op afmelding uit te oefenen contact met ons op via [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 DIENSTVERLENERS, ZAKENPARTNERS EN ONDERAANNEMERS
----------------------------------------------------

 We kunnen uw Persoonlijke informatie doorgeven aan dienstverleners die namens ons diensten verlenen, zoals hierboven besproken. Deze dienstverleners kunnen toegang hebben tot uw Persoonlijke informatie om deze diensten aan ons of namens ons te leveren. Als we dienstverleners inschakelen voor iets van het voorgaande, is het gebruik van uw Persoonlijke informatie gebonden aan geheimhoudingsverplichtingen en hun gebruik van Persoonlijke informatie is beperkt tot het leveren van hun diensten aan ons. We kunnen Persoonlijke informatie opslaan op locaties buiten onze directe controle (bijvoorbeeld op servers of gegevensbestanden die zich bevinden op locaties voor of samen met dienstverleners voor gegevenspresentatie)  

3.3 CONTEXT-OVERSCHRIJDENDE GEDRAGSGERICHTE RECLAME
---------------------------------------------------

We zijn verplicht om bekend te maken of we Persoonlijke informatie doorgeven aan een derde partij die zich bezighoudt met contextoverschrijdende gedragsgerichte (gerichte) reclame. In de afgelopen twaalf (12) maanden hebben we de volgende categorieën Persoonlijke informatie bekendgemaakt of hebben we deze misschien bekendgemaakt in een context die, krachtens bepaalde wetten (bijv. CPRA van Californië, AVG of UK GDPR), kan worden beschouwd als een verkoop:

* identificatoren
* internet- of andere soortgelijke netwerkactiviteiten
* gegevens over geolocatie

U hebt de mogelijkheid om u af te melden voor dit doorgeven door te klikken op de afmeldingsaanwijzingen die verschijnen op de kennisgeving die u wordt aangeboden wanneer u onze mobiele applicaties of Websites voor het eerst bezoekt.

3.4 ZAKELIJKE OVERDRACHTEN
--------------------------

U erkent (en maakt geen bezwaar tegen) onze openbaarmaking of overdracht van uw Persoonlijke informatie, Gedeïdentificeerde Persoonlijke informatie en andere informatie die u aan ons verstrekt, evenals de rechten die u hebt verleend of erkend in dit Privacybeleid (gezamenlijk “Overgedragen informatie”) aan een potentiële of daadwerkelijke koper of overnemende partij van ons bedrijf of een andere opvolger met als doel het overwegen of ondergaan van een fusie, afstoting, herstructurering, reorganisatie, ontbinding, verandering van controle, of overdracht van sommige of al onze activa (elk van het voorgaande aangeduid als een “Overdracht”), hetzij als continu bedrijf of als onderdeel van faillissement, liquidatie of andere gerechtelijke procedure, waarin Persoonlijke informatie die door ons wordt bewaard behoren tot de overgedragen activa, en u stemt ermee in geen bezwaar te maken tegen een dergelijke openbaarmaking en/of overdracht. We kunnen geen verklaringen afleggen met betrekking tot het gebruik of de overdracht van Overgedragen informatie die we eventueel in bezit hebben in geval van ons faillissement, reorganisatie, insolventie, curatele of een overdracht ten behoeve van crediteuren. Bovendien zijn wij, behalve indien wettelijk vereist, niet verantwoordelijk en zullen ook niet verantwoordelijk zijn voor enige inbreuk op de beveiliging door niet-gelieerde partijen of voor enige acties van niet-gelieerde partijen die de Overgedragen informatie ontvangen die aan ons wordt bekendgemaakt.

3.5 VEREISTE OPENBAARMAKINGEN; BESCHERMING VAN RECHTEN; VEILIGHEID
------------------------------------------------------------------

Tenzij anderszins beschreven in dit Privacybeleid, maken wij uw Persoonlijke informatie niet bekend aan een niet-gelieerde partij, tenzij dit wettelijk verplicht is, of op grond van een gerechtelijk bevel, juridische procedure (bijv. dagvaarding), waaronder, maar niet beperkt tot, om te reageren op een verzoek van de overheid, een regelgevende instantie, of vergunningsaanvraag, of als wij van mening zijn dat een dergelijke actie noodzakelijk is om: (a) de wet na te leven, te voldoen aan juridische procedures die worden betekend aan ons of onze gelieerde ondernemingen, dochterondernemingen, gecontracteerde leveranciers, of affiniteitspartners, of om vermoedelijke of daadwerkelijke illegale activiteiten te onderzoeken, voorkomen, of in verband daarmee actie te ondernemen; (b) onze Voorwaarden of klantenovereenkomst af te dwingen (inclusief voor facturerings- en incassodoeleinden); (c) voorzorgsmaatregelen te nemen tegen aansprakelijkheid; (d) onszelf te onderzoeken en verdedigen tegen vorderingen of beschuldigingen van derden; (e) handhavingsinstanties van de overheid te helpen of te voldoen aan nationale of andere veiligheidsvereisten van de overheid; (f) de veiligheid of integriteit van onze Websites, onze Diensten en mobiele applicaties te beschermen; of, (g) de rechten uit te oefenen en ons eigendom of de persoonlijke veiligheid van ons, onze gebruikers of anderen te beschermen. 

We proberen u, indien mogelijk, op de hoogte te stellen van deze verzoeken, tenzij: (i) het verstrekken van kennisgeving is verboden door de juridische procedure zelf, door een gerechtelijk bevel dat we ontvangen, of door de toepasselijke wetgeving, of (ii) we van mening zijn dat het verstrekken van een kennisgeving nutteloos, ineffectief zou zijn, een risico op letsel of lichamelijk of ander letsel voor een persoon of groep zou creëren of het risico op fraude voor ons, onze gebruikers, onze Websites, Diensten of mobiele applicaties zou verhogen. In gevallen waarin we om deze redenen zonder kennisgeving voldoen aan juridische verzoeken, proberen we die gebruiker achteraf op de hoogte te stellen van het verzoek als we te goeder trouw vaststellen dat ons dit niet langer wettelijk verboden is en dat er geen risicoscenario’s zoals beschreven in deze paragraaf van toepassing zijn.

3.6 OPENBAARMAKING VAN GEDEÏDENTIFICEERDE PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE
-----------------------------------------------------------------

We kunnen Gedeïdentificeerde Persoonlijke informatie (inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, anonieme gebruiksgegevens, verwijzende/afsluitpagina’s en URL’s, IP-adres, platformsoorten, aantal klikken enz.) doorgeven aan niet-gelieerde partijen op elke manier die we kiezen en voor elk doel, bijvoorbeeld voor systeembeheer en om het gebruik van de Websites te controleren, voor het meten van het aantal bezoeken aan onze Websites, gemiddelde tijd die is doorgebracht, aantal bekeken pagina’s en het controleren van verschillende andere websitestatistieken om de inhoud te verbeteren.

4\.  “NIET VOLGEN”-VERZOEKEN
============================

Sommige webbrowsers (waaronder Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox en Chrome) bevatten een functie, of soortelijke functie, “Niet volgen” (Do Not Track, “DNT”) die aangeeft aan websites dat een gebruiker zijn of haar online activiteit en gedrag niet wil laten volgen. Als een website die reageert op een bepaald niet-volgen-signaal het niet-volgen-signaal ontvangt, kan de browser die website blokkeren voor het verzamelen van bepaalde informatie over de gebruiker van de browser. Niet alle browsers bieden een niet-volgen-optie en niet-volgen-signalen zijn nog niet uniform. Daarom reageren veel websitebeheerders, waaronder PlugShare, niet op niet-volgen-signalen.

5\. COMMUNICATIE VAN PLUGSHARE, VOORKEUREN EN AFMELDING
=======================================================

Door ons uw e-mailadres te verstrekken, stemt u ermee in dat wij het e-mailadres gebruiken om u dienstengerelateerde kennisgevingen per e-mail te sturen, inclusief, maar niet beperkt tot, kennisgevingen die wettelijk vereist zijn (bijv. kennisgeving van gegevensprivacy- of beveiligingsincidenten), in plaats van communicatie per post. U gaat er ook mee akkoord dat we u meldingen kunnen sturen over activiteiten met betrekking tot onze Producten, Diensten, de Websites, de mobiele applicaties, uw Persoonlijke informatie of enig aspect van onze relatie, naar het e-mailadres dat u ons opgeeft, in overeenstemming met alle toepasselijke privacy-instellingen. We kunnen uw e-mailadres gebruiken om u andere berichten of inhoud te sturen, zoals, maar niet beperkt tot, nieuwsbrieven, toevoegingen of wijzigingen aan functies van de Dienst of speciale aanbiedingen. Als u dergelijke e-mailberichten niet wilt ontvangen, kunt u zich afmelden door te klikken op Afmelden, indien beschikbaar. Als u zich afmeldt, kunt u wellicht geen e-mailberichten ontvangen over herzieningen, verbeteringen, speciale functies, aankondigingen of aanbiedingen. U kunt zich niet afmelden voor dienstengerelateerde e-mails. Als u ervoor hebt gekozen om ons geen e-mail- of ander adres te verstrekken, ontvangt u misschien geen e-mails met betrekking tot onze Diensten.

Via de instellingenpagina van uw gebruikersaccount kunt u bepaalde informatie die u aan ons hebt verstrekt, zoals naam en wachtwoord, e-mailadres, adres, gebruikersprofielinformatie enz. openen en, in sommige gevallen, bewerken of verwijderen. De informatie die u kunt bekijken, bijwerken en verwijderen kan veranderen naarmate de Producten, Websites, Diensten of onze praktijken veranderen. Als u vragen hebt over het bekijken of bijwerken van informatie die we over u hebben, neem dan contact met ons op. Wanneer u informatie bijwerkt, kunnen we echter een kopie van de niet-herziene informatie in onze administratie bewaren. U kunt verzoeken om verwijdering van uw account door ons een e-mail te sturen. Het is uw verantwoordelijkheid om uw huidige e-mailadres bij ons te bewaren. Afhankelijk van in welke staat of welk land u woont, hebt u eventueel aanvullende rechten. Zie hieronder voor meer informatie.

6\. ONTWIKKELAARS DIE PLATFORMDIENSTEN VAN PLUGSHARE GEBRUIKEN
==============================================================

We werken samen met en stellen derden in staat om het ontwikkelaarsplatform van PlugShare te gebruiken om diensten en functionaliteit aan te bieden samen met PlugShare. Deze externe ontwikkelaars hebben ofwel onderhandeld over een overeenkomst om de platformtechnologie van PlugShare te gebruiken of hebben ingestemd met onze zelfbedienings-Application Programming Interfaces (“API”) en plug-invoorwaarden om softwareplatformtoepassingen (“Platformtoepassingen”) te ontwerpen. Zowel de onderhandelde overeenkomsten als onze API- en plug-ingebruiksvoorwaarden bevatten beperkingen over hoe derden toegang kunnen krijgen tot de Persoonlijke informatie die u aan PlugShare verstrekt, en deze kunnen opslaan en gebruiken. Als u ervoor kiest om een platformtoepassing te gebruiken, wordt u gevraagd om acceptatie van het privacybeleid en de gebruikersovereenkomst van de externe ontwikkelaar te bevestigen. Ga naar uw instellingen om de toestemming voor een platformtoepassing in te trekken. Houd er echter rekening mee dat zelfs als u de toestemming voor een platformtoepassing intrekt, uw verbindingen misschien nog steeds gebruikmaken van de platformtoepassing, zodat de platformtoepassing wellicht nog steeds toegang heeft tot bepaalde informatie over u, evenals uw verbindingen dat hebben.

7\. BEWAREN VAN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE
=======================================

De periode waarin we uw Persoonlijke informatie bewaren hangt af van de doeleinden waarvoor we deze gebruiken. We bewaren uw Persoonlijke informatie zolang uw account actief is, of zolang u een geregistreerde accounthouder of gebruiker van onze Diensten bent of zolang we een ander zakelijk doel hebben om dit te doen (zoals, maar niet beperkt tot, voor zakelijke, belasting- of juridische doeleinden) en, daarna, niet langer dan wettelijk is vereist of toegestaan, of ons beleid inzake het bewaren van documenten, redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk is voor interne rapportage- en afstemmingsdoeleinden, of om u terugkoppeling of informatie te geven die u zou kunnen opvragen. Deze bewaartermijn is onderhevig aan onze beoordeling en wijziging. We kunnen Gedeïdentificeerde Persoonlijke informatie bewaren zolang we dit gepast achten.

Na beëindiging of deactivering van uw gebruikersaccount kunnen we uw profielinformatie en alle informatie die op openbare delen van de Websites is geplaatst, bewaren. Na beëindiging of deactivering van uw gebruikersaccount kunnen we uw Persoonlijke informatie en andere gegevens bewaren, maar houden we deze vertrouwelijk volgens de Voorwaarden, dit Privacybeleid en indien vereist door de toepasselijke wetgeving. We hebben het recht om al uw Persoonlijke informatie en andere gegevens na beëindiging van uw gebruikersaccount zonder kennisgeving aan u te verwijderen.

8\. GEEN OPZETTELIJKE VERZAMELING VAN GEGEVENS VAN KINDEREN
===========================================================

We verzamelen, vragen of bewaren niet bewust Persoonlijke informatie van iemand jonger dan 18 jaar of staan niet bewust toe dat dergelijke personen zich registreren voor of gebruikmaken van onze Diensten. Als u jonger bent dan 18 jaar, stuur ons dan geen Persoonlijke informatie. Indien we te weten komen dat we Persoonlijke informatie hebben verzameld van een kind jonger dan 18 jaar zonder verificatie van ouderlijke toestemming, leveren we commercieel redelijke inspanningen om die informatie uit ons gegevensbestand te verwijderen.

9\. WAAR PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE WORDT VERWERKT EN OPGESLAGEN; TOEPASSELIJK GELDEND RECHT
=========================================================================================

We hebben ons hoofdkantoor in de Verenigde Staten. De Persoonlijke informatie die wij of onze dienstverleners verzamelen, kan worden opgeslagen en verwerkt op servers binnen of buiten de Verenigde Staten en overal waar wij en onze Dienstverleners faciliteiten over de hele wereld hebben, en bepaalde informatie kan toegankelijk zijn voor personen of bedrijven buiten de Verenigde Staten die diensten voor ons verlenen. U stemt in met de overbrenging en/of overdracht van uw Persoonlijke informatie door ons en onze Dienstverleners naar, of toegang daartoe in, rechtsgebieden die wellicht niet hetzelfde niveau van gegevensbescherming bieden als uw eigen rechtsgebied. We nemen redelijke maatregelen om ervoor te zorgen dat uw Persoonlijke informatie een adequaat beschermingsniveau krijgt in de rechtsgebieden waarin we deze verwerken.

De Amerikaanse wetten zijn van toepassing voor zover u inwoner van de Verenigde Staten bent. Anders worden dit Privacybeleid en alle andere zaken geïnterpreteerd en opgevat in overeenstemming met de provinciale/staats- en federale wetten van het rechtsgebied waar u woont. Rechtsgebieden buiten uw woonplaats kunnen privacywetten hebben die verschillen van die in uw rechtsgebied, waaronder het recht van wetshandhavings- en overheidsinstanties om toegang te krijgen tot de Persoonlijke informatie.  Voor zover we gegevens buiten uw land verwerken, voeren we een privacyeffectbeoordeling uit om te bepalen dat onze Dienstverleners in wezen hetzelfde niveau van bescherming kunnen bieden als vereist in uw rechtsgebied en contracten kunnen aangaan om de verplichtingen om uw Persoonlijke informatie op de juiste manier te verwerken verder te versterken.

10\. BEVEILIGING
================

We hebben technische en organisatorische beveiligingsmaatregelen geïmplementeerd die zijn ontworpen om uw Persoonlijke informatie te beschermen tegen onopzettelijk verlies en tegen onbevoegd(e) toegang, gebruik, vernietiging, wijziging en openbaarmaking. Houd er echter rekening mee dat het internet geen 100% veilige omgeving is. Het is uw verantwoordelijkheid om de veiligheid van uw inloggegevens te beschermen, voorzichtig te zijn bij het verzenden van Persoonlijke informatie via e-mails, chatberichten (instant messaging) en soortgelijke communicatiemiddelen, en goede internetbeveiligingspraktijken te handhaven. We zullen u nooit e-mailen om uw wachtwoord of andere inloggegevens van uw account op te vragen. Als u een dergelijke e-mail ontvangt, stuur deze dan naar ons zodat we dit kunnen onderzoeken.

11\. AANVULLENDE RECHTEN VAN BETROKKENEN VOOR INWONERS IN BEPAALDE RECHTSGEBIEDEN BESCHREVEN IN DE AANVULLENDE PRIVACYVERKLARINGEN
==================================================================================================================================

De volgende informatie geeft uitleg over elk recht van de betrokkene dat wordt beschreven in de Aanvullende privacyverklaringen:

* recht om informatie over Privacypraktijken te ontvangen: U hebt het recht om bepaalde wettelijk vereiste informatie te ontvangen op of vóór het moment van verzameling of in reactie op uw verzoek.
* Recht op verwijdering. U kunt ons verzoeken om alle Persoonlijke informatie over u die wij van u hebben verzameld, te verwijderen, behoudens bepaalde uitzonderingen.
* Recht op correctie. U kunt ons verzoeken om onjuiste Persoonlijke informatie die wij over u bewaren te corrigeren.
* Recht om te weten: U kunt ons verzoeken om u specifieke informatie te verstrekken over hoe we uw Persoonlijke informatie hebben behandeld, inclusief het verstrekken van een kopie van de specifieke Persoonlijke informatie die we over u hebben verzameld in een draagbaar formaat.
* Recht op non-discriminatie: U hebt het recht om niet gediscrimineerd te worden voor het uitoefenen van uw rechten als betrokkene. Dat betekent dat u geen goederen of diensten worden ontzegd, u geen andere prijzen of tarieven in rekening worden gebracht of een ander kwaliteitsniveau wordt geboden voor producten of diensten als gevolg van het uitoefenen van uw rechten als betrokkene.
* Rechten om u af te melden: U kunt verzoeken om u af te melden voor de verkoop en het doorgeven van uw Persoonlijke informatie, contextoverschrijdende gedrags- of gerichte reclame, geautomatiseerde besluitvorming of profilering, voor zover dergelijke activiteiten zijn gedefinieerd en beperkt krachtens de toepasselijke wetgeving.
* Recht op beperking van of bezwaar tegen verwerking: U kunt ons verzoeken om de verwerking van gedeelten van uw Persoonlijke informatie te onderdrukken of te stoppen, maar we kunnen uw Persoonlijke informatie nog steeds opslaan.  
* Recht om het gebruik van uw gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie te beperken: U kunt verzoeken om het gebruik van uw gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie te beperken tot alleen de doeleinden die zijn toegestaan door de toepasselijke wetgeving.
* Recht om een klacht in te dienen: U hebt het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij uw lokale gegevensbeschermingsautoriteit als u van mening bent dat de verwerking van Persoonlijke informatie met betrekking tot u inbreuk maakt op uw rechten.
* Recht om toestemming in te trekken: Voor zover onze verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie uitsluitend gebaseerd is op uw toestemming, kunt u die toestemming op elk moment intrekken.

12\. CONTACTINFORMATIE
======================

PlugShare heeft een Functionaris voor gegevensbescherming aangewezen als de persoon die toezicht houdt op de naleving van de privacyvereisten. De Functionaris voor gegevensbescherming van PlugShare kan worden gecontacteerd op het onderstaande adres met betrekking tot problemen met het privacybeleid.

Als u vragen of opmerkingen hebt over dit Privacybeleid of onze privacypraktijken, neem dan contact met ons op via: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, Californië 90245 VS; Attn: Data Protection Officer; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

PRIVACYVERKLARING VOOR INWONERS VAN BEPAALDE AMERIKAANSE STATEN
===============================================================

Als u inwoner bent van Californië, Virginia, Colorado, Utah of Connecticut (in dit document soms “consument” genoemd), bieden de wetten van die staten u aanvullende rechten met betrekking tot ons gebruik van uw Persoonlijke informatie.

‘SHINE THE LIGHT’-WET VAN CALIFORNIË
------------------------------------

Paragraaf 1798.83 van het Burgerlijk Wetboek van Californië, bekend als de “Shine The Light”-wet, staat alle gebruikers die inwoners van Californië zijn toe om een lijst op te vragen en van ons te verkrijgen van welke Persoonlijke informatie (indien van toepassing) we in het voorgaande kalenderjaar aan derden hebben bekendgemaakt voor directe-marketingdoeleinden en de namen en adressen van die derden. Aanvragen kunnen slechts eenmaal per jaar worden ingediend en zijn kosteloos.

CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (“CALOPPA”; CALIF. BUS. & PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, [HIER](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D) [BESCHIKBAAR](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D-unjQiFUTqBmO4c2RM1s))
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA is alleen van toepassing op bedrijven die Persoonlijke informatie van inwoners van Californië verzamelen.

1. HOE WE REAGEREN OP SIGNALEN VAN NIET VOLGEN.

Sommige webbrowsers sturen “niet volgen” (DNT/GPC) signalen naar de websites en andere online diensten waarmee uw webbrowser communiceert. Er bestaat momenteel geen norm die bepaalt wat websites moeten doen wanneer zij deze signalen ontvangen; wij hebben echter wel maatregelen getroffen om op deze signalen te reageren.

2. GEDRAGSTRACERING VAN DERDEN

We kunnen deze technologieën ook gebruiken om informatie te verzamelen over uw online activiteiten in de loop der tijd en op websites van derden of andere online diensten, of om Persoonlijke informatie te koppelen aan andere informatie die op deze manier wordt verzameld. We kunnen Persoonlijke informatie gebruiken om de klik- en surfpatronen van gebruikers bij te houden.

CALIFORNIA CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT OF 2018 (“CCPA”, [HIER](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.-l-l_E20) [BESCHIKBAAR](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) EN DE OPVOLGER DAARVAN, DE CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS ACT OF 2020 (“CPRA”, [HIER](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf) [BESCHIKBAAR](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)).
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

In de onderstaande tabel wordt beschreven hoe we persoonlijke informatie die we over u hebben verzameld openbaar maken:

| Categorie | Categorieën niet-gelieerde derden aan wie we persoonlijke informatie bekendmaken | Categorieën niet-gelieerde derden aan wie we Persoonlijke informatie verkopen of doorgeven |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificatoren | Leveranciers van gegevensopslag of -presentatie<br><br>Aanbieders van identiteitsbeheer<br><br>Aanbieders van betalingsoplossingen<br><br>Aanbieders van enquêtes en onderzoek<br><br>Reclamepartners, waaronder aanbieders van sociale media | n.v.t. |
| Demografisch | Aanbieders van enquêtes en onderzoek | n.v.t. |
| Commerciële informatie | n.v.t. | n.v.t. |
| Internet- of andere elektronische netwerkactiviteit; apparaatinformatie | Leveranciers van gegevensopslag of -presentatie<br><br>Gegevensbestand- en softwaredienstverleners<br><br>Aanbieders van identiteitsbeheer<br><br>Reclamepartners, waaronder aanbieders van sociale media | n.v.t. |
| Geolocatie | Leveranciers van gegevensopslag of -presentatie<br><br>Gegevensbestand- en softwaredienstverleners<br><br>Reclamepartners, waaronder aanbieders van sociale media | n.v.t. |
| Overig | Leveranciers van gegevensopslag of -presentatie<br><br>Gegevensbestand- en softwaredienstverleners<br><br>Aanbieders van enquêtes en onderzoek<br><br>Reclamepartners, waaronder aanbieders van sociale media | Fabrikanten, detailhandelaren en groothandelaren |

U kunt contact met ons opnemen om de volgende rechten uit te oefenen krachtens de CCPA en CPRA (zie sectie 11 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid voor beschrijvingen van deze rechten):

1. Recht om informatie over Privacypraktijken te ontvangen.
2. Recht om het volgende te weten:

* de categorieën Persoonlijke informatie die we over u hebben verzameld.
* de categorieën bronnen voor Persoonlijke informatie die we over u hebben verzameld.
* ons zakelijke of commerciële doel voor het verzamelen van die Persoonlijke informatie.
* de categorieën derden aan wie we die Persoonlijke informatie doorgeven.
* de specifieke Persoonlijke informatie die we over u hebben verzameld (ook wel een verzoek om gegevensportabiliteit genoemd) en u een kopie verstrekken in elektronisch of papieren formaat.
* Als we uw Persoonlijke informatie openbaar hebben gemaakt voor een zakelijk doel, een lijst met openbaarmakingen voor een zakelijk doel, waarbij de categorieën Persoonlijke informatie worden geïdentificeerd die elke categorie ontvanger heeft verkregen.

3. Recht op verwijdering.
4. Recht op correctie.
5. Recht om u af te melden voor contextoverschrijdende gedragsadvertenties, de verkoop of het doorgeven van Persoonlijke informatie, de verwerking van Persoonlijke informatie voor profilering en geautomatiseerde besluitvorming.
6. Recht om het gebruik van uw gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie te beperken. Houd er rekening mee dat wij geen gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie over u gebruiken voor doeleinden die niet zijn toegestaan door de CCPA en CPRA.

VIRGINIA CONSUMER DATA PROTECTION ACT (VCDPA), COLORADO PRIVACY ACT (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), UTAH CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) EN CONNECTICUT DATA PRIVACY ACT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

U kunt contact met ons opnemen om de volgende rechten uit te oefenen krachtens deze staatsspecifieke wetten:

1. Recht om informatie over Privacypraktijken te ontvangen.
2. Recht om te weten.
3. Recht op verwijdering.
4. Recht op correctie.
5. Recht om u af te melden van gerichte reclame of de verkoop van Persoonlijke informatie.
6. Recht op afmelding van profilering (geautomatiseerde verwerking van persoonlijke informatie voor het analyseren of voorspellen van de kenmerken of het toekomstige gedrag van een persoon, resulterend in beslissingen die de essentiële rechten van een persoon beïnvloeden).  
7. Consumenten in Virginia, Colorado en Connecticut hebben ook het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen onze beslissingen over hun verzoeken van betrokkenen door contact met ons op te nemen via dezelfde methode voor het indienen van een verzoek. Voeg een kopie bij van of verwijs anderszins specifiek naar onze beslissing over uw verzoek van de betrokkene, zodat we uw beroep adequaat kunnen behandelen. Wij reageren op uw beroep in overeenstemming met de toepasselijke wetgeving.

NEVADA
------

Zoals hierboven beschreven, kunnen we uw identificatiegegevens of andere identificerende informatie die we verzamelen van onze Websites en online Diensten verkopen aan niet-gelieerde partijen voor contextoverschrijdende gedragstraceringsdoeleinden in de zin van de wetgeving van Nevada. U hebt het recht om u af te melden voor het verkopen of in licentie geven van die categorieën Persoonlijke informatie over u aan niet-gelieerde partijen.

UITOEFENEN VAN RECHTEN
----------------------

Om de hierboven beschreven rechten op toegang, correctie, gegevensportabiliteit en verwijdering uit te oefenen, kunt u een verzoek bij ons indienen via ons webformulier dat [hier](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form) [beschikbaar is.](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form-iLJlideBS_6WgCKZ50). Alleen u of een persoon die u heeft gemachtigd om namens u te handelen, kan een verzoek indienen met betrekking tot uw Persoonlijke informatie. U kunt ook een verzoek indienen namens uw minderjarige kind. Indien wij een verzoek ontvangen van een persoon om namens u rechten uit te oefenen, zullen wij vragen om een kopie van uw ondertekende toestemming om namens u dergelijke verzoeken in te dienen en zullen wij contact met u opnemen om deze toestemming rechtstreeks te bevestigen. U mag slechts twee keer binnen een periode van 12 maanden een verzoek om toegang of gegevensportabiliteit indienen. Het verifieerbare consumentenverzoek moet:

* voldoende informatie verstrekken waarmee we redelijkerwijs kunnen verifiëren dat u de persoon bent over wie we Persoonlijke informatie hebben verzameld of dat een bevoegde vertegenwoordiger het verzoek heeft gedaan.
* uw verzoek beschrijven met voldoende informatie zodat we het goed kunnen begrijpen, evalueren en erop kunnen reageren.

We kunnen niet reageren op uw verzoek of u Persoonlijke informatie verstrekken als we uw identiteit of bevoegdheid om het verzoek in te dienen en te bevestigen dat de Persoonlijke informatie op u betrekking hebben, niet kunnen verifiëren. Als u een verzoek indient, hoeft u geen account bij ons aan te maken. We gebruiken alleen Persoonlijke informatie die is verstrekt in een verzoek om de identiteit of bevoegdheid van de aanvrager om het verzoek in te dienen te verifiëren.

Om uw rechten uit te oefenen om u af te melden voor contextoverschrijdende gedragsreclame, gerichte reclame of het doorgeven van Persoonlijke informatie zoals hierboven beschreven, moet u zich afmelden volgens de regels van het platform waarop u zich bevindt.  Houd er rekening mee dat uw verzoek tot afmelding specifiek is voor het apparaat en het platform waarop u dat verzoek indient, zodat u mogelijk meerdere verzoeken zult moeten indienen als u zich voor meerdere apparaten en platforms wilt afmelden voor deze specifieke verwerkingsactiviteiten. Klik:

* hier om u af te melden voor Plugshare.com (webplatform)
* hier om u af te melden voor de Plugshare iOS-app
* hier om u af te melden voor de Plugshare Android-app

### Verificatieprocedure

Na ontvangst van een verzoek om toegang, correctie, gegevensportabiliteit of verwijdering van gegevens van u sturen we u binnen 10 werkdagen een e-mail naar het e-mailadres dat we voor u in ons bestand hebben. In de e-mail wordt u gevraagd om te reageren om te verifiëren dat u de consument bent die het verzoek indient. Na ontvangst van uw verificatie koppelen we uw informatie aan die welke in ons bestand opgenomen. Na verificatie van uw identiteit verwerken we uw verzoek en reageren we binnen 45 kalenderdagen, tenzij (a) we uw verzoek niet kunnen verifiëren, (b) we niet in staat zijn om u te koppelen aan informatie in ons gegevensbestand, of (c) er een wettelijke uitzondering bestaat die ons vrijstelt van het voldoen aan uw verzoek. Als we meer tijd nodig hebben (maximaal vijfenveertig (45) kalenderdagen extra), informeren we u schriftelijk over de reden en de verlengingsperiode.

Als wij niet aan uw verzoek kunnen voldoen, zullen wij in ons antwoord de redenen hiervoor toelichten. Voor verzoeken om gegevensportabiliteit selecteren we een formaat om uw Persoonlijke informatie te verstrekken dat gemakkelijk bruikbaar is en u in staat moet stellen de informatie zonder belemmering van de ene entiteit naar de andere te verzenden.

We brengen geen kosten in rekening om uw verifieerbare consumentenverzoek te verwerken of te beantwoorden, tenzij het buitensporig, repetitief of kennelijk ongegrond is. Als we bepalen dat het verzoek een vergoeding rechtvaardigt, vertellen we u waarom we die beslissing hebben genomen en geven we u een kostenraming voordat we uw verzoek afhandelen.

* * *

PRIVACYVERKLARINGEN VOOR BEPAALDE NIET-AMERIKAANSE LANDEN
=========================================================

ALGEMENE INFORMATIE
-------------------

1. ### UW SPECIFIEKE TOESTEMMING VOOR DE VERWERKING VAN “GEVOELIGE” OF “SPECIALE” CATEGORIEËN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE

Krachtens de privacywetgeving van sommige landen worden bepaalde soorten Persoonlijke informatie beschouwd als “gevoelige” of “speciale” categorieën informatie. We verwerken zelden gevoelige of speciale categorieën gegevens, tenzij het in uw vitale belang is of dat van iemand anders dat we dit doen. In alle andere omstandigheden stemt u specifiek in met onze verzameling, verwerking en bewaring van gevoelige of speciale categorieën Persoonlijke informatie zoals beschreven in sectie 1.2 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid en stemt u anderszins in met de verwerking van Persoonlijke informatie in overeenstemming met deze Privacyverklaring.  

2. ### ONZE RECHTSGRONDEN VOOR HET VERWERKEN VAN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE

Onze rechtsgronden voor het verzamelen en gebruiken van de hierboven beschreven Persoonlijke informatie zijn afhankelijk van de betreffende Persoonlijke informatie en de specifieke context waarin we deze verzamelen. Over het algemeen verzamelen en verwerken we uw persoonlijke informatie alleen wanneer we de persoonlijke informatie nodig hebben om diensten voor u uit te voeren waarvoor u een overeenkomst met ons hebt afgesloten, of wanneer de verwerking in ons legitieme belang is en niet wordt opgeheven door uw belangen op het gebied van gegevensbescherming of fundamentele rechten en vrijheden; we baseren ons op uw toestemming wanneer we wettelijk verplicht zijn om dit te doen. In sommige gevallen kunnen we ook een wettelijke verplichting hebben om Persoonlijke informatie van u te verzamelen of anderszins de Persoonlijke informatie nodig hebben om uw vitale belangen of die van iemand anders te beschermen.

LEGITIEME BELANGENBASIS VOOR HET VERZAMELEN VAN PERSOONLIJKE INFORMATIE: Het verzamelen en verwerken van uw Persoonlijke informatie kan noodzakelijk zijn voor onze legitieme belangen. Dergelijke legitieme belangen kunnen het volgende omvatten:

* fraudepreventie
* zorgen voor netwerk- en informatiebeveiliging
* mogelijke criminele handelingen of bedreigingen voor de openbare veiligheid aangeven, waaronder het verbeteren van de bescherming van onze gemeenschap tegen ongewenste berichten, intimidatie, inbreuk op intellectuele eigendom, misdaad en alle soorten veiligheidsrisico’s en het afdwingen van juridische vorderingen, waaronder onderzoek naar mogelijke schendingen van onze gebruiksvoorwaarden
* wanneer we voldoen aan wettelijke verplichtingen
* verwerken van gegevens van werknemers of bezoekers, leden, deelnemers of registranten
* uitvoeren van de functie of dienst die u van ons hebt aangevraagd
* leveren van onze Diensten en hun functionaliteit aan u wanneer een dergelijke verwerking noodzakelijk is voor de doeleinden van de legitieme belangen die door ons of door onze dienstverleners worden nagestreefd met betrekking tot de Diensten
* directe marketing
* de relevante en passende relatie die we met u hebben
* analyse, bijv. het beoordelen van het aantal bezoekers, bekijken van pagina’s, gebruik van de Websites enz. om te begrijpen hoe onze Websites, Producten en Diensten worden gebruikt, om de Websites en/of toekomstige communicatie te optimaliseren en om nieuwe diensten en websitefuncties te ontwikkelen
* uw informatie en voorkeuren bijwerken
* aanbieden en verbeteren van onze Websites, Producten en Diensten
* afdwingen van juridische vorderingen, inclusief onderzoek naar mogelijke schendingen van onze Voorwaarden

Naast de hierboven verstrekte informatie zijn de volgende secties alleen van toepassing op inwoners of staatsburgers van het besproken land of de besproken regio. Voor de doeleinden van de volgende secties, tenzij specifiek vermeld, betekent “Persoonlijke informatie” zoals hierboven gebruikt persoonlijke informatie, persoonsgegevens of een soortgelijke term zoals van toepassing krachtens de wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming van dat land of die regio. In geval van een conflict, en voor zover er een conflict bestaat, tussen de onderstaande secties en de bovenstaande secties, hebben de onderstaande secties voorrang.

AVG – PRIVACYVERKLARING VOOR INWONERS VAN DE EUROPESE ECONOMISCHE RUIMTE (EEA), HET VERENIGD KONINKRIJK EN ZWITSERLAND
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### OVERZICHT

De volgende bepalingen zijn alleen van toepassing als u inwoner bent van de EER, het Verenigd Koninkrijk of Zwitserland (in deze sectie voor het gemak de “EU-regio” genoemd).

Voor dergelijke inwoners wordt alle verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie uitgevoerd in overeenstemming met privacyrechten en -voorschriften, met name (EU) 2016/679 van het Europees Parlement en de Raad van 27 april 2016, bekend als de Algemene Verordening Gegevensbescherming of de General Data Protection Regulation van het Verenigd Koninkrijk voor inwoners van het Verenigd Koninkrijk (gezamenlijk “AVG”), en onze verwerking vindt plaats in overeenstemming met de AVG. Voor de doeleinden van de AVG zijn wij de “verwerkingsverantwoordelijke” van Persoonlijke informatie (aangeduid en gedefinieerd in de AVG ([hier](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/) [beschikbaar](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) als “persoonsgegevens”) die we verzamelen, tenzij we dergelijke informatie verzamelen namens een “verwerkingsverantwoordelijke” in welk geval wij een “verwerker” zijn. Dit Privacybeleid is niet van toepassing op websites, toepassingen of diensten die dit Privacybeleid niet weergeven of ernaar doorkoppelen of die een ander privacybeleid weergeven of ernaar doorkoppelen. Alleen voor inwoners en staatsburgers van de EU-regio, voor zover een definitie in dit Privacybeleid in strijd is met een definitie krachtens de AVG, heeft de definitie van de AVG voorrang.

Wij bieden adequate bescherming voor de overdracht van Persoonlijke informatie naar landen buiten de EU-regio via een of meer van de volgende methoden: (a) een reeks overeenkomsten tussen bedrijven op basis van of met inbegrip van de modelcontractbepalingen, (b) we kunnen ons baseren op de adequaatheidsbeslissingen van de Europese Commissie over bepaalde landen, indien van toepassing, (c) we kunnen uw toestemming verkrijgen voor deze gegevensoverdrachten van de EU-regio naar de Verenigde Staten naar andere landen, (d) we kunnen bindende bedrijfsregels aannemen, of (e) voor zover van toepassing kunnen we kunnen ons beroepen op vrijstellingen zoals uiteengezet in AVG artikel 49 voor de overdracht en verdere overdracht van Persoonlijke informatie die is verzameld van personen in de EU-regio naar de Verenigde Staten en andere landen die volgens de EU-regio onvoldoende gegevensbescherming bieden. Met betrekking tot methode (e) kunnen we Persoonlijke informatie overdragen aan een derde partij om een contract met u uit te voeren, met uw uitdrukkelijke toestemming of op een manier die niet zwaarder weegt dan uw rechten en vrijheden. Als deze Persoonlijke informatie niet wordt verwerkt en overgedragen, kunnen we het contract met u niet uitvoeren of hebt u geen toegang tot enige of alle voordelen en functies die verband houden met uw transactie.

We moeten uw informatie eventueel ook overdragen aan andere groepsbedrijven of dienstverleners in landen buiten de EU-regio. Dit kan gebeuren als onze servers of leveranciers en dienstverleners buiten de EU-regio zijn gevestigd, of als u onze Producten en/of Diensten gebruikt terwijl u landen buiten deze gebieden bezoekt.

Onze rechtsgronden voor het verzamelen van uw Persoonlijke informatie worden besproken .

2. ### UW GEGEVENSRECHTEN KRACHTENS DE AVG.

Als u onderworpen bent aan de AVG, omvatten uw rechten het:

* Recht om te weten.
* Recht op correctie.
* Recht op verwijdering.
* Recht op beperking van of bezwaar tegen verwerking. U hebt het recht om bezwaar te maken tegen uw Persoonlijke informatie die op de volgende manieren wordt gebruikt: (a) verwerking op basis van legitieme belangen of de uitvoering van een taak in het algemeen belang/uitoefening van officiële autoriteit (inclusief profilering); (b) directe marketing (inclusief profilering); en (c) verwerking voor doeleinden van wetenschappelijk/historisch onderzoek en statistieken. Zie hieronder voor meer informatie.
* Recht om u af te melden. U hebt het recht om niet te worden onderworpen aan een beslissing die uitsluitend is gebaseerd op geautomatiseerde verwerking, inclusief profilering, die rechtsgevolgen met betrekking tot u heeft of die op vergelijkbare wijze een aanzienlijke invloed op u heeft, met uitzondering van de uitzonderingen die van toepassing zijn op grond van de relevante wetgeving inzake gegevensbescherming.
* Recht om een klacht in te dienen. Als u binnen de EER woont, vindt u [hier](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm) [een lijst met nationale gegevensbeschermingsautoriteiten](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm-YhzxkCA). Als u in het Verenigd Koninkrijk woont, kunt u [hier](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/) contact opnemen met het Commissioner’s Office.
* Recht om toestemming in te trekken.

KENNISGEVINGEN AAN INWONERS VAN BEPAALDE ANDERE (NIET-AMERIKAANSE) LANDEN
-------------------------------------------------------------------------

Het volgende in deze sectie is een aanvulling op de informatie die wordt besproken in ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid.

We respecteren de volgende rechten van betrokkenen voor alle inwoners buiten de VS:

* recht om informatie over Privacypraktijken te ontvangen:

* onze identiteit en contactinformatie;
* het specifieke doel van onze verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie;
* de vorm en duur van onze verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie;
* informatie over ons doorgeven en het doel van het doorgeven van uw Persoonlijke informatie;
* de verantwoordelijkheden van derden die uw Persoonlijke informatie verwerken, en;
* informatie met betrekking tot openbare en particuliere entiteiten waaraan we uw Persoonlijke informatie hebben doorgegeven.

* Recht om te weten:

* beslissingen die uitsluitend worden genomen op basis van geautomatiseerde verwerking van Persoonlijke informatie;
* toegang krijgen tot informatie over de Persoonlijke informatie die we verzamelen.

* Recht op correctie.
* Recht op beperking van of bezwaar tegen verwerking.
* Recht om toestemming in te trekken.

Elke vertaling van dit Privacybeleid in een andere taal dan het Engels wordt uitsluitend ter informatie verstrekt. In geval van discrepanties is de enige wettelijk geldige en bindende versie de Engelse versie van dit document.

1. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN ARGENTINIË

De technische en organisatorische beveiligingsmaatregelen die door PlugShare worden geïmplementeerd, ondersteunen ook regels in de Argentijnse Wet inzake bescherming persoonsgegevens (PDPA) 25.326, zoals het verbod op secundair gebruik van de persoonsgegevens van een betrokkene en het verbod op de overdracht van persoonsgegevens naar landen die geen adequaat beschermingsniveau bieden. PlugShare gebruikt een overeenkomst voor gegevensoverdracht/-verwerking om te helpen bij de naleving van PDPA-bepaling 60-E/2016, die de grensoverschrijdende overdracht van persoonsgegevens regelt.

Inwoners van Argentinië hebben (a) het recht om informatie te weten over het bestaan en doel van dergelijke Persoonlijke informatie, en (b) het recht op correctie en het recht om de verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie te beperken of er bezwaar tegen te maken als deze onjuist, onnauwkeurig of discriminerend is.

2. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN AUSTRALIË

We kunnen uw Persoonlijke informatie (zoals gedefinieerd door de Australische wetgeving) gebruiken en bekendmaken aan derden buiten Australië, voornamelijk in de Verenigde Staten, zoals beschreven in sectie 9 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid. U gaat ermee akkoord en erkent dat de buitenlandse ontvangers onderworpen zijn aan de privacywetgeving van hun lokale rechtsgebied en wellicht niet onderworpen zijn aan privacyverplichtingen of aan principes die vergelijkbaar zijn met de Australische privacyprincipes. Ze kunnen ook onderworpen zijn aan een buitenlandse wet die de openbaarmaking van Persoonlijke informatie aan een derde partij, zoals een overzeese autoriteit, zou kunnen afdwingen. Tenzij u ons schriftelijk op de hoogte stelt van het tegendeel, wordt u geacht toestemming te hebben gegeven voor de openbaarmaking door ons van Persoonlijke informatie aan buitenlandse ontvangers. U hebt de mogelijkheid om anoniem te blijven in uw omgang met ons, of om bepaalde Persoonlijke informatie niet aan ons bekend te maken. Dit kan echter betekenen dat we eventueel niet in staat zijn om onze Diensten aan u te leveren.

Voor inwoners van Australië zijn herzieningen van dit Privacybeleid van kracht als we uw uitdrukkelijke toestemming verkrijgen of als we een optie bieden om u af te melden wanneer essentiële wijzigingen worden aangekondigd (bijv. op onze Websites of via e-mail).

3. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN BRAZILIË

Inwoners van Brazilië hebben het recht om de volgende informatie te weten: of uw verstrekking aan ons van uw Persoonlijke informatie een contractuele vereiste is, of als het niet verstrekken van dergelijke gegevens gevolgen heeft (het antwoord is nee op beide), informatie met betrekking tot geautomatiseerde besluitvorming (inclusief profilering) die we doen (zie sectie 2.1 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid), hebt u het recht om uw toestemming voor de verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie in te trekken, en uw toegangsrechten als betrokkene (zie hieronder).

Inwoners van Brazilië hebben ook: (a) het recht om te weten, inclusief het verkrijgen van een kopie van dergelijke informatie; (b) het recht op correctie; (c) het recht om verwerking te beperken of er bezwaar tegen te maken; (d) het recht op verwijdering; (e) het recht om informatie te ontvangen over privacypraktijken over de openbare en particuliere entiteiten waaraan uw Persoonlijke informatie is doorgegeven; en, (f) het recht om een klacht in te dienen bij de Braziliaanse toezichthoudende autoriteit voor gegevens (de ANPD).

4. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN CANADA (INCLUSIEF QUEBEC)

Ons Privacybeleid en onze algemene praktijken zijn ontworpen om te voldoen aan de Canadese privacywetgeving, waaronder de Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), en, indien van toepassing, de privacywet van de privésector van Quebec, de Protection of Personal Information in the Private Sector (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Voor alle informatieverwerkingspraktijken die redelijkerwijs niet verband houden met de doeleinden waarvoor u PlugShare hebt bereikt, hebt u het recht om u af te melden voor dergelijke informatieverwerkingspraktijken (inclusief marketing, profilering, gedragsadvertenties, doorgeven aan een derde partij die geen dienstverlener is).  

Inwoners van Canada hebben het recht om zich af te melden voor ons gebruik van Persoonlijke informatie voor directe-marketingdoeleinden en andere verwerking die niet redelijkerwijs noodzakelijk is om te reageren op datgene waarvoor u ons hebt ingeschakeld.

5. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN HONGKONG

We gebruiken uw Persoonlijke informatie voor de volgende directe-marketingdoeleinden: (a) om met u te communiceren over onze producten en diensten en die van onze gelieerde ondernemingen; en (b) om u verdere kennisgevingen, promoties of ander marketingmateriaal te sturen met betrekking tot onze Websites, Producten en Diensten en die van onze gelieerde ondernemingen. Uw toestemming voor dit doel wordt gevraagd op het moment dat u Persoonlijke informatie bij ons indient (bijv. bij het aanmaken van een account, registratie van een evenement enz.).

6. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN MEXICO

Naast de hierboven gepresenteerde informatie hebben inwoners van Mexico het recht om informatie over privacypraktijken te ontvangen, inclusief (a) of uw verstrekking aan ons van uw Persoonlijke informatie een contractuele vereiste is en of er een gevolg is van het niet verstrekken van dergelijke gegevens (het antwoord is nee op beide), (b) informatie met betrekking tot geautomatiseerde besluitvorming (inclusief profilering) die we doen (die wordt besproken in sectie 2.1 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid), (c) hoelang deze wordt bewaard (zie sectie 7 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid), (d) het recht om de toestemming voor de verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie in te trekken, en, (e) uw toegangsrechten als betrokkene (zie hieronder). U hebt ook het recht om de uitdrukkelijke indicatie te weten van de gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie die moet worden verwerkt.

Inwoners van Mexico hebben ook: (a) het recht om de Persoonlijke informatie die we verzamelen te kennen, waaronder geïnformeerd worden over de openbare en particuliere entiteiten waaraan uw Persoonlijke informatie is doorgegeven en het verkrijgen van een kopie van dergelijke informatie; (b) het recht op correctie; (c) het recht om verwerking te beperken of er bezwaar tegen te maken; en (d) het recht op verwijdering.

7. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN SINGAPORE

Naast andere rechten hebt u, als wij in Singapore aanwezig zijn, het recht om uw Persoonlijke informatie die wij bezitten te laten overdragen aan een andere organisatie.

De personen of bedrijven aan wie wij uw Persoonlijke informatie bekendmaken en overdragen, kunnen zich buiten Singapore bevinden. We zorgen ervoor dat de ontvangers van de overgedragen Persoonlijke informatie in staat zijn om de overgedragen Persoonlijke informatie een beschermingsniveau te bieden dat vergelijkbaar is met de beschermingsniveaus die zijn uiteengezet in de privacywetgeving van Singapore door het gebruik van schriftelijke overeenkomsten voor gegevensoverdracht (voor overdrachten aan derden) of bindende bedrijfsregels (voor overdrachten aan onze gelieerde ondernemingen en andere entiteiten die met ons verband houden).

8. ### KENNISGEVING AAN INWONERS VAN TAIWAN

Inwoners van Taiwan hebben het recht om informatie over privacypraktijken te ontvangen.

Inwoners van Taiwan hebben ook: (a) het recht om de Persoonlijke informatie die we verzamelen te kennen, waaronder geïnformeerd worden over de openbare en particuliere entiteiten waaraan uw Persoonlijke informatie is doorgegeven en het verkrijgen van een kopie van dergelijke informatie; (b) het recht op correctie; (c) het recht om verwerking te beperken of er bezwaar tegen te maken; en (d) het recht op verwijdering.

Naast de hierboven gepresenteerde informatie, hebben inwoners van Taiwan het recht om bepaalde informatie te weten over de Persoonlijke informatie die we verzamelen, inclusief (a) of uw verstrekking aan ons van uw Persoonlijke informatie een contractuele vereiste is en of er een gevolg is van het niet verstrekken van dergelijke gegevens (het antwoord is nee op beide), (b) informatie met betrekking tot geautomatiseerde besluitvorming (inclusief profilering) die we doen (die wordt besproken in sectie 2.1 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid), (c) hoelang deze wordt bewaard (zie sectie 7 van ons belangrijkste Privacybeleid), (d) het recht om de toestemming voor de verwerking van uw Persoonlijke informatie in te trekken, en, (e) uw toegangsrechten als betrokkene (zie hieronder). U hebt ook het recht om de uitdrukkelijke indicatie te weten van de gevoelige Persoonlijke informatie die moet worden verwerkt (we verzamelen geen “gevoelige” informatie).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) De Colorado Privacy Act treedt op 1 juli 2023 in werking.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) De Utah Consumer Privacy Act treedt op 31 december 2023 in werking.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) De Connecticut Data Privacy Act treedt op 1 juli 2023 in werking.

POLITYKA PRYWATNOŚCI PLUGSHARE
==============================

DATA WEJŚCIA W ŻYCIE: 10 lipca 2023 r
-------------------------------------

Celem spółki PlugShare, LLC („PlugShare”, „my”, „nas” lub „nasz”) jest stworzenie wspierającej społeczności użytkowników pojazdów elektrycznych („EV”) oraz dostarczanie wiodących w branży informacji o ładowaniu oraz szerokiej gamy innowacyjnych produktów i usług, które pomogą uczynić wrażenia z jazdy samochodem elektrycznym jak najłatwiejszymi i jak najbardziej satysfakcjonującymi. Niniejsza Polityka prywatności określa nasze polityki dotyczące gromadzenia danych, wykorzystywania, ujawniania, przechowywania i przekazywania Danych osobowych (zdefiniowanych poniżej), które gromadzimy na temat użytkownika („użytkownik” lub „Państwo”) poprzez nasze interakcje z użytkownikiem za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn internetowych ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); lub [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); łącznie, „Witryny internetowe”), odpowiednich usług i naszych aplikacji mobilnych (łącznie „Usługi”), a także poprzez interakcje z niepowiązanymi podmiotami, takimi jak nasi dostawcy, którzy współpracują z nami przy świadczeniu naszych Usług na rzecz użytkownika.

Prosimy o uważne zapoznanie się z niniejszą Polityką prywatności. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce, abyśmy przetwarzali jego Dane osobowe, nie powinien nam ich przekazywać; może jednak wówczas nie być w stanie korzystać z niektórych funkcji naszych Usług.

Korzystanie przez użytkownika z Witryny internetowej i naszych Usług podlega przez cały czas również naszym Warunkom użytkowania (dostępnym pod adresem [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html), które mogą podlegać okresowym aktualizacjom („Warunki”)).

Niniejsza Polityka prywatności nie ma zastosowania do żadnej niestowarzyszonej witryny ani usługi, do której odnośnik można znaleźć w naszych Witrynach internetowych lub w ramach Usług, z wyjątkiem tych od naszych Usługodawców, naszych kanałów i platform na mediach społecznościowych, które hostują takie Usługi oraz wszelkich witryn i usług polecanych na naszej Witrynie internetowej lub w ramach Usług bądź przez nasz personel.

Mieszkańcy stanu Kalifornia, Wirginia, Kolorado, Utah i Connecticut: Prosimy o zapoznanie się z naszą [Dodatkową informacją o ochronie prywatności dla mieszkańców niektórych stanów USA](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) w celu uzyskania dodatkowych informacji na temat przetwarzania przez nas Państwa Danych osobowych.

Mieszkańcy innych krajów: Jeśli użytkownik jest mieszkańcem kraju innego niż Stany Zjednoczone, należy zapoznać się z naszą Dodatkową informacją o ochronie prywatności dla mieszkańców niektórych krajów poza USA znajdującą się na naszej Witrynie internetowej, aby uzyskać dodatkowe informacje na temat przetwarzania przez nas jego Danych osobowych.

Nieustannie pracujemy nad ulepszaniem naszych Usług i być może będziemy również musieli okresowo wprowadzać zmiany do niniejszej Polityki prywatności. Nasza aktualna Polityka prywatności zawsze będzie dostępna na naszej Witrynie internetowej. Prosimy pamiętać o dacie wejścia w życie niniejszej Polityki prywatności i regularnie sprawdzać aktualizacje.

1\. JAKIE DANE OSOBOWE GROMADZIMY?
==================================

1.1 CZYM SĄ DANE OSOBOWE?
-------------------------

Niniejsza Polityka prywatności obejmuje obsługę przez nas danych umożliwiających identyfikację użytkownika. „Dane osobowe” oznaczają ogólnie wszelkie niezaszyfrowane informacje, które identyfikują, odnoszą się do, opisują lub mogą być w uzasadniony sposób powiązane z konkretną osobą, takie jak między innymi imię i nazwisko, adres korespondencyjny, adres e-mail, numer telefonu itp.

Dane osobowe nie obejmują Danych osobowych użytkownika, które zostały pozbawione elementów umożliwiających identyfikację, zanonimizowane lub zagregowane w sposób wymagany na mocy obowiązujących przepisów prawa, tak aby dane te nie mogły już być wykorzystane bezpośrednio lub za pośrednictwem innych dostępnych środków do ustalenia tożsamości poszczególnej osoby (łącznie „Dane osobowe pozbawione elementów umożliwiających ustalenie tożsamości”).

1.2 KATEGORIE DANYCH OSOBOWYCH, KTÓRE GROMADZIMY I PRZETWARZAMY
---------------------------------------------------------------

Gromadzimy kilka kategorii Danych osobowych od użytkownika i na jego temat, jak podsumowano w poniższej tabeli:

| Kategoria | Dokładne rodzaje danych osobowych |
| --- | --- |
| Identyfikatory | * imię i nazwisko;<br>* nazwa użytkownika (może zawierać imię i nazwisko);<br>* adres e-mail;<br>* kod pocztowy;<br>* płeć, tożsamość płciowa;<br>* unikalny identyfikator osobisty, np. nazwa lub numer klienta lub konta, numer telefonu, identyfikator urządzenia mobilnego. |
| Dane demograficzne | * kraj zamieszkania. |
| Informacje handlowe | * historia i tendencje zakupów produktów/usług. |
| Aktywność w Internecie lub innej sieci elektronicznej; informacje o urządzeniu | * rodzaj i producent urządzenia oraz jego identyfikator/UDID lub podobny kod charakterystyczny dla urządzenia;<br>* system operacyjny i platforma;<br>* rozdzielczość ekranu;<br>* nazwa dostawcy usług internetowych lub operatora sieci komórkowej, prędkość połączenia i rodzaj połączenia;<br>* adres protokołu internetowego (lub adres IP), informacje o protokole i sekwencji;<br>* pliki cookie;<br>* znaczniki pikselowe;<br>* adres Media Access Control (MAC) odwiedzonych stron;<br>* identyfikator reklamowy urządzenia mobilnego;<br>* rodzaj przeglądarki, język i wersja;<br>* przeglądanie stron internetowych, sesje, interakcje i historia wyszukiwania, przeglądane materiały i strony, godzina i data uzyskania dostępu do stron internetowych, liczba przesłanych bajtów, liczba kliknięć na wizytę, czas spędzony na stronie, dane dotyczące kliknięć i sekwencji kliknięć, zapytania, wybrane wyniki wyszukiwania, wprowadzone komentarze;<br>* znacznik daty i adres URL ostatniej strony internetowej odwiedzonej przed odwiedzeniem naszych Witryn internetowych oraz adres URL pierwszej strony odwiedzonej po opuszczeniu naszych Witryn internetowych<br>* rodzaj żądanej usługi;<br>* nagłówki protokołów przesyłania hipertekstu, banery klienta aplikacji i serwera. |
| Geolokalizacja | * lokalizacja fizyczna i/lub ruchy. |
| Inne | * dane dotyczące ładowania pojazdu elektrycznego, marka, model i rok;<br>* informacje dobrowolnie przekazane przez użytkownika w ramach udzielania informacji zwrotnych lub udzielania odpowiedzi na inne ogólne zapytania złożone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn internetowych;<br>* wnioski wyciągnięte z którychkolwiek wymienionych informacji w celu utworzenia profilu konsumenta odzwierciedlającego preferencje, cechy, trendy psychologiczne, predyspozycje, zachowania, postawy, inteligencję, umiejętności lub zdolności konsumenta. |

1.3 GDZIE GROMADZIMY DANE OSOBOWE?
----------------------------------

Możemy gromadzić Dane osobowe bezpośrednio od użytkownika za pośrednictwem naszych Usług, gdy:

* użytkownik przekazuje nam Dane osobowe poprzez wypełnianie formularzy na naszych Witrynach internetowych lub przeprowadzanie transakcji w sklepach (należących do podmiotów nadrzędnych, zależnych i stowarzyszonych). Obejmuje to informacje podawane podczas tworzenia konta online, zakupu naszych Usług, subskrybowania naszych elektronicznych biuletynów informacyjnych lub innych komunikatów, żądania od nas informacji, przesyłania lub publikowania materiałów (jeśli jest to dozwolone) na naszych forach lub interakcji z działem obsługi klienta lub usługami, zgłaszania problemów związanych z naszymi Witrynami internetowymi, aplikacjami mobilnymi lub Usługami lub w inny sposób komunikowania się z nami;
* użytkownik kontaktuje się z nami. Obejmuje to wszystkie rejestry i kopie korespondencji z nami, np. z naszymi biurami lub obsługą klienta/wsparciem i wszelkie przesłane pocztą czeki;
* użytkownik rejestruje się na wydarzenie lub informuje nas o wszelkich żądaniach dostępności lub innych udogodnieniach;
* użytkownik odpowiada na ankiety, o których wypełnienie my lub nasi Usługodawcy możemy poprosić w celach badawczych;
* użytkownik korzysta z narzędzi do wyszukiwania w Witrynach internetowych;
* użytkownik bierze udział w programach lojalnościowych/nagrodowych;
* użytkownik składa podanie o pracę;
* użytkownik korzysta z urządzeń i sieci w celu uzyskania dostępu do naszych Usług, takich jak synchronizacja pojazdów elektrycznych z naszymi Usługami;
* użytkownik korzysta z określonych funkcji w naszych Witrynach internetowych i aplikacjach mobilnych. Mimo, iż użytkownicy mogą uzyskać dostęp do ograniczonych funkcji, takich jak przeglądanie publicznych stacji ładowania bez konta, bez ujawniania swoich Danych osobowych, gromadzimy Dane osobowe podczas rejestracji konta. Użytkownicy mogą korzystać wyłącznie ze swojego adresu e-mail i hasła w celu przeglądania ładowarek domowych. Użytkownicy mogą również skorzystać z rozszerzonych możliwości, zawierając w poście, komentując, publikując lub udostępniając społeczności dodatkowe Dane osobowe. Ogólnie rzecz biorąc, do użytkowników należy wybór w zakresie tego, ile informacji chcą wyświetlać na swój temat i mogą w każdej chwili zmienić zdanie.

Możemy również gromadzić Dane osobowe od podmiotów niestowarzyszonych, w tym:

* od dostawców danych (np. firm dostarczających dane demograficzne i inne informacje dotyczące konsumentów);
* w aplikacjach mobilnych (podmioty nadrzędne, zależne i stowarzyszone);
* od wspólnych partnerów marketingowych;
* od firm lub platform reklamowych online (np. jeśli użytkownik dobrowolnie połączy swój profil w mediach społecznościowych z naszymi Usługami);
* od dostawców usług w zakresie realizacji zamówień i dostawy;
* od firm z branży mediów społecznościowych;
* od innych usługodawców;
* w związku odpowiedziami na możliwości zatrudnienia;
* w związku z działaniami związanymi z witryną internetową/formularzem internetowym lub aplikacją;
* od dostawców usług w zakresie weryfikacji zatrudnienia lub weryfikacji danych;
* w sytuacjach, gdzie użytkownik zezwoli, za pośrednictwem ustawień urządzenia lub usług innych firm, abyśmy mogli otrzymywać dane geolokalizacyjne w celu wyświetlania lokalnych informacji (na przykład lokalnej stacji ładowania) w naszych aplikacjach mobilnych.

1.4 INFORMACJE GROMADZONE ZA POMOCĄ ZAUTOMATYZOWANYCH TECHNOLOGII
-----------------------------------------------------------------

W trakcie poruszania się po naszych Usługach i interakcji z nimi możemy również korzystać z technologii automatycznego gromadzenia danych w celu gromadzenia określonych informacji z urządzenia, przeglądarki lub innych działań sieciowych użytkownika, zgodnie z opisem w naszej Polityce dotyczącej plików cookie, dostępnej pod adresem [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Odwiedzanie Witryny internetowej a informacje o urządzeniu. Gromadzimy szczegółowe informacje na temat wizyt użytkownika na naszych Witrynach internetowych i korzystania z naszych Aplikacji mobilnych, w tym między innymi dane dotyczące ruchu, dane geolokalizacyjne, dzienniki i inne dane komunikacyjne oraz zasoby, do których użytkownik uzyskuje dostęp i z których korzysta w Witrynach internetowych. Gromadzimy informacje o komputerze, urządzeniu mobilnym i połączeniu internetowym użytkownika, w tym informacje o adresie IP, systemie operacyjnym, typie przeglądarki, wzorcach klikania (tj. tym, co użytkownik kliknął na stronie internetowej), adresie URL ostatniej witryny internetowej, którą użytkownik odwiedził przed wejściem na nasze Witryny internetowe, ilości czasu spędzonego na naszych Witrynach internetowych oraz stronach, które użytkownik przeglądał podczas ich przeglądania. Gdy użytkownik odwiedza nasze Witryny internetowe, jesteśmy w stanie oszacować przybliżoną lokalizację użytkownika na podstawie jego adresu IP. W przypadku użytkowników naszych Aplikacji mobilnych możemy również gromadzić i przechowywać historię dokładnych informacji o lokalizacji użytkownika za pomocą technologii Wi-Fi i/lub Bluetooth, a także identyfikatory urządzeń i współrzędne GPS (np. szerokość geograficzna/długość geograficzna). Aby zapobiec gromadzeniu informacji o swojej lokalizacji, należy dostosować swoje ustawienia na urządzeniu mobilnym, aby ograniczyć dostęp aplikacji mobilnej do informacji o swojej lokalizacji.

Kiedy korzystasz z naszej strony internetowej, udostępniamy informacje, które od Ciebie zbieramy, takie jak Twój adres e-mail (w postaci zaszyfrowanej), adres IP lub informacje o Twojej przeglądarce lub systemie operacyjnym, naszym partnerom/dostawcom usług tożsamości. Partnerzy ci zwracają internetowy kod identyfikacyjny, który możemy przechowywać w naszych własnych plikach cookie do wykorzystania w reklamach online, w aplikacjach i międzykanałowych, i który może być udostępniany firmom reklamowym w celu umożliwienia reklamy opartej na zainteresowaniach i ukierunkowanej. Aby zrezygnować z takiego wykorzystania, kliknij tutaj ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Śledzenie zachowań. Możemy również wykorzystywać te technologie do gromadzenia informacji na temat aktywności użytkownika w Internecie w czasie i na stronach internetowych podmiotów zewnętrznych lub w innych usługach internetowych, lub do kojarzenia Danych osobowych z innymi informacjami zebranymi w ten sposób.

Analityka lokalizacji: nasze Aplikacje mobilne i Witryny internetowe, które można przeglądać z telefonu komórkowego (np. umożliwiające weryfikację miejsca ładowania przez kierowcę), które pozwalają nam zidentyfikować lokalizację kierowcy oraz miejsce ładowania, w którym obecnie znajduje się użytkownik. Gromadzimy informacje takie jak adres IP, identyfikator urządzenia i geolokalizacja. Użytkownicy Aplikacji mobilnych mogą korzystać z Aplikacji mobilnych anonimowo lub zalogować się jako zidentyfikowany użytkownik, w którym to przypadku mogą zostać wykorzystane dane osobowe podane podczas rejestracji.

W przypadku użytkowników Aplikacji mobilnych możemy poprosić o zgodę na dostęp do określonych informacji z urządzenia mobilnego użytkownika, w tym listy kontaktów, zdjęć i filmów oraz mikrofonu i kamery. Udzielenie dostępu do tych informacji nie jest obowiązkowe. Jednak niektóre funkcje Aplikacji mobilnych mogą nie działać optymalnie, jeśli użytkownik zdecyduje się nie udzielić nam zgody.

Sygnały nawigacyjne. Strony naszych Witryn internetowych i nasze wiadomości e-mail mogą zawierać małe pliki elektroniczne znane jako sygnały nawigacyjne (nazywane również przezroczystymi gifami, tagami pikselowymi i jednopikselowymi gifami), które pozwalają nam na przykład liczyć użytkowników, którzy odwiedzili te strony lub otworzyli wiadomość e-mail oraz na potrzeby innych powiązanych statystyk witryny internetowej (na przykład rejestrowanie popularności określonych treści witryny internetowej i sprawdzanie integralności systemu i serwera).

Śledzenie pikseli. Oprócz korzystania z plików cookie Witryny internetowe mogą stosować „śledzenie pikseli”. Śledzenie pikseli polega na użyciu znaczników pikselowych, które nie są widoczne dla użytkownika i składają się z kilku wierszy kodu komputerowego. Śledzenie pikseli mierzy skuteczność reklam i opracowuje zbiorcze i konkretne statystyki użytkowania. Możemy uzyskiwać dostęp do tych znaczników pikselowych w celu identyfikacji aktywności i zainteresowań, które mogą umożliwić nam lepsze dopasowanie naszych Produktów, Usług i ofert do zainteresowań i potrzeb użytkownika. Dla przykładu, jeśli użytkownik odwiedza nasze Witryny internetowe z reklamy znajdującej się na innej witrynie internetowej, tag pikselowy pozwoli reklamodawcy śledzić, czy jego reklama doprowadziła użytkownika do Witryn internetowych. Jeśli użytkownik odwiedza nasze Witryny internetowe i łączymy go z inną witryną internetową, możemy również być w stanie określić, czy użytkownik został wysłany do witryny internetowej podmiotu zewnętrznego i/lub zawierał z nią transakcje.

Piki GIF. Możemy używać małych obrazów znanych jako czyste pliki GIF w celu śledzenia zachowań użytkowników, w tym do sporządzania statystyk dotyczących tego, kto otwiera nasze wiadomości e-mail.

Adres IP. Nasze serwery (lub serwery naszych dostawców usług) automatycznie rejestrują określone informacje z plików dziennika zgłoszone z przeglądarki użytkownika podczas uzyskiwania dostępu do Witryn internetowych. Te dzienniki serwera mogą obejmować informacje, takie jak odwiedzone strony Witryn internetowych, adres protokołu internetowego („IP”), typ przeglądarki oraz inne informacje dotyczące interakcji użytkownika z Witrynami internetowymi. Te pliki dziennika są zazwyczaj okresowo usuwane.

Wskaźniki i analizy stron trzecich. Wskaźniki i analizy osób trzecich mogą być wykorzystywane na niektórych stronach lub w niektórych funkcjach Usług, aby pomóc nam zrozumieć i przeanalizować ruch odwiedzających, mierzyć skuteczność promocyjną i skuteczność naszych funkcji, ofert i kampanii marketingowych. Używamy tych narzędzi również do identyfikowania uchybień, niedociągnięć i obszarów naszej działalności, które wymagają poprawy, a także w ramach sprawdzenia naszych ogólnych wyników i naszej obecności w Internecie. Narzędzia te mogą przechowywać pliki cookie na urządzeniu użytkownika według swego uznania.

OŚWIADCZENIE I POLITYKA DOTYCZĄCA PLIKÓW COOKIE

Technologie wykorzystywane do automatycznego gromadzenia danych obejmują również pliki cookie opisane poniżej.

Pliki cookie przeglądarki

Pliki cookie przeglądarki to małe pliki umieszczane na dysku twardym komputera lub urządzenia mobilnego. Mogą one zawierać pewne dane, w tym między innymi nazwę serwera, który je umieścił, identyfikator w postaci unikalnego numeru oraz datę ważności (tylko niektóre pliki cookie). Pliki cookie przeglądarki są zarządzane przez przeglądarkę internetową (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome itp.) na komputerze lub urządzeniu mobilnym użytkownika. W naszych Witrynach internetowych wykorzystywane są różne rodzaje plików cookie, które mają różne cele.

Niezbędne pliki cookie

Niezbędne pliki cookie są konieczne, aby umożliwić użytkownikowi przeglądanie naszych Witryn internetowych i korzystanie z ich funkcjonalności. Bez nich usługi, takie jak koszyki zakupowe i fakturowanie elektroniczne, nie byłyby w stanie działać.

Pliki cookie związane z wydajnością

Pliki cookie związane z wydajnością gromadzą informacje na temat korzystania z naszych Witryn internetowych, takie jak najczęściej przeglądane strony. Informacje te umożliwiają nam optymalizację naszych Witryn internetowych i uproszczenie przeglądania. Pliki cookie dotyczące wydajności umożliwiają również naszym spółkom stowarzyszonym i partnerom sprawdzenie, czy użytkownik uzyskał dostęp do jednej z naszych Witryn internetowych z ich witryny oraz czy wizyta użytkownika doprowadziła do skorzystania z lub zakupu Produktu bądź Usługi z naszych Witryn internetowych, włącznie z odniesieniami do zakupionych Produktów lub Usług. Wszystkie informacje gromadzone przez pliki cookie dotyczące wydajności są zagregowane, a więc również anonimowe.

Pliki cookie związane z funkcjonalnością

Pliki cookie związane z funkcjonalnością umożliwiają naszym Witrynom internetowym zapamiętywanie wyborów dokonanych przez użytkownika podczas przeglądania. Możemy na przykład przechowywać lokalizację geograficzną użytkownika w pliku cookie, aby wyświetlane były Witryny internetowe odpowiednie dla jego obszaru. Możemy również zapamiętać preferencje użytkownika, takie jak rozmiar tekstu, czcionka i inne konfigurowalne aspekty Witryn internetowych. Pliki cookie związane z funkcjonalnością mogą również śledzić przeglądane produkty lub filmy, aby uniknąć ich powtarzania. Informacje gromadzone przez te pliki cookie nie mogą być wykorzystywane do identyfikacji użytkownika i nie mogą monitorować jego aktywności w witrynach internetowych, które nie należą do nas. Funkcjonalne pliki cookie umożliwiają nam wyświetlanie w naszych Witrynach internetowych reklam dostosowanych do użytkownika, zrozumienie, które części naszych treści najbardziej go interesują oraz które kategorie produktów lub usług użytkownik zamawia. Niektórzy z naszych usługodawców mogą umieszczać pliki cookie w naszych Witrynach internetowych. Firmy te mogą również zapewnić użytkownikowi możliwość zapobiegania wykorzystywaniu plików cookie w przyszłości.

Użytkownik może w dowolnym momencie uniemożliwić lub zrezygnować z dalszego korzystania z niektórych plików cookie, aktywując odpowiednie ustawienie w przeglądarce, aby odmówić akceptacji plików cookie przeglądarki. Jednak w takim przypadku może to wpłynąć na korzystanie z naszych Witryn internetowych; np. użytkownik może nie mieć dostępu do niektórych części naszych Witryn internetowych. O ile użytkownik nie dostosował ustawień przeglądarki tak, aby odrzucała pliki cookie, nasz system będzie umieszczał pliki cookie na urządzeniu użytkownika po przekierowaniu przeglądarki na nasze Witryny internetowe.

Lokalne pliki cookie

Niektóre funkcje naszych Witryn internetowych mogą wykorzystywać lokalnie przechowywane obiekty (do gromadzenia i przechowywania informacji o preferencjach użytkownika i nawigacji do, z i na naszych Witrynach internetowych). Lokalne pliki cookie nie są zarządzane przez takie same ustawienia przeglądarki, jak w przypadku plików cookie przeglądarki.

Możemy również łączyć Dane osobowe, które gromadzimy od użytkownika poza naszymi Witrynami internetowymi albo Usługami z Danymi osobowymi, które są gromadzone za pośrednictwem naszych Witryn internetowych albo Usług albo w inny sposób, jak opisano powyżej.

1.5 INFORMACJE O URZĄDZENIU, SIECI, GEOLOKALIZACJI I POJEŹDZIE ELEKTRYCZNYM
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

Gdy użytkownik odwiedza lub opuszcza nasze Witryny internetowe lub Usługi, klikając hiperłącze lub wyświetlając wtyczkę w witrynie internetowej podmiotu zewnętrznego, automatycznie otrzymujemy adres URL witryny, z której użytkownik przyszedł lub witryny, do której jest skierowany. Ponadto, gdy użytkownik kliknie reklamę, która może pojawić się w naszych Usługach, reklamodawcy otrzymują adres URL strony, na której znajduje się użytkownik. Otrzymujemy również adres protokołu internetowego („IP”) komputera użytkownika lub serwera proxy, z którego użytkownik korzysta do uzyskania dostępu do Internetu, szczegóły systemu operacyjnego komputera, rodzaj przeglądarki internetowej, informacje dotyczące urządzenia mobilnego użytkownika (w tym identyfikator urządzenia mobilnego dostarczony przez system operacyjny urządzenia mobilnego), informacje dotyczące mobilnego systemu operacyjnego użytkownika (jeśli użytkownik uzyskuje dostęp do naszych witryn internetowych lub usług za pomocą urządzenia mobilnego) oraz nazwę usługodawcy internetowego lub operatora sieci komórkowej użytkownika.

1.6 ANKIETY
-----------

My lub podmioty niepowiązane możemy przeprowadzać ankiety użytkowników dotyczące naszych Usług. Niektóre niepowiązane z nami podmioty mogą kierować do użytkownika reklamy lub promocje na podstawie jego odpowiedzi w ankiecie. My lub podmioty niepowiązane opracowujemy nowe programy lub produkty w oparciu o informacje, które użytkownik udostępnia w ankietach. Możemy korzystać z usług podmiotów niepowiązanych w ramach zapewnienia użytkownikowi zachęt finansowych lub innych celem skłonienia użytkownika do udziału w ankietach. Jeśli dostarczenie zachęt wymaga podania danych kontaktowych, użytkownik może zostać poproszony o podanie Danych osobowych niepowiązanemu podmiotowi realizującemu taką zachęcającą ofertę, które zostaną wykorzystane wyłącznie w celu dostarczenia obiecanych zachęt i weryfikacji jego danych kontaktowych. To od użytkownika zależy, czy przekaże on te informacje bądź czy chce skorzystać z takiej oferty. O zgodę użytkownika na wykorzystywanie jakichkolwiek Danych osobowych w celach określonych w ankiecie wyraźnie poprosi niepowiązany podmiot wykorzystujący te dane. Aby zrezygnować z naszych ankiet, użytkownik może przesłać do nas swoją prośbę, korzystając z poniższych danych kontaktowych.

2\. CHARAKTER I CEL PRZETWARZANIA DANYCH OSOBOWYCH
==================================================

Wykorzystujemy informacje, które gromadzimy na temat użytkownika lub które użytkownik nam przekazuje, w tym wszelkie Dane osobowe, w jednym lub kilku z następujących celów:

* prezentowanie użytkownikowi naszych Witryn internetowych i aplikacji mobilnych oraz ich zawartości;
* dostarczanie użytkownikowi informacji i udzielanie odpowiedzi na pytania dotyczące Produktów lub Usług, o które użytkownik prosi, oraz informacji na temat nowych produktów i usług, rabatów, specjalnych promocji lub nadchodzących wydarzeń, a także funkcji lub ofert, które naszym zdaniem będą interesujące dla użytkownika lub dotyczących promocji, konkursu lub loterii, w których użytkownik uczestniczył;
* przetwarzanie informacji o koncie i płatności transakcyjnych, w tym między innymi o opłatach za Produkt lub Usługę oraz płatnościach i zwrotach za wszelkie zakupione Produkty lub Usługi (z zastrzeżeniem, że nie otrzymamy pełnego numeru karty kredytowej lub debetowej);
* przetwarzanie rabatów, ofert, nagród lojalnościowych i/lub wniosków rabatowych, formularzy i innych wniosków oraz koordynacja z producentem, sprzedawcą detalicznym i/lub hurtownikiem;
* dostarczanie użytkownikowi powiadomień o jego koncie, w tym powiadomień o wygaśnięciu i odnowieniu;
* powiadamianie użytkownika o informacjach lub zmianach dotyczących naszych Witryn internetowych, naszych polityk, warunków lub jakichkolwiek Produktów bądź Usług, które oferujemy lub dostarczamy oraz informacjach lub zmianach dotyczących jego konta;
* przetwarzanie Danych osobowych lub innych informacji, które użytkownik nam przekazuje;
* umożliwianie użytkownikowi korzystania z interaktywnych funkcji w naszych Witrynach internetowych;
* rozwijanie i ulepszanie naszych Produktów i Usług oraz opracowywanie nowych, na przykład poprzez analizę trendów użytkowników oraz pomiar danych demograficznych i zainteresowań;
* do wewnętrznej obsługi Witryny internetowej, Usług i systemu, administracji, konserwacji, audytów wewnętrznych i przeglądów, diagnozowania problemów technicznych i utrzymania bezpieczeństwa;
* badanie wszelkich naruszeń naszych Warunków użytkowania lub niniejszej Polityki prywatności;
* śledzenie potencjalnych problemów i trendów związanych z korzystaniem przez użytkowników z naszych Witryn internetowych i Usług oraz dostosowywanie naszego wsparcia w celu lepszej obsługi użytkownika;
* dostarczanie naszym Usługodawcom statystyk dotyczących poziomów użytkowania Witryn internetowych i innych powiązanych informacji;
* powiadamianie użytkownika o incydentach związanych z prywatnością danych lub przekazywanie mu informacji wymaganych przez prawo;
* zapraszanie użytkownika do udziału w ratingach, ocenach, ankietach, grupach fokusowych lub innych inicjatywach, które pomagają nam gromadzić informacje wykorzystywane do opracowywania i ulepszania naszych Produktów i Usług;
* realizowanie wszelkich innych celów, w związku z którymi użytkownik przekazuje Dane osobowe;
* dowolny cel, który opiszemy i na jaki uzyskamy zgodę użytkownika w chwili, gdy ten przekazuje informacje.

Używamy plików cookie, przezroczystych plików GIF i informacji o pliku dziennika aby: (a) zapamiętać informacje, aby nie trzeba było ich ponownie wprowadzać podczas wizyty lub przy następnej wizycie na Witrynach internetowych; (b) zapewnić spersonalizowane treści i informacje; (c) monitorować skuteczność naszych Usług; (d) monitorować wskaźniki zbiorcze, takie jak całkowita liczba odwiedzających, ruch uliczny i modele demograficzne; (e) diagnozować lub naprawiać problemy techniczne zgłaszane przez naszych użytkowników lub inżynierów, które są powiązane z określonymi adresami IP; i/lub (f) pomóc użytkownikowi w skutecznym dostępie do informacji po zalogowaniu.

Dane statystyczne, które gromadzimy automatycznie, pomagają nam ulepszać nasze Witryny internetowe i dostarczać lepsze i bardziej spersonalizowane Produkty i Usługi, w tym między innymi poprzez umożliwienie nam: określania naszych odbiorców/odwiedzających i wzorców użytkowania, przechowywania informacji o preferencjach użytkownika, umożliwiania nam dostosowywania i ulepszania naszych Witryn internetowych, przyspieszania wyszukiwania i/lub rozpoznawania użytkownika po powrocie na nasze Witryny internetowe.

Możemy gromadzić i wykorzystywać informacje dotyczące sesji ładowania pojazdów elektrycznych (np. czas ładowania, zużycie energii, właściciel stacji i dane itp.) oraz marki, modelu i roku pojazdu do zarządzania kontem użytkownika, na przykład w celu rozróżnienia wielu pojazdów lub użytkowników korzystających z jednego konta oraz w celach analitycznych.

W zakresie, w jakim użytkownik nie wyraża zgody na praktyki dotyczące przetwarzania informacji określone w niniejszym dokumencie, może mieć prawo do rezygnacji z takich praktyk. Wszystkie wnioski o rezygnację należy kierować na adres [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). W zakresie, w jakim wnioski o rezygnację są uznawane, będą miały wpływ na przyszłe przetwarzanie, a nie na przetwarzanie, które miało miejsce na podstawie uprzedniej zgody.

2.1 ZAUTOMATYZOWANE PODEJMOWANIE DECYZJI
----------------------------------------

Możemy wykorzystywać przekazane nam przez użytkownika Dane osobowe, które pozyskujemy z innych źródeł, aby lepiej zrozumieć jego zainteresowania, abyśmy mogli spróbować przewidzieć, jakie inne Produkty, Usługi i informacje mogą go najbardziej zainteresować. Praktyka ta polega na podejmowaniu zautomatyzowanych decyzji na podstawie tych informacji, aby lepiej dostosować nasze interakcje z użytkownikiem tak, aby były one bardziej dopasowane i interesujące. Użytkownikowi przysługuje prawo wnieść sprzeciw wobec tego działania w dowolnym momencie lub poprosić nas o więcej informacji na temat metodologii stosowanej w naszych zautomatyzowanych procesach podejmowania decyzji, kontaktując się z nami (patrz punkt 12 poniżej).

2.2 WIADOMOŚCI TEKSTOWE
-----------------------

Nasze Usługi mogą obejmować wysyłanie użytkownikowi wiadomości tekstowych („SMS”), co może obejmować dostarczanie użytkownikowi do dwóch wiadomości dziennie na jego urządzenie bezprzewodowe (chyba że użytkownik się z nami w tej sprawie skontaktuje), z zastrzeżeniem, że częstotliwość wysyłania wiadomości może się różnić.  Wyrażając zgodę na otrzymywanie od nas wiadomości tekstowych i podając numer telefonu komórkowego, użytkownik wyraża zgodę na otrzymywanie cyklicznych wiadomości informacyjnych i transakcyjnych od nas lub wysyłanych w naszym imieniu na podany przez użytkownika numer. Wyrażając zgodę na otrzymywanie od nas wiadomości SMS i podając swój numer telefonu komórkowego, użytkownik gwarantuje i oświadcza, że to on jest właścicielem określonego numeru telefonu. Możemy wykorzystywać dane użytkownika w celu kontaktowania się z nim w sprawie jego użytkowania, zakupów, zwrotów (jeśli są dostępne), aktualizacji dotyczących Witryn internetowych, przeprowadzania ankiet lub komunikatów informacyjnych i związanych z usługami, w tym ważnych aktualizacji bezpieczeństwa. Po wysłaniu do nas wiadomości SMS o treści „STOP” wyślemy użytkownikowi wiadomość SMS z potwierdzeniem anulowania subskrypcji. Użytkownik może też przesłać nam swoje żądanie pocztą elektroniczną, wysyłając wiadomość, w treści której należy pamiętać o umieszczeniu adresu e-mail i numeru telefonu podanego podczas rejestracji lub korzystając z innych uzasadnionych środków. Następnie użytkownik nie będzie już więcej otrzymywał od nas wiadomości SMS. W przypadku chęci ponownego dołączenia, użytkownik powinien zarejestrować się tak samo, jak zrobił to za pierwszym razem, a my zaczniemy wysyłać mu wiadomości SMS. Aby uzyskać pomoc, należy odpowiedzieć na dowolnego SMS-a wysyłając wiadomość o treści POMOC. W zależności od planu telefonii komórkowej mogą obowiązywać opłaty za wiadomości i dane. Operatorzy nie ponoszą odpowiedzialności za opóźnione lub niedostarczone wiadomości.

2.3 WTYCZKI MEDIÓW SPOŁECZNOŚCIOWYCH
------------------------------------

W Witrynach internetowych integrujemy interfejsy lub wtyczki programów mediów społecznościowych („Wtyczki”) z serwisów społecznościowych takich jak Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest i/lub ewentualnie innych firm. Dzięki temu użytkownik może mieć możliwość zarejestrowania się u nas logując się do swojego konta w serwisie Facebook lub na innym portalu społecznościowym.

Dla przykładu, gdy użytkownik odwiedza nasze Witryny internetowe, wtyczka tworzy bezpośrednie połączenie pomiędzy przeglądarką użytkownika a serwerem Facebook. Umożliwia to Facebookowi otrzymywanie informacji o wizycie użytkownika na naszych Witrynach internetowych z adresem IP użytkownika. Jeśli użytkownik kliknie przycisk „Lubię to” na Facebooku podczas logowania się do swojego konta na Facebooku, może połączyć zawartość naszych Witryn internetowych ze swoim profilem na Facebooku. Dzięki temu Facebook może przypisać wizytę użytkownika na naszych Witrynach internetowych do jego konta użytkownika. Należy pamiętać, że jako dostawca Witryn internetowych nie otrzymujemy powiadomienia o treści przesyłanych danych ani ich wykorzystaniu przez serwis Facebook. Jeśli użytkownik nie chce, aby serwis Facebook przypisał jego wizytę na naszych Witrynach internetowych do jego konta użytkownika serwisu Facebooka, należy wylogować się ze swojego konta użytkownika serwisu Facebook.

W przypadku logowania za pomocą wtyczki mediów społecznościowych, użytkownik upoważnia nas do dostępu do określonych informacji o koncie z danej strony mediów społecznościowych, takich jak profil użytkownika w mediach społecznościowych (zgodnie z ustawieniami prywatności w witrynie mediów społecznościowych), adres e-mail, zainteresowania, polubienia, płeć, urodziny, historia wykształcenia, relacje, zainteresowania, aktualne miasto, zdjęcia, osobisty opis, listy znajomych, oraz informacje o i zdjęcia znajomych ze strony użytkownika w mediach społecznościowych, którzy mogą być wspólnymi znajomymi innych użytkowników tego samego portalu. Wtyczki mogą przesyłać informacje o użytkowniku na odpowiednią platformę wtyczki bez podejmowania działań przez użytkownika. Informacje te mogą obejmować numer identyfikacyjny użytkownika platformy, stronę internetową, na której użytkownik się znajduje i inne informacje. Interakcja z Wtyczką spowoduje przesyłanie informacji bezpośrednio do sieci społecznościowej tej Wtyczki i informacje te mogą być widoczne dla innych osób na tej platformie. Wtyczki są kontrolowane przez politykę prywatności danej witryny mediów społecznościowych (dostępną na jej stronie internetowej), a nie przez naszą Politykę prywatności.

3\. W JAKI SPOSÓB UJAWNIAMY DANE OSOBOWE STRONOM NIEPOWIĄZANYM?
===============================================================

3.1 RODZAJE NIEPOWIĄZANYCH STRON
--------------------------------

Możemy ujawniać lub ujawniamy Dane osobowe użytkownika, w całości lub w części, następującym rodzajom stron niepowiązanych oraz w jednym lub kilku z następujących celów:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Rodzaj niepowiązanej strony | Cel |
| Dostawcy usług w zakresie przechowywania lub hostingu danych | Bezpieczne przechowywanie i przesyłanie danych |
| Dostawcy usług w zakresie baz danych i oprogramowania | Zarządzanie danymi i śledzenie ich |
| Konsultanci ds. prawnych i zgodności, tacy jak zewnętrzni doradcy, zewnętrzni audytorzy lub konsultanci podatkowi | Świadczenie profesjonalnych usług na naszą rzecz |
| Dostawcy usług w zakresie zarządzania tożsamością | Cele związane z uwierzytelnianiem |
| Dostawcy rozwiązań w zakresie płatności | Bezpieczne przetwarzanie płatności przekazywanych nam przez użytkownika |
| Producenci, sprzedawcy detaliczni i hurtownicy | Składanie, przetwarzanie i zarządzanie rabatami, zniżkami, ofertami, nagrodami lojalnościowymi itp. |
| Dostawcy usług w zakresie realizacji zamówień i wysyłki | Realizacja zamówienia i dostawa Produktów, Usług i towarów |
| Dostawcy usług badań, w tym badań ankietowych | Prowadzenie badań w naszym imieniu |
| Partnerzy reklamowi, w tym dostawcy mediów społecznościowych | Dostarczanie ukierunkowanych reklam |

W przypadku wszelkich transferów Danych osobowych, które nie są w uzasadniony sposób niezbędne do osiągnięcia celów, dla których użytkownik wchodzi w interakcję z PlugShare (np. do celów marketingowych lub ankietowych), użytkownik ma prawo do rezygnacji z takiego przetwarzania. Aby skorzystać z prawa do rezygnacji, prosimy o kontakt pod adresem [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 USŁUGODAWCY, PARTNERZY BIZNESOWI I PODWYKONAWCY
---------------------------------------------------

 Możemy udostępniać Dane osobowe użytkownika Usługodawcom, którzy świadczą usługi w naszym imieniu, zgodnie z opisem powyżej. Usługodawcy tego typu mogą mieć dostęp do Danych osobowych użytkownika w celu świadczenia określonych usług na naszą rzecz lub w naszym imieniu. Jeśli zatrudnimy Usługodawców do realizacji któregokolwiek z powyższych celów, wykorzystanie Danych osobowych użytkownika będzie związane zobowiązaniem do zachowania poufności, a wykorzystanie przez nich Danych osobowych będzie ograniczone do świadczenia nam ich usług. Możemy przechowywać Dane osobowe w miejscach pozostających poza naszą bezpośrednią kontrolą (na przykład na serwerach lub w bazach danych zlokalizowanych w całości lub częściowo u Usługodawców świadczących usługi hostingu danych).  

3.3 REKLAMA BEHAWIORALNA O RÓŻNYCH KONTEKSTACH
----------------------------------------------

Jesteśmy zobowiązani do ujawnienia, czy udostępniamy Dane osobowe stronie trzeciej, która jest zaangażowana w (ukierunkowane) reklamy behawioralne o różnych kontekstach. W ciągu ostatnich dwunastu (12) miesięcy ujawniliśmy lub mogliśmy ujawnić następujące kategorie Danych osobowych w kontekście, który na mocy pewnych przepisów prawa (np. CPRA, RODO lub RODO w Wielkiej Brytanii) może być uznany za sprzedaż:

* identyfikatory;
* aktywność w Internecie lub innej podobnej sieci;
* dane geolokalizacyjne;

Użytkownik może zrezygnować z bycia uwzględnionym w takich ujawnieniach, klikając monity o rezygnację, które pojawią się w powiadomieniu, które użytkownik otrzymuje podczas pierwszej wizyty w naszych aplikacjach mobilnych lub Witrynach internetowych.

3.4 TRANSAKCJE BIZNESOWE
------------------------

Użytkownik przyjmuje do wiadomości (i nie będzie sprzeciwiać się) naszemu ujawnieniu lub przekazaniu jego Danych osobowych, Danych osobowych pozbawionych elementów umożliwiających ustalenie tożsamości oraz innych informacji, które użytkownik nam przekazuje, jak również praw przyznanych lub potwierdzonych przez użytkownika w niniejszej Polityce prywatności (łącznie „Przekazywane informacje”) potencjalnemu lub faktycznemu nabywcy naszej firmy lub ją przejmującemu lub innemu następcy w celu rozważenia lub przeprowadzenia fuzji, zbycia, restrukturyzacji, reorganizacji, rozwiązania, zmiany kontroli lub przeniesienia części lub całości naszych aktywów (każde z powyższych zwane jest „Przekazaniem informacji”), czy to w ramach dalszego prowadzenia działalności, czy to w związku z upadłością, likwidacją lub innym postępowaniem sądowym, w którym przechowywane przez nas Dane osobowe znajdują się wśród przekazywanych aktywów, i zobowiązuje się nie sprzeciwiać takiemu ujawnieniu i/lub przekazaniu. Nie możemy składać żadnych oświadczeń dotyczących wykorzystywania lub przekazywania Przekazywanych informacji, które możemy mieć w przypadku naszej upadłości, reorganizacji, niewypłacalności, ustanowienia zarządcy komisarycznego lub cesji na rzecz wierzycieli. Ponadto, z wyjątkiem przypadków wymaganych przez prawo, nie ponosimy i nie będziemy ponosić odpowiedzialności za jakiekolwiek naruszenie bezpieczeństwa przez jakiekolwiek niepowiązane strony ani za żadne działania jakichkolwiek niepowiązanych stron, które otrzymują jakiekolwiek Przekazywane informacje, które zostały nam ujawnione.

3.5 WYMAGANE UJAWNIENIA; OCHRONA PRAW; BEZPIECZEŃSTWO
-----------------------------------------------------

O ile niniejsza Polityka prywatności nie stanowi inaczej, nie ujawnimy Państwa Danych osobowych żadnej stronie niepowiązanej, chyba że będzie to wymagane przez prawo, nakaz sądowy, proces prawny (np. wezwanie sądowe), w tym, ale nie tylko, aby odpowiedzieć na jakiekolwiek wezwanie ze strony organu rządowego, regulacyjnego bądź udzielającego licencji/pozwoleń, lub jeśli uważamy, że takie działanie jest niezbędne do: (a) przestrzegania przepisów prawa, przestrzegania procedur prawnych dotyczących nas lub naszych podmiotów stowarzyszonych, spółek zależnych, zakontraktowanych dostawców lub powiązanych partnerów, lub dochodzenia, zapobiegania lub podejmowania działań w odniesieniu do podejrzewanych lub faktycznych działań niezgodnych z prawem; (b) egzekwowania naszych Warunków lub umowy z klientem (w tym w celach rozliczeniowych i windykacyjnych); (c) podejmowania środków ostrożności w zakresie odpowiedzialności; (d) dochodzenia i obrony przed roszczeniami lub zarzutami osób trzecich; (e) pomocy rządowym organom ścigania lub spełnienia krajowych lub innych rządowych wymogów bezpieczeństwa; (f) ochrony bezpieczeństwa lub integralności naszych Witryn internetowych, Usług i Aplikacji mobilnych; lub (g) wykonywania lub ochrony praw, nieruchomości lub bezpieczeństwa osobistego, naszych użytkowników lub innych osób. 

W miarę możliwości postaramy się powiadomić użytkownika o takich żądaniach, chyba że: (i) powiadomienie jest zabronione przez sam proces prawny, na podstawie nakazu sądowego, który otrzymujemy lub na mocy obowiązującego prawa lub (ii) uważamy, że powiadomienie byłoby bezsensowne, nieskuteczne, stwarzałoby ryzyko obrażeń ciała lub innych szkód dla osoby lub grupy, lub stworzyło lub zwiększyło ryzyko oszustwa wobec nas, naszych użytkowników, naszych Witryn internetowych, Usług lub aplikacji mobilnych. W przypadkach, w których będziemy spełniać żądania prawne bez powiadomienia z tych powodów, postaramy się powiadomić tego użytkownika o żądaniu po fakcie, jeśli w dobrej wierze stwierdzimy, że nie mamy już prawnego zakazu takiego działania i nie mają zastosowania żadne scenariusze ryzyka opisane w niniejszym paragrafie.

3.6 UJAWNIANIE ZANONIMIZOWANYCH DANYCH OSOBOWYCH
------------------------------------------------

Możemy udostępniać Dane osobowe pozbawione elementów umożliwiających ustalenie tożsamości (w tym w szczególności anonimowe dane dotyczące użytkowania, strony i adresy URL odsyłające/wyjściowe, adres IP, rodzaje platform, liczba kliknięć itp.) stronom niepowiązanym w dowolny sposób i w dowolnym celu, na przykład: w celu administrowania systemem i monitorowania korzystania z Witryn internetowych; w celu pomiaru liczby wizyt na naszych Witrynach internetowych, średniego czasu poświęconego na korzystanie z nich, liczby wyświetlanych stron; oraz monitorowania różnych innych statystyk Witryny internetowej w celu poprawy treści.

4\.  POLECENIA „NIE ŚLEDŹ”
==========================

Niektóre przeglądarki internetowe (w tym Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox i Chrome) posiadają funkcję „Nie śledź” („Do Not Track, DNT”) lub podobną, która sygnalizuje witrynom internetowym, że użytkownik nie życzy sobie, aby jego aktywność i zachowanie w Internecie były śledzone. Jeżeli witryna internetowa odpowiadająca na określony sygnał DNT otrzyma sygnał DNT, przeglądarka może zablokować gromadzenie przez tę witrynę pewnych informacji o użytkowniku przeglądarki. Nie wszystkie przeglądarki oferują opcję DNT, a polecenia DNT nie są jeszcze jednolite. Z tego powodu wielu operatorów stron internetowych, w tym PlugShare, nie reaguje na sygnały DNT.

5\. WIADOMOŚCI PLUGSHARE, PREFERENCJE I REZYGNACJA
==================================================

Przekazując nam swój adres e-mail, użytkownik wyraża zgodę na wykorzystywanie przez nas adresu e-mail do wysyłania powiadomień związanych z Usługą pocztą elektroniczną, w tym między innymi wszelkich powiadomień wymaganych przez prawo (np. powiadomienia o prywatności danych lub incydentach związanych z bezpieczeństwem), zamiast komunikacji pocztą tradycyjną. Użytkownik zgadza się również, że możemy wysyłać mu powiadomienia o aktywności dotyczącej naszych Produktów, Usług, Witryn internetowych, aplikacji mobilnych, Danych osobowych użytkownika lub dowolnego aspektu naszej relacji na podany przez niego adres e-mail, zgodnie z obowiązującymi ustawieniami prywatności. Możemy wykorzystywać adres e-mail użytkownika do wysyłania mu innych wiadomości lub treści, takich jak m.in. newslettery, dodatki lub zmiany w funkcjach Usługi lub oferty specjalne. Jeśli użytkownik nie życzy sobie otrzymywać takich wiadomości e-mail, może z nich zrezygnować, klikając opcję Anuluj subskrypcję tam, gdzie jest ona dostępna. Rezygnacja może uniemożliwić otrzymywanie wiadomości e-mail dotyczących aktualizacji, ulepszeń, specjalnych funkcji, ogłoszeń lub ofert. Użytkownik nie może zrezygnować z otrzymywania wiadomości e-mail związanych z Usługą. Jeśli użytkownik zdecydował się nie przekazywać nam adresu e-mail ani innego adresu, może nie otrzymywać wiadomości e-mail związanych z Usługą.

Za pośrednictwem strony ustawień konta użytkownika użytkownik może uzyskać dostęp do określonych informacji, które nam przekazał, takich jak imię i nazwisko, hasło, adres e-mail, adres, informacje o profilu użytkownika itp., a w niektórych przypadkach może je edytować lub usuwać. Informacje, które użytkownik może przeglądać, aktualizować i usuwać, mogą ulec zmianie wraz ze zmianą Produktów, Witryn internetowych, Usług lub naszych praktyk. W razie jakichkolwiek pytań dotyczących przeglądania lub aktualizowania informacji, które posiadamy na temat użytkownika, prosimy o kontakt. Jednak w przypadku aktualizacji informacji możemy zachować kopię niepoprawionych informacji w naszej dokumentacji. Użytkownik może zażądać usunięcia swojego konta, wysyłając do nas wiadomość e-mail. Obowiązkiem użytkownika jest zachowanie u nas aktualnego adresu e-mail. W zależności od stanu lub kraju zamieszkania użytkownika mogą przysługiwać mu dodatkowe prawa. Więcej informacji znajduje się poniżej.

6\. PROGRAMIŚCI KORZYSTAJĄCY Z USŁUG PLATFORMY PLUGSHARE
========================================================

Współpracujemy z podmiotami zewnętrznymi i umożliwiamy im korzystanie z platformy programistycznej PlugShare w celu oferowania usług i funkcjonalności w połączeniu z PlugShare. Ci zewnętrzni programiści wynegocjowali umowę dotyczącą korzystania z technologii platformy PlugShare lub zgodzili się na stosowanie przez nas samoobsługowych interfejsów programowania aplikacji („API”) i warunków dotyczących wtyczek z myślą o tworzeniu aplikacji platformy oprogramowania („Aplikacje platformy”). Zarówno wynegocjowane umowy, jak i nasze API i warunki korzystania z wtyczek zawierają ograniczenia dotyczące tego, w jaki sposób podmioty zewnętrzne mogą uzyskiwać dostęp, przechowywać i wykorzystywać Dane osobowe przekazane przez użytkownika PlugShare. Jeśli użytkownik zdecyduje się korzystać z Aplikacji platformy, zostanie poproszony o potwierdzenie akceptacji polityki prywatności i zgody użytkownika zewnętrznego dewelopera. Aby wycofać pozwolenie na korzystanie z Aplikacji platformy, należy przejść do ustawień. Należy jednak pamiętać, że nawet po wycofaniu zgody na korzystanie z Aplikacji platformy, osoby powiązane z użytkownikiem będą mogły nadal korzystać z Aplikacji platformy, więc Aplikacja platformy może nadal mieć dostęp do pewnych informacji na temat użytkownika, takich jak osoby z nim powiązane.

7\. PRZECHOWYWANIE DANYCH OSOBOWYCH
===================================

Okres, przez jaki przechowujemy Dane osobowe użytkownika, zależy od celów, dla których je wykorzystujemy. Będziemy przechowywać Dane osobowe użytkownika tak długo, jak jego konto będzie aktywne, tak długo, jak użytkownik jest zarejestrowanym posiadaczem konta lub użytkownikiem naszych Usług, lub tak długo, jak mamy w tym inny cel biznesowy (np. między innymi cele biznesowe, podatkowe lub prawne), a następnie nie dłużej niż jest to wymagane lub dozwolone przez prawo lub naszą politykę przechowywania dokumentacji, w uzasadnionym zakresie niezbędnym do celów wewnętrznej sprawozdawczości i uzgadniania bądź aby przekazać użytkownikowi informacje zwrotne lub informacje, o które użytkownik może prosić. Taki okres przechowywania podlega naszej weryfikacji i zmianom. Możemy przechowywać Dane osobowe pozbawione elementów umożliwiających ustalenie tożsamości tak długo, jak uznamy to za stosowne.

Po zamknięciu lub dezaktywacji konta użytkownika możemy zachować informacje o profilu użytkownika i wszystkie informacje opublikowane w publicznych obszarach Witryn internetowych. Po zamknięciu lub dezaktywacji konta użytkownika możemy zachować Dane osobowe i inne dane użytkownika, ale będziemy je traktować jako poufne zgodnie z Warunkami, niniejszą Polityką prywatności i zgodnie z wymogami obowiązującego prawa. Mamy prawo usunąć wszystkie Dane osobowe i inne dane użytkownika po zamknięciu konta użytkownika bez powiadomienia użytkownika.

8\. NIE GROMADZIMY CELOWO DANYCH DZIECI
=======================================

Nie gromadzimy, nie zabiegamy ani nie przechowujemy świadomie Danych osobowych osób poniżej 18. roku życia ani nie zezwalamy takim osobom na rejestrację lub korzystanie z naszych Usług. Jeśli użytkownik nie ma jeszcze ukończonych 18 lat, nie należy przesyłać nam żadnych Danych osobowych. W przypadku, gdy dowiemy się, że zebraliśmy Dane osobowe od dziecka poniżej 18. roku życia bez weryfikacji zgody rodziców, dołożymy wszelkich starań uzasadnionych z biznesowego punktu widzenia, aby usunąć te informacje z naszej bazy danych.

9\. GDZIE PRZETWARZAMY I PRZECHOWUJEMY DANE OSOBOWE; OBOWIĄZUJĄCE PRAWO WŁAŚCIWE
================================================================================

Nasza siedziba główna znajduje się w Stanach Zjednoczonych. Gromadzone przez nas lub naszych Usługodawców Dane osobowe mogą być przechowywane i przetwarzane na serwerach na terenie lub poza terenem Stanów Zjednoczonych oraz na całym świecie wszędzie tam, gdzie my i nasi Usługodawcy posiadamy placówki, a dostęp do niektórych informacji mogą mieć osoby lub firmy spoza Stanów Zjednoczonych, które świadczą dla nas usługi. Użytkownik wyraża zgodę na przekazywanie swoich Danych osobowych przez nas i naszych Usługodawców do jurysdykcji, które mogą nie zapewniać takiego samego poziomu ochrony danych jak kraj zamieszkania użytkownika lub na uzyskiwanie do nich dostępu w takich jurysdykcjach. Podejmiemy uzasadnione kroki w celu zapewnienia, że Dane osobowe użytkownika otrzymają odpowiedni poziom ochrony w jurysdykcjach, w których je przetwarzamy.

Przepisy prawa Stanów Zjednoczonych mają zastosowanie, o ile użytkownik jest mieszkańcem Stanów Zjednoczonych. W przeciwnym razie niniejsza Polityka prywatności i wszystkie inne kwestie będą interpretowane zgodnie z przepisami prawa prowincji/stanu i federalnego jurysdykcji, w której mieszka użytkownik. Jurysdykcje poza miejscem zamieszkania użytkownika mogą mieć inne przepisy dotyczące ochrony prywatności niż te, które obowiązują w miejscu zamieszkania użytkownika, włącznie z prawem do dostępu do Danych osobowych przez organy ścigania i organy rządowe.  W zakresie, w jakim przetwarzamy dane poza krajem zamieszkania użytkownika, przeprowadzamy ocenę wpływu na prywatność w celu ustalenia, czy nasi Usługodawcy mogą zapewnić zasadniczo taki sam poziom ochrony, jaki jest wymagany w jurysdykcji użytkownika oraz zawieramy umowy w celu dalszego wzmocnienia zobowiązań do odpowiedniego przetwarzania Danych osobowych użytkownika.

10\. BEZPIECZEŃSTWO
===================

Wdrożyliśmy techniczne i organizacyjne zabezpieczenia mające na celu ochronę Danych osobowych użytkownika przed przypadkową utratą oraz nieuprawnionym dostępem, wykorzystaniem, zniszczeniem, zmianą i ujawnieniem. Należy jednak pamiętać, że Internet nie jest w 100% bezpiecznym środowiskiem. Obowiązkiem użytkownika jest ochrona bezpieczeństwa danych logowania, zachowanie ostrożności podczas przesyłania Danych osobowych za pośrednictwem wiadomości e-mail, komunikatorów internetowych i podobnych środków komunikacji oraz stosowanie dobrych praktyk w zakresie bezpieczeństwa w Internecie. Nigdy nie wyślemy użytkownikowi wiadomości e-mail z prośbą o podanie hasła lub innych danych logowania do konta. W przypadku otrzymania takiej wiadomości e-mail, należy wysłać ją do nas, abyśmy mogli przeprowadzić dochodzenie.

11\. DODATKOWE PRAWA OSÓB, KTÓRYCH DANE DOTYCZĄ, DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW NIEKTÓRYCH JURYSDYKCJI OPISANYCH W DODATKOWYCH INFORMACJACH O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI
===================================================================================================================================================

Poniżej wyjaśniono każde prawo osoby, której dane dotyczą, opisane w Dodatkowych informacjach o ochronie prywatności:

* Prawo do otrzymania informacji na temat praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności: użytkownik ma prawo otrzymać określone, wymagane prawem informacje w chwili gromadzenia informacji lub wcześniej bądź w odpowiedzi na złożony przez użytkownika wniosek.
* Prawo do usunięcia: użytkownik może zażądać usunięcia wszelkich swoich Danych osobowych, które od niego zebraliśmy, z zastrzeżeniem pewnych wyjątków.
* Prawo do korekty: użytkownik może zażądać sprostowania wszelkich nieprawidłowych Danych osobowych, które przechowujemy na jego temat.
* Prawo do bycia poinformowanym: Użytkownik może zażądać od nas przekazania mu szczegółowych informacji na temat sposobu, w jaki przetwarzamy Dane osobowe użytkownika, w tym przekazania użytkownikowi kopii określonych Danych osobowych, które zgromadziliśmy na jego temat w przenośnym formacie.
* Prawo do nie bycia dyskryminowanym(-ą): użytkownik ma prawo nie być dyskryminowanym(-ą) w związku z wykonywaniem swoich praw osób, których dane dotyczą. Oznacza to, że nie należy odmawiać dostępu do towarów lub usług, naliczać różnych cen lub stawek ani zapewniać innego poziomu jakości produktów lub usług w wyniku korzystania przez użytkownika z przysługujących mu praw.
* Prawa do rezygnacji: użytkownik może że poprosić o rezygnację ze sprzedaży i udostępniania swoich Danych osobowych, reklam behawioralnych o różnych kontekstach lub reklam ukierunkowanych, zautomatyzowanego podejmowania decyzji lub profilowania, w zakresie, w jakim takie działania są zdefiniowane i ograniczone przez obowiązujące przepisy prawa.
* Prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania lub sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania: użytkownik może zażądać od nas zaprzestania przetwarzania niektórych jego Danych osobowych, ale nadal możemy przechowywać Dane osobowe użytkownika.  
* Prawo do ograniczenia wykorzystywania wrażliwych Danych osobowych użytkownika: użytkownik może zażądać ograniczenia wykorzystywania jego wrażliwych Danych osobowych wyłącznie do celów dozwolonych przez obowiązujące przepisy prawa.
* Prawo do złożenia skargi: użytkownik ma prawo złożyć skargę do lokalnego organu ochrony danych, jeśli uzna, że przetwarzanie dotyczących użytkownika Danych osobowych narusza jego prawa.
* Prawo do wycofania zgody: W zakresie, w jakim przetwarzanie przez nas Danych osobowych użytkownika odbywa się wyłącznie na podstawie jego zgody, użytkownik może ją wycofać w dowolnym momencie.

12\. DANE KONTAKTOWE
====================

Firma PlugShare wyznaczyła inspektora ochrony danych jako osobę, która będzie nadzorować zgodność z wymogami dotyczącymi prywatności. Z inspektorem ochrony danych PlugShare można skontaktować się w sprawie wszelkich kwestii związanych z polityką prywatności pod poniższym adresem.

W razie jakichkolwiek pytań lub uwag dotyczących niniejszej Polityki prywatności lub naszych praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności prosimy o kontakt pod adresem: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, Kalifornia 90245 Stany Zjednoczone; do wiadomości: Inspektor ochrony danych; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

INFORMACJA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW NIEKTÓRYCH STANÓW W USA
=========================================================================

Jeśli użytkownik jest mieszkańcem stanu Kalifornia, Wirginia, Kolorado, Utah lub Connecticut (czasami określanych w niniejszym dokumencie jako „Konsument”), przepisy stanowe zapewniają użytkownikowi dodatkowe prawa dotyczące wykorzystywania przez nas jego Danych osobowych.

KALIFORNIJSKI PRZEPIS „SHINE THE LIGHT”
---------------------------------------

Artykuł 1798.83 Kodeksu cywilnego stanu Kalifornia, znany jako przepis „Shine The Light”, zezwala wszystkim użytkownikom będącym mieszkańcami stanu Kalifornia na żądanie i uzyskanie od nas listy Danych osobowych (jeśli dotyczy) ujawnionych stronom trzecim w celach marketingu bezpośredniego w poprzednim roku kalendarzowym oraz nazw i adresów tych stron trzecich. Wnioski można składać tylko raz w roku i są one bezpłatne.

USTAWA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI W INTERNECIE W STANIE KALIFORNIA („CALOPA”; KALIFORNIJSKI KODEKS BIZNESOWY I ZAWODOWY § 22575-22578, DOSTĘPNY [TUTAJ](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D-Q4wBu8zw))
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA ma zastosowanie wyłącznie do firm, które gromadzą Dane osobowe mieszkańców stanu Kalifornia.

1. JAK REAGUJEMY NA POLECENIA „NIE ŚLEDŹ”.

Niektóre przeglądarki internetowe wysyłają sygnały „nie śledź” (DNT/GPC) do witryn internetowych i innych usług online, z którymi komunikuje się przeglądarka użytkownika. Obecnie nie istnieje żadna norma, która określałby, co ewentualnie witryny internetowe powinny robić po otrzymaniu takich sygnałów; aktualnie posiadamy mechanizmy umożliwiające podjęcie działań w odpowiedzi na takie sygnały.

2. ŚLEDZENIE ZACHOWAŃ OSÓB TRZECICH

Możemy również wykorzystywać te technologie do gromadzenia informacji na temat aktywności użytkownika w Internecie w czasie i na stronach internetowych podmiotów zewnętrznych lub w innych usługach internetowych, lub do kojarzenia Danych osobowych z innymi informacjami zebranymi w ten sposób. Możemy wykorzystywać dane osobowe do śledzenia wzorców klikania i przeglądania użytkowników.

USTAWA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI KONSUMENTÓW W STANIE KALIFORNIA Z 2018 R. („CCPA”, DOSTĘPNA [TUTAJ](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) I JEJ NASTĘPCA, USTAWA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI W STANIE KALIFORNIA Z 2020 R. („CPRA”, DOSTĘPNA [TUTAJ](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)).
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Poniższa tabela zawiera szczegółowe informacje na temat sposobu, w jaki ujawniamy Dane osobowe, które zgromadziliśmy na temat użytkownika:

| Kategoria | Kategorie niepowiązanych stron trzecich, którym ujawniam Dane osobowe | Kategorie niepowiązanych podmiotów zewnętrznych, którym sprzedajemy lub udostępniamy Dane osobowe |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identyfikatory | Dostawcy usług w zakresie przechowywania lub hostingu danych<br><br>Dostawcy usług w zakresie zarządzania tożsamością<br><br>Dostawcy rozwiązań w zakresie płatności<br><br>Dostawcy usług badań, w tym badań ankietowych<br><br>Partnerzy reklamowi, w tym dostawcy mediów społecznościowych | Nd. |
| Dane demograficzne | Dostawcy usług badań, w tym badań ankietowych | Nd. |
| Informacje handlowe | Nd. | Nd. |
| Aktywność w Internecie lub innej sieci elektronicznej; informacje o urządzeniu | Dostawcy usług w zakresie przechowywania lub hostingu danych<br><br>Dostawcy usług w zakresie baz danych i oprogramowania<br><br>Dostawcy usług w zakresie zarządzania tożsamością<br><br>Partnerzy reklamowi, w tym dostawcy mediów społecznościowych | Nd. |
| Geolokalizacja | Dostawcy usług w zakresie przechowywania lub hostingu danych<br><br>Dostawcy usług w zakresie baz danych i oprogramowania<br><br>Partnerzy reklamowi, w tym dostawcy mediów społecznościowych | Nd. |
| Inne | Dostawcy usług w zakresie przechowywania lub hostingu danych<br><br>Dostawcy usług w zakresie baz danych i oprogramowania<br><br>Dostawcy usług badań, w tym badań ankietowych<br><br>Partnerzy reklamowi, w tym dostawcy mediów społecznościowych | Producenci, sprzedawcy detaliczni i hurtownicy |

Użytkownik może się z nami skontaktować w celu skorzystania z następujących praw wynikających z CCPA i CPRA (opisy tych praw można znaleźć w punkcie 11 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności):

1. Prawo do otrzymania informacji na temat praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności:  
2. Prawo do bycia poinformowanym(-ą) w zakresie następujących kwestii:

* kategorie Danych osobowych, które zgromadziliśmy na temat użytkownika;
* kategorie źródeł, z których zgromadziliśmy Dane osobowe na temat użytkownika;
* nasz cel biznesowy lub handlowy gromadzenia tych Danych osobowych;
* kategorie stron trzecich, którym udostępniamy te Dane osobowe;
* konkretne dane osobowe, które zgromadziliśmy na temat użytkownika (zwane również jako wniosek o przeniesienie danych) – dostarczymy użytkownikowi ich kopię w formacie elektronicznym lub papierowym;
* jeśli ujawnimy Dane osobowe użytkownika w celach biznesowych, lista wymieniająca ujawnienia w celach biznesowych, określająca kategorie Danych osobowych, które każda kategoria odbiorcy uzyskała.

3. Prawo do usunięcia.
4. Prawo do korekty.
5. Prawo do rezygnacji z reklam behawioralnych o różnych kontekstach, sprzedaży lub udostępniania Danych osobowych, przetwarzania Danych osobowych do profilowania i zautomatyzowanego podejmowania decyzji.
6. Prawo do ograniczenia wykorzystywania wrażliwych Danych osobowych użytkownika. Należy pamiętać, że nie wykorzystujemy wrażliwych Danych osobowych na temat użytkownika do celów, które nie są dozwolone na mocy ustawy CCPA i CPRA.

USTAWA DOTYCZĄCA OCHRONY DANYCH KONSUMENTÓW W WIRGINII (VIRGINIA CONSUMER DATA PROTECTION ACT, VCDPA), USTAWA DOTYCZĄCA PRYWATNOŚCI W KOLORADO (COLORADO PRIVACY ACT, CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), USTAWA DOTYCZĄCA OCHRONY DANYCH KONSUMENTÓW W UTAH (UTAH CONSUMER PRIVACY ACT, UCPA) ORAZ USTAWA DOTYCZĄCA PRYWATNOŚCI DANYCH W CONNECTICUT (CONNECTICUT DATA PRIVACY ACT, CDPA).[\[2\]](#ftnt2)   [\[3\]](#ftnt3)
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Użytkownik może skontaktować się z nami w celu skorzystania z następujących praw wynikających z tych przepisów obowiązujących w określonych stanach:

1. Prawo do otrzymania informacji na temat praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności:  
2. Prawo do bycia poinformowanym(-ą).
3. Prawo do usunięcia.
4. Prawo do korekty.
5. Prawo do rezygnacji z reklam ukierunkowanych lub sprzedaży Danych osobowych.
6. Prawo do rezygnacji z profilowania (zautomatyzowanego przetwarzania danych osobowych w celu analizy lub przewidywania cech lub przyszłych zachowań osoby, skutkujące podejmowaniem decyzji mających wpływ na prawa materialne danej osoby).  
7. Konsumenci z Wirginii, Kolorado i Connecticut mają również prawo odwołać się od naszych decyzji w sprawie ich wniosków osoby, której dane dotyczą, kontaktując się z nami za pomocą tej samej metody składania wniosku. Prosimy dołączyć kopię lub w inny sposób konkretnie odnieść się do naszej decyzji w sprawie złożonego przez użytkownika wniosku osoby, której dane dotyczą, abyśmy mogli odpowiednio rozpatrzyć odwołanie użytkownika. Odpowiemy na odwołanie użytkownika zgodnie z obowiązującym prawem.

NEVADA
------

Jak opisano powyżej, możemy sprzedawać identyfikatory użytkownika lub inne informacje umożliwiające identyfikację, które gromadzimy z naszych Witryn internetowych i Usług internetowych, niepowiązanym podmiotom w celu śledzenia zachowań o różnych kontekstach w rozumieniu prawa stanu Nevada. Użytkownik ma prawo do rezygnacji ze sprzedaży lub licencjonowania tych kategorii danych osobowych podmiotom niepowiązanym.

EGZEKWOWANIE PRAW
-----------------

Aby skorzystać z opisanych wyżej praw do uzyskania dostępu, korekty, przeniesienia i usunięcia danych, należy przesłać wniosek za pośrednictwem naszego formularza internetowego dostępnego [tutaj](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Tylko użytkownik albo osoba upoważniona do działania w jego imieniu może wysłać wniosek dotyczący Danych osobowych użytkownika. Użytkownik może również złożyć wniosek Konsumenta w imieniu swojego niepełnoletniego dziecka. Jeśli otrzymamy od osoby wniosek dotyczący skorzystania z praw w imieniu użytkownika, poprosimy o przedstawienie podpisanej zgody użytkownika upoważniającej do składania takich wniosków w imieniu użytkownika i skontaktujemy się z użytkownikiem, aby bezpośrednio potwierdzić takie upoważnienia. Użytkownik może złożyć wniosek Konsumenta dotyczący dostępu do danych lub ich przeniesienia tylko dwa razy w ciągu 12 miesięcy. Możliwy do weryfikacji wniosek Klienta musi:

* uwzględniać wystarczającą ilość informacji, by pozwolić nam w uzasadniony sposób zweryfikować, czy użytkownik jest osobą, której dane osobowe zgromadziliśmy lub czy upoważniony przedstawiciel złożył wniosek;
* opisywać wniosek wystarczająco szczegółowo, by pozwolić nam właściwie zrozumieć, ocenić i odpowiedzieć na niego.

Nie możemy odpowiedzieć na wniosek użytkownika ani przekazać mu Danych osobowych, jeżeli nie będziemy w stanie zweryfikować jego tożsamości ani upoważnienia do złożenia wniosku i potwierdzenia, że Dane osobowe faktycznie odnoszą się do użytkownika. Składanie wniosku Konsumenta nie wymaga utworzenia u nas konta. Będziemy wykorzystywać Dane osobowe podane we wniosku Konsumenta wyłącznie w celu weryfikacji tożsamości lub upoważnienia wnioskodawcy do złożenia żądania.

Aby skorzystać z prawa do rezygnacji z reklam behawioralnych o różnych kontekstach, reklam ukierunkowanych lub udostępniania Danych osobowych w sposób opisany powyżej, należy dokonać rezygnacji w sposób zależny platformy, z której użytkownik korzysta.  Należy pamiętać, że wniosek związany z rezygnacją dotyczy konkretnego urządzenia i platformy, za pośrednictwem których użytkownik przesyła takie żądanie, dlatego jeśli użytkownik zamierza zrezygnować z konkretnych czynności przetwarzania na wielu urządzeniach i platformach konieczne może być wysłanie wielu wniosków. Należy kliknąć:

* tutaj, aby zrezygnować w witrynie Plugshare.com (platforma internetowa)
* tutaj, aby zrezygnować w aplikacji Plugshare w systemie iOS
* tutaj, aby zrezygnować w aplikacji Plugshare w systemie Android

### Proces weryfikacji

Po otrzymaniu od użytkownika możliwego do weryfikacji wniosku o uzyskanie dostępu do danych lub usunięcia danych, w ciągu 10 dni roboczych wyślemy użytkownikowi wiadomość e-mail na adres zapisany w jego dokumentacji. W wiadomości e-mail użytkownik zostanie poproszony o udzielenie odpowiedzi w celu weryfikacji użytkownika jako konsumenta składającego wniosek. Po otrzymaniu weryfikacji użytkownika dopasujemy dane użytkownika do danych znajdujących się w naszej dokumentacji. Po weryfikacji tożsamości użytkownika będziemy kontynuować przetwarzanie wniosku i udzielimy odpowiedzi w ciągu 45 dni kalendarzowych, chyba że (a) nie będziemy w stanie zweryfikować wniosku użytkownika, (b) nie będziemy w stanie dopasować użytkownika do informacji zawartych w naszej bazie danych lub (c) istnieje wyjątek prawny, który zwalnia nas z obowiązku wypełniania postulatów wniosku użytkownika. Jeśli będziemy potrzebować więcej czasu (maksymalnie do dodatkowych czterdziestu pięciu (45) dni kalendarzowych), poinformujemy użytkownika na piśmie o przyczynie i okresie przedłużenia.

Jeśli nie będziemy w stanie spełnić żądania użytkownika, udzielona przez nas odpowiedź będzie zawierać odpowiednie wyjaśnienie. W przypadku wniosków o przeniesienie danych, do samego przekazania takich Danych osobowych użytkownikowi wybierzemy format który jest łatwy w użyciu i który umożliwi użytkownikowi przesłanie tych informacji z jednego podmiotu do innego bez przeszkód.

Nie pobieramy opłat za rozpatrzenie i udzielenie odpowiedzi na możliwe do zweryfikowania wnioski Konsumenta, chyba że są one nadmierne, powtarzalne lub ewidentnie bezpodstawne. Jeśli stwierdzimy, że w związku z wnioskiem należna jest opłata, poinformujemy użytkownika, dlaczego podjęliśmy tę decyzję i przedstawimy szacunkowe koszty przed rozpatrzeniem wniosku.

* * *

POWIADOMIENIA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI DLA NIEKTÓRYCH KRAJÓW POZA STANAMI ZJEDNOCZONYMI
=====================================================================================

INFORMACJE OGÓLNE
-----------------

1. ### WYRAŹNA ZGODA UŻYTKOWNIKA NA PRZETWARZANIE „WRAŻLIWYCH” DANYCH OSOBOWYCH LUB DANYCH OSOBOWYCH „SZCZEGÓLNYCH” KATEGORII

Zgodnie z przepisami dotyczącymi prywatności obowiązującymi w niektórych krajach niektóre rodzaje Danych osobowych są uznawane za informacje „wrażliwe” lub informacje „szczególnych” kategorii. Rzadko przetwarzamy dane wrażliwe lub dane szczególnych kategorii, chyba że leży to w istotnym interesie użytkownika lub interesie innej osoby. We wszystkich innych okolicznościach użytkownik wyraźnie zgadza się na gromadzenie, przetwarzanie i przechowywanie przez nas wrażliwych Danych osobowych lub Danych osobowych szczególnych kategorii zgodnie z opisem ujętym w ustępie 1.2 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności i wyraża zgodę na przetwarzanie Danych osobowych zgodnie z niniejszą Informacją o ochronie prywatności.  

2. ### NASZE PODSTAWY PRAWNE PRZETWARZANIA DANYCH OSOBOWYCH

Nasze podstawy prawne gromadzenia i wykorzystywania przez nas Danych osobowych opisanych powyżej będą zależeć od poszczególnych Danych osobowych oraz konkretnego kontekstu, w jakim je gromadzimy. Ogólnie rzecz biorąc, będziemy gromadzić i przetwarzać Dane osobowe użytkownika tylko wtedy, gdy będziemy potrzebować Danych osobowych do świadczenia użytkownikowi Usług, w związku z którymi użytkownik zawarł z nami umowę lub gdy przetwarzanie leży w naszym prawnie uzasadnionym interesie i nie jest nadrzędne wobec interesów użytkownika w zakresie ochrony danych ani podstawowych praw i wolności, a ponadto będziemy polegać na zgodzie użytkownika, we wszystkich sytuacjach, w których jesteśmy do tego prawnie zobowiązani. W niektórych przypadkach możemy również mieć prawny obowiązek gromadzenia Danych osobowych od użytkownika lub w inny sposób możemy potrzebować Danych osobowych w celu ochrony żywotnych interesów użytkownika lub innej osoby.

PODSTAWA PRAWNIE UZASADNIONEGO INTERESU GROMADZENIA DANYCH OSOBOWYCH: Gromadzenie i przetwarzanie Danych osobowych użytkownika może być konieczne do celów naszych uzasadnionych interesów. Takie uzasadnione cele mogą obejmować:

* zapobieganie oszustwom;
* zapewnienie bezpieczeństwa sieci i informacji;
* wskazywanie możliwych działań przestępczych lub zagrożeń dla bezpieczeństwa publicznego, w tym zwiększenie ochrony naszej społeczności przed spamem, nękaniem, naruszeniem własności intelektualnej, przestępstwami i zagrożeniami bezpieczeństwa wszelkiego rodzaju oraz egzekwowanie roszczeń prawnych, w tym dochodzenie potencjalnych naruszeń naszych Warunków użytkowania;
* spełnianie naszych zobowiązań prawnych;
* przetwarzanie danych pracownika lub gościa, członka, uczestnika lub osoby rejestrującej;
* wykonywanie funkcji lub usługi, o którą użytkownik prosił;
* świadczenie naszych Usług i ich funkcjonalność, gdy takie przetwarzanie jest niezbędne do celów uzasadnionych interesów realizowanych przez nas lub przez naszych usługodawców związanych z Usługami;
* marketing bezpośredni;
* prowadzenie z użytkownikiem odpowiedniej i stosownej relacji;
* analizy, np. oceny liczby odwiedzających, liczby wyświetleń stron, korzystania z Witryn internetowych itp. w celu zrozumienia sposobu korzystania z naszych Witryn internetowych, Produktów i Usług, optymalizacji Witryn internetowych i/lub przyszłej komunikacji oraz opracowywania nowych usług i funkcji Witryny internetowej;
* aktualizacje informacji i preferencji;
* oferowanie i ulepszanie naszych Witryn internetowych, Produktów i Usług;
* egzekwowanie roszczeń prawnych, w tym badanie potencjalnych naruszeń naszych Warunków.

Oprócz informacji podanych powyżej, poniższe postanowienia dotyczą wyłącznie mieszkańców lub obywateli omawianego kraju lub regionu. Na potrzeby poniższych postanowień, o ile nie wskazano inaczej, definicja „Danych osobowych” wykorzystywana powyżej będzie mieć taką samą definicję, co informacje osobowe, dane osobowe lub podobny termin, zgodnie z przepisami o ochronie danych obowiązującymi w danym kraju lub regionie. W przypadku i w zakresie sprzeczności między poniższymi a powyższymi postanowieniami, znaczenie nadrzędne mają postanowienia znajdujące się poniżej.

RODO – INFORMACJA O OCHRONIE PRYWATNOŚCI DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW EUROPEJSKIEGO OBSZARU GOSPODARCZEGO (EEA), WIELKIEJ BRYTANII I SZWAJCARII
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### INFORMACJE OGÓLNE

Poniższe postanowienia mają zastosowanie tylko wobec mieszkańców EOG, Wielkiej Brytanii lub Szwajcarii (zwanych w niniejszym punkcie dla wygody „Rejonem UE”).

W przypadku takich rezydentów przetwarzanie Danych osobowych użytkownika odbywa się zgodnie z prawami i przepisami dotyczącymi prywatności, w szczególności (UE) 2016/679 Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r., zwanymi Ogólnym rozporządzeniem o ochronie danych lub Ogólnym rozporządzeniem o ochronie danych w Wielkiej Brytanii dla mieszkańców Wielkiej Brytanii (łącznie „RODO”) i wszelkie wykonywane przez nas przetwarzanie będzie zgodne z postanowieniami RODO. Na potrzeby RODO pełnimy funkcję „administratora” Danych osobowych (określanych i zdefiniowanych w RODO (dostępne [tutaj](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) jako „dane osobowe”), które gromadzimy, chyba że gromadzimy takie informacje w imieniu „administratora danych”, w którym to przypadku będziemy pełnić funkcję „podmiotu przetwarzającego dane”. Niniejsza Polityka prywatności nie dotyczy witryn internetowych, aplikacji ani usług, które nie wyświetlają niniejszej Polityki prywatności ani nie łączą się z nią, ani też wyświetlają lub zawierają łącza do innej polityki prywatności. Tylko w przypadku mieszkańców i obywateli regionu UE, w zakresie, w jakim jakakolwiek definicja w niniejszej Polityce prywatności jest sprzeczna z definicją zawartą w RODO, znaczenie nadrzędne ma definicja RODO.

Zapewniamy odpowiednią ochronę w przypadku przekazywania Danych osobowych do krajów spoza regionu UE za pomocą jednej lub kilku z następujących metod: (a) serii umów zawieranych pomiędzy firmami opartych na Standardowych klauzulach umownych lub zawierających te Standardowe klauzule umowne; (b) możemy polegać na decyzjach Komisji Europejskiej stwierdzających odpowiedni stopień ochrony dotyczących niektórych krajów, w stosownych przypadkach; (c) możemy uzyskać zgodę użytkownika na takie przekazywanie danych z regionu UE do Stanów Zjednoczonych i innych krajów; (d) możemy przyjąć wiążące reguły korporacyjne; lub (e) w odpowiednim zakresie, możemy polegać na odstępstwach określonych w art. 49 RODO w zakresie przekazywania i dalszego przekazywania Danych osobowych zebranych od osób fizycznych w regionie UE do Stanów Zjednoczonych i innych krajów, które w regionie UE nie uchodzą za zapewniające odpowiednią ochronę danych. Jeśli chodzi o metodę (e), możemy przekazywać Dane osobowe stronie trzeciej w celu wykonania umowy z użytkownikiem, za jego wyraźną zgodą lub w sposób, który nie narusza jego praw i wolności. Jeśli te Dane osobowe nie będą przetwarzane i przekazywane, nie będziemy w stanie zawrzeć z użytkownikiem umowy lub użytkownik nie będzie mieć dostępu do żadnych korzyści i funkcji związanych z jego transakcją.

Możemy również być zmuszeni do przekazania danych użytkownika innym firmom należącym do grupy lub usługodawcom w krajach spoza regionu UE. Może to nastąpić, jeśli nasze serwery lub dostawcy i usługodawcy znajdują się poza regionem UE lub jeśli użytkownik korzysta z naszych Produktów i/lub Usług znajdując się w krajach poza tym obszarem.

Nasze podstawy prawne do gromadzenia Danych osobowych omówiono w .

2. ### PRAWA DOTYCZĄCE DANYCH PRZYSŁUGUJĄCE UŻYTKOWNIKOWI W ZWIĄZKU Z RODO.

Jeśli użytkownik podlega RODO, jego prawa obejmują:

* prawo do bycia poinformowanym(-ą);
* prawo do korekty;
* prawo do usunięcia;
* prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania lub sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania; Użytkownik ma prawo sprzeciwić się wykorzystywaniu swoich Danych osobowych, jeśli są one wykorzystywane w następujący sposób: (a) przetwarzanie w oparciu o uzasadnione interesy lub wykonywanie zadania w interesie publicznym/wykonywanie władzy publicznej (w tym profilowanie); (b) marketing bezpośredni (w tym profilowanie); oraz (c) przetwarzanie w celach badań naukowych/historycznych i statystyk. Więcej informacji znajduje się poniżej.
* Prawo do rezygnacji. Użytkownik ma prawo nie podlegać decyzjom podejmowanym wyłącznie na podstawie zautomatyzowanego przetwarzania, w tym profilowania, które wywołują skutki prawne dotyczące użytkownika lub w podobny sposób znacząco na niego wpływają, z zastrzeżeniem wyjątków mających zastosowanie na mocy odpowiednich przepisów o ochronie danych.
* Prawo do złożenia skargi. Jeśli użytkownik mieszka na terenie EOG, listę krajowych organów ochrony danych można znaleźć [tutaj](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Jeśli użytkownik mieszka w Wielkiej Brytanii, można skontaktować się z Biurem Komisarza ds. Informacji [tutaj.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Prawo do wycofania zgody.

POWIADOMIENIA DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW NIEKTÓRYCH INNYCH KRAJÓW (POZA STANAMI ZJEDNOCZONYMI)
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Poniższe informacje zawarte w niniejszej części stanowią uzupełnienie informacji omówionych w naszej głównej Polityce prywatności.

Będziemy z szacunkiem traktować następujące prawa osób, których dane dotyczą, wobec wszystkich rezydentów poza Stanami Zjednoczonymi:

* prawo do otrzymania informacji na temat praktyk w zakresie ochrony prywatności:

* Nasza tożsamość i dane kontaktowe;
* Konkretny cel przetwarzania przez nas Danych osobowych użytkownika;
* Formularz i czas trwania przetwarzania przez nas Danych osobowych użytkownika;
* Informacje o udostępnianiu przez nas Danych osobowych i celu ich udostępniania;
* Obowiązki osób trzecich przetwarzających Dane osobowe użytkownika; oraz
* Informacje dotyczące wszelkich publicznych i prywatnych podmiotów prawnych, którym udostępniliśmy Dane osobowe użytkownika;  

* Prawo do bycia poinformowanym:

* Decyzje podejmowane wyłącznie na podstawie zautomatyzowanego przetwarzania Danych osobowych;
* Dostęp do informacji na temat gromadzonych przez nas Danych osobowych.  

* prawo do korekty;
* prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania lub sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania;
* prawo do wycofania zgody.

Wszelkie tłumaczenia niniejszej Polityki prywatności na język inny niż angielski są udostępniane wyłącznie w celach informacyjnych. W przypadku jakichkolwiek rozbieżności jedyną obowiązującą i wiążącą wersją prawną będzie angielska wersja niniejszego dokumentu.

1. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW ARGENTYNY

Techniczne i organizacyjne środki bezpieczeństwa wdrożone przez PlugShare będą również wspierać zasady określone w art. 25.326 argentyńskiej Ustawy o ochronie danych osobowych (Personal Data Protection Act, PDPA), takie jak zakaz wszelkiego wtórnego wykorzystywania danych osobowych osób, których dane dotyczą, oraz zakaz przekazywania danych osobowych do krajów, które nie zapewniają odpowiedniego poziomu ochrony. Firma PlugShare wykorzystuje umowę o przekazywaniu/przetwarzaniu danych w celu zapewnienia zgodności z postanowieniami PDPA 60-E/2016, która reguluje przekazywanie danych osobowych przez granice.

Mieszkańcy Argentyny mają: (a) prawo do bycia poinformowanym(-ą) na temat istnienia i celu takich Danych osobowych; oraz (b) prawo do korekty i prawo do ograniczenia lub wniesienia sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania Danych osobowych, jeśli są one fałszywe, niedokładne lub dyskryminujące.

2. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW AUSTRALII

Możemy wykorzystywać i ujawniać Dane osobowe użytkownika (zgodnie z definicją zawartą w przepisach prawa australijskiego) stronom trzecim z siedzibą poza Australią, głównie w Stanach Zjednoczonych, zgodnie z opisem zawartym w ustępie 9 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności. Użytkownik zgadza się i przyjmuje do wiadomości, że odbiorcy zagraniczni będą podlegać przepisom o ochronie prywatności obowiązującym w ich lokalnej jurysdykcji i nie mogą podlegać żadnym zobowiązaniom dotyczącym ochrony prywatności ani żadnym zasadom podobnym do australijskich Zasad ochrony prywatności. Tacy odbiorcy będą również podlegać prawu zagranicznemu, które może wymusić ujawnienie Danych osobowych stronie trzeciej, takiej jak organ zagraniczny. O ile użytkownik nie powiadomi nas na piśmie o podjęciu przeciwstawnej decyzji, zostanie poproszony o wyrażenie zgody na ujawnienie przez nas Danych osobowych odbiorcom zagranicznym. Użytkownik ma możliwość zachowania anonimowości w kontaktach z nami lub nieujawniania nam określonych Danych osobowych. Może to jednak oznaczać, że możemy nie być w stanie świadczyć użytkownikowi naszych Usług.

W przypadku mieszkańców Australii aktualizacje niniejszej Polityki prywatności wchodzą w życie, jeśli uzyskamy wyraźną zgodę użytkownika lub jeśli zapewnimy możliwość rezygnacji w chwili ogłaszania istotnych zmian (np. w naszych Witrynach internetowych lub za pośrednictwem poczty elektronicznej).

3. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW BRAZYLII

Mieszkańcy Brazylii mają prawo znać następujące informacje: czy przekazanie nam Danych osobowych użytkownika jest wymogiem umownym, czy istnieją jakiekolwiek negatywne konsekwencje niepodania takich danych (odpowiedź na oba pytania brzmi „nie”) oraz informacje dotyczące zautomatyzowanego podejmowania decyzji (w tym profilowania), które podejmujemy (zob. ust. 2.1 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności). Ponadto użytkownik ma prawo wycofać zgodę na przetwarzanie swoich Danych osobowych oraz przysługują mu prawa dostępu osoby, której dane dotyczą (patrz poniżej).

Mieszkańcy Brazylii mają również: (a) prawo do bycia poinformowanym(-ą), w tym do uzyskania kopii takich informacji; (b) prawo do korekty; (c) prawo do ograniczenia lub wyrażenia sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania; (d) prawo do usunięcia; (e) prawo do otrzymania informacji o praktykach ochrony prywatności dotyczących podmiotów publicznych i prywatnych, którym udostępniono Dane osobowe użytkownika; oraz (f) prawo do złożenia skargi do brazylijskiego organu nadzorczego ds. danych (AnPD).

4. ### POWIADOMIENIE MIESZKAŃCÓW KANADY (W TYM QUEBEC)

Nasza Polityka prywatności i nasze ogólne praktyki mają na celu zachowanie zgodności z kanadyjskimi przepisami dotyczącymi ochrony prywatności, w tym ustawą o ochronie danych osobowych i dokumentach elektronicznych (Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, PIPEDA) oraz, w stosownych przypadkach, ustawy o ochronie prywatności w sektorze prywatnym Quebec, ochrony danych osobowych w sektorze prywatnym (Security Information in Private Sector, RSQ, c. P-39.1). W przypadku wszelkich praktyk związanych z przetwarzaniem informacji, które nie są w uzasadniony sposób powiązane z celami, dla których użytkownik skontaktował się z PlugShare, użytkownik ma prawo zrezygnować z takich praktyk związanych z przetwarzaniem informacji (w tym działań marketingowych, profilowania, reklamy behawioralnej, udostępniania stronom trzecim, które nie są usługodawcami).  

Mieszkańcy Kanady mają prawo do rezygnacji z wykorzystywania przez nas Danych osobowych do celów marketingu bezpośredniego oraz z innych rodzajów przetwarzania, które nie są w uzasadniony sposób niezbędne do udzielenia odpowiedzi na to, do czego nas zaangażowali.

5. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW HONGKONGU

Wykorzystujemy Dane osobowe użytkownika do następujących celów marketingu bezpośredniego: (a) w celu komunikowania się z użytkownikiem w sprawie naszych produktów i usług oraz produktów i usług naszych podmiotów stowarzyszonych; oraz (b) w celu wysyłania użytkownikowi dalszych powiadomień, promocji lub innych materiałów marketingowych dotyczących naszych Witryn internetowych, Produktów i Usług, a także tych naszych podmiotów stowarzyszonych. Poprosimy użytkownika o wyrażenie zgody na ten cel w momencie przekazywania nam przez niego swoich Danych osobowych (np. podczas tworzenia konta, rejestracji wydarzenia itp.).

6. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW MEKSYKU

Oprócz informacji przedstawionych powyżej mieszkańcy Meksyku mają prawo do otrzymania informacji o praktykach ochrony prywatności, w tym: (a) do otrzymania informacji, czy przekazanie nam przez użytkownika Danych osobowych użytkownika jest wymogiem umownym lub czy istnieje jakikolwiek skutek niedostarczenia takich danych (odpowiedź „nie” dotyczy obu tych kwestii); (b) informacji dotyczących zautomatyzowanego podejmowania decyzji (w tym profilowania), które podejmujemy (o czym mowa w ustępie 2.1 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności); (c) informacji, jak długo dane są przechowywane (patrz ustęp 7 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności); (d) prawo do wycofania zgody na przetwarzanie Danych osobowych; oraz (e) prawa dostępu przysługujące osobie, której dane dotyczą (patrz poniżej). Użytkownik ma również prawo znać wyraźne wskazanie wrażliwych danych osobowych, które mają być przetwarzane.

Mieszkańcy Meksyku mają również: (a) prawo do otrzymania informacji o gromadzonych przez nas Danych osobowych, w tym prawo do informacji o podmiotach publicznych i prywatnych, którym udostępniono Dane osobowe użytkownika, oraz prawo do uzyskania kopii takich informacji; (b) prawo do korekty; (c) prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania lub sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania; oraz (d) prawo do usunięcia danych.

7. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW SINGAPURU

Jeśli, między innymi, posiadamy placówkę w Singapurze, użytkownik ma prawo do zlecenia przekazania swoich Danych osobowych, które posiadamy, innej organizacji.

Osoby lub firmy, którym ujawniamy i przekazujemy Dane osobowe użytkownika, mogą znajdować się poza Singapurem. W takich przypadkach zapewnimy, że odbiorcy przekazywanych Danych osobowych będą w stanie zapewnić przekazywanym Danym osobowym standard ochrony porównywalny ze standardami ochrony określonymi w przepisach o ochronie prywatności Singapuru poprzez wykorzystanie pisemnych umów o przekazywaniu danych (w przypadku przekazywania danych podmiotom zewnętrznym) lub wiążących reguł korporacyjnych (w przypadku przekazywania danych naszym podmiotom stowarzyszonym i innym podmiotom powiązanym z nami).

8. ### POWIADOMIENIE DLA MIESZKAŃCÓW TAJWANU

Mieszkańcy Tajwanu mają prawo do otrzymywania informacji o praktykach ochrony prywatności.

Mieszkańcy Tajwanu mają również: (a) prawo do otrzymania informacji o gromadzonych przez nas Danych osobowych, w tym prawo do informacji o podmiotach publicznych i prywatnych, którym udostępniono Dane osobowe użytkownika, oraz prawo do uzyskania kopii takich informacji; (b) prawo do korekty; (c) prawo do ograniczenia przetwarzania lub sprzeciwu wobec przetwarzania; oraz (d) prawo do usunięcia danych.

Oprócz informacji przedstawionych powyżej mieszkańcy Tajwanu mają prawo do otrzymania określonych informacji o gromadzonych przez nas Danych osobowych, w tym: (a) do otrzymania informacji, czy przekazanie nam przez użytkownika Danych osobowych użytkownika jest wymogiem umownym lub czy istnieje jakikolwiek skutek niedostarczenia takich danych (odpowiedź „nie” dotyczy obu tych kwestii); (b) informacji dotyczących zautomatyzowanego podejmowania decyzji (w tym profilowania), które podejmujemy (o czym mowa w ustępie 2.1 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności); (c) informacji, jak długo dane są przechowywane (patrz ustęp 7 naszej głównej Polityki prywatności); (d) prawo do wycofania zgody na przetwarzanie Danych osobowych; oraz (e) prawa dostępu przysługujące osobie, której dane dotyczą (patrz poniżej). Użytkownik ma również prawo znać wyraźne wskazanie wrażliwych danych osobowych, które mają być przetwarzane (nie zbieramy „wrażliwych” informacji).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) Ustawa dotycząca prywatności w Kolorado (Colorado Privacy Act) wchodzi w życie 1 lipca 2023 r.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) Ustawa dotycząca prywatności danych w Connecticut (Connecticut Data Privacy Act) wchodzi w życie 1 lipca 2023 r.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) Ustawa dotycząca ochrony danych konsumentów w Utah (Utah Consumer Privacy Act) wchodzi w życie 31 grudnia 2023 r.

POLÍTICA DE PRIVACIDADE DA PLUGSHARE
====================================

DATA DE ENTRADA EM VIGOR: 10 de julho de 2023
---------------------------------------------

A PlugShare, LLC (“PlugShare” “nós”, “nos” ou “nosso”) tem como objetivos criar uma comunidade de apoio de utilizadores de Veículos Elétricos (“VE”) e fornecer informações de carregamento líder do setor e uma ampla gama de produtos e serviços inovadores para ajudar a tornar a experiência de condução de VE o mais fácil e gratificante possível. A presente Política de Privacidade estabelece as nossas políticas sobre a recolha, utilização, divulgação, retenção, e transferência das Informações Pessoais (definidas abaixo) que recolhemos sobre si (“você” ou “seu”) através das nossas interações consigo através dos nossos Websites ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); ou [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); coletivamente, “Websites”), serviços correspondentes e as nossas aplicações móveis (coletivamente “Serviços”), bem como através de interações com partes não afiliadas, como os nossos fornecedores que trabalham connosco para lhe prestar os nossos Serviços.

Leia atentamente a presente Política de Privacidade. Se não quiser que tratemos as suas Informações Pessoais, não nos forneça quaisquer informações; no entanto, poderá não conseguir tirar partido de determinadas funcionalidades dos nossos Serviços.

A sua utilização do Website e dos nossos Serviços está sempre sujeita aos nossos Termos de Utilização (disponíveis em [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) e atualizados periodicamente (os “Termos”)).

A presente Política de Privacidade não se aplica a qualquer site ou serviço não afiliado ligado a ou a partir dos nossos Websites ou Serviços, exceto aos dos nossos Prestadores de Serviços, aos nossos canais ou plataformas de redes sociais que alojam os mesmos, ou a qualquer site ou serviço recomendado ou referido pelos nossos Websites ou Serviços ou pelo nosso pessoal.

Residentes na Califórnia, Virgínia, Colorado, Utah e Connecticut: Consulte o nosso Aviso de Privacidade [Suplementar para Residentes de Determinados Estados dos EUA](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html)  relativamente a informações adicionais sobre o nosso tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais.

Residentes de outros países: Se residir num país que não os Estados Unidos, consulte a nossa página de Avisos de Privacidade Suplementares para Determinados Países Fora dos EUA para obter informações adicionais sobre o nosso tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais.

Estamos constantemente a trabalhar para melhorar os nossos Serviços e poderemos precisar também de alterar a presente Política de Privacidade regularmente. A nossa Política de Privacidade atual estará sempre disponível nos nossos Websites. Tenha em atenção a data de entrada em vigor da presente Política de Privacidade e certifique-se de que consulta periodicamente as atualizações.

1\. QUE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS RECOLHEMOS
=======================================

1.1 O QUE SÃO INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS
----------------------------------

A presente Política de Privacidade abrange o nosso tratamento das suas informações pessoais identificáveis. “Informações Pessoais” geralmente significa qualquer informação não encriptada que identifique, se relacione com, descreva, seja razoavelmente capaz de ser associada a, ou possa ser razoavelmente ligada a uma pessoa em particular, como, mas não se limitando a, o seu nome, endereço postal, endereço de e-mail, número de telefone, etc.

As Informações Pessoais não incluem as suas Informações Pessoais que tenham sido não identificadas, anonimizadas ou agregadas de formas exigidas pelas leis aplicáveis, para que as informações deixem de poder ser diretamente, ou através de outros meios razoavelmente disponíveis, utilizadas para identificar um indivíduo (coletivamente, “Informações Pessoais Não Identificadas”).

1.2 CATEGORIAS DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS QUE RECOLHEMOS E TRATAMOS
----------------------------------------------------------------

Recolhemos várias categorias de Informações Pessoais de e sobre si, conforme resumido na tabela seguinte:

| Categoria | Itens Específicos de Informações Pessoais |
| --- | --- |
| Identificadores | * nome próprio e apelido<br>* nome de utilizador (que pode incluir nome próprio e apelido)<br>* endereço de e-mail<br>* código postal<br>* sexo, género<br>* identificador pessoal único, por exemplo, nome ou número de cliente ou de conta, número de telefone, identificador de dispositivo móvel |
| Demografia | * país de residência |
| Informações comerciais | * histórico de compras e tendências de produtos/serviços |
| Atividade na Internet ou outra rede eletrónica; informações do dispositivo | * tipo e fabricante do dispositivo e respetiva ID/UDID ou código específico do dispositivo semelhante<br>* sistema operativo e plataforma<br>* resolução do ecrã<br>* nome do prestador de serviços de Internet ou do operador móvel, velocidade de ligação e tipo de ligação<br>* Informações sobre o endereço, protocolo e sequência do Protocolo de Internet (ou IP)<br>* cookies<br>* etiquetas pixel<br>* Endereço MAC (Media Access Control) das páginas que visitou<br>* identificador de publicidade de dispositivo móvel<br>* tipo de navegador, idioma e versão<br>* Navegação no website, sessão, interação e histórico de pesquisa, material e páginas visualizados, hora e data de acesso aos websites, número de bytes transferidos, número de cliques por visita, tempo gasto numa página, dados de cliques e sequências de cliques, consultas feitas, resultados de pesquisa selecionados, comentários feitos<br>* carimbo de data e URL da última página web visitada antes de visitar os nossos Websites, e URL da primeira página visitada depois de sair dos nossos Websites<br>* tipo de Serviço solicitado<br>* cabeçalhos de protocolo de transferência de hipertexto, banners de cliente de aplicação e servidor |
| Geolocalização | * localização física e/ou movimentos |
| Outro | * Dados de carregamento de VE, marca do veículo, modelo e ano<br>* Informações disponibilizadas por si como parte de uma resposta de feedback ou outra consulta geral feita através dos nossos Websites<br>* Inferências retiradas de qualquer das informações listadas para criar um perfil sobre um consumidor que reflita as preferências, características, tendências psicológicas, predisposições, comportamento, atitudes, inteligência, capacidades ou aptidão do consumidor |

1.3 ONDE RECOLHEMOS INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS
----------------------------------------

Podemos recolher Informações Pessoais diretamente de si através dos nossos Serviços quando:

* Nos fornece Informações Pessoais preenchendo formulários Web nos nossos Websites ou quando realiza transações em lojas (marcas principais, subsidiárias e afiliadas). Isto inclui informações fornecidas ao criar uma conta online, comprar os nossos Serviços, subscrever as nossas e-newsletters ou outras comunicações, solicitar informações sobre nós, enviar ou publicar material (quando permitido) nos nossos fóruns, interagir com o apoio ao cliente ou serviço, comunicar um problema com os nossos Websites, aplicações móveis ou Serviços ou comunicar connosco de outra forma.
* Contacte-nos. Isto inclui todos os registos e cópias da sua correspondência connosco, tais como com os nossos escritórios ou serviço de apoio/apoio ao cliente ou envio de um cheque.
* Se regista num evento ou nos informa de qualquer acessibilidade ou outros pedidos de alojamento.
* Responde a inquéritos que nós ou os nossos Prestadores de Serviços lhe possamos pedir para preencher para fins de investigação.
* Faz pesquisas nos Websites.
* Participa em programas de fidelidade/recompensas.
* Se candidata a emprego.
* Utiliza dispositivos e redes para aceder aos nossos Serviços, tais como sincronizar o seu VE com os nossos Serviços.
* Utiliza determinadas funcionalidades nos nossos Websites e aplicações móveis. Embora os utilizadores possam aceder a funcionalidades limitadas sem divulgar as suas Informações Pessoais, tais como navegar em estações de carregamento públicas sem uma conta, recolhemos Informações Pessoais quando os utilizadores registam uma conta. Os utilizadores podem optar por utilizar apenas o seu e-mail e palavra-passe para navegar pelos carregadores domésticos. Os utilizadores também podem optar por tirar partido das capacidades melhoradas publicando, comentando, publicando ou partilhando Informações Pessoais adicionais com a comunidade. De um modo geral, os Utilizadores escolhem a quantidade de informações que pretendem apresentar sobre si próprios e podem optar por não participar a qualquer momento.

Também podemos recolher Informações Pessoais de partes não afiliadas, incluindo:

* Fornecedores de dados (por exemplo, empresas que fornecem dados demográficos e outras informações relativas aos consumidores)
* Em aplicações móveis (marcas principais, subsidiárias e afiliadas)
* Parceiros de marketing conjuntos
* Empresas ou plataformas de publicidade online (como, por exemplo, se se associar voluntariamente ou ligar o seu perfil de redes sociais aos nossos Serviços)
* Prestadores de serviços de atendimento e entrega
* Empresas de redes sociais
* Outros Prestadores de Serviços
* Responder a oportunidades de emprego
* Ações do website/formulário web ou aplicação do utilizador
* Fornecedores de verificação de emprego ou verificação de antecedentes
* Permitir-nos, através das definições do seu dispositivo ou serviços de terceiros, receber dados de geolocalização para mostrar informações locais (por exemplo, uma estação de carregamento local) nas nossas aplicações móveis.

1.4 INFORMAÇÕES RECOLHIDAS ATRAVÉS DE TECNOLOGIAS AUTOMATIZADAS
---------------------------------------------------------------

À medida que navega e interage com os nossos Serviços, também podemos utilizar tecnologias de recolha automática de dados para recolher determinadas informações do seu dispositivo, navegador ou outras atividades de rede, conforme descrito na nossa Política de Cookies, disponível em [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Consulta no Website e Informação do Dispositivo. Recolhemos detalhes das suas visitas aos nossos Websites e da utilização das nossas Aplicações Móveis, incluindo, mas não se limitando a, dados de tráfego, dados de geolocalização, registos e outros dados de comunicação e os recursos a que acede e utiliza nos Websites. Recolhemos informações sobre o seu computador, dispositivo móvel e ligação à Internet, incluindo o seu endereço IP, sistema operativo, tipo de navegador, padrões de sequência de cliques (ou seja, o que clica num website), o URL do website mais recente que visitou antes de chegar aos nossos Websites, a quantidade de tempo que passou nos nossos Websites e as páginas que visualizou enquanto nos nossos Websites. Podemos obter uma estimativa aproximada da sua localização a partir do seu endereço IP quando visita os nossos Websites. Para utilizadores das nossas Aplicações Móveis, também podemos recolher e manter um histórico das suas informações de localização precisas usando tecnologias Wi-Fi e/ou Bluetooth, bem como os identificadores do seu dispositivo e coordenadas GPS (por exemplo, latitude/longitude). Se pretender impedir a recolha das suas informações de localização, ajuste as suas definições no seu dispositivo móvel para limitar o acesso da Aplicação Móvel às suas informações de localização.

Quando você usa nosso site, compartilhamos informações que coletamos de você, como seu e-mail (em forma de hash), endereço IP ou informações sobre seu navegador ou sistema operacional, com nossos parceiros de identidade/provedores de serviços. Esses parceiros retornam um código de identificação on-line que podemos armazenar em nosso cookie primário para nosso uso em publicidade on-line, no aplicativo e em canais cruzados e pode ser compartilhado com empresas de publicidade para permitir publicidade direcionada e baseada em interesses. Para desativar esse uso, clique aqui ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Monitorização comportamental. Também podemos utilizar estas tecnologias para recolher informações sobre as suas atividades online ao longo do tempo e em websites de terceiros ou outros serviços online, ou associar Informações Pessoais a outras informações recolhidas desta forma.

Análise da localização: as nossas Aplicações Móveis e Websites de navegadores móveis incluem funcionalidades (por exemplo, para o envio de uma revisão de um condutor de uma instalação de carregamento) que nos permite identificar a localização de um condutor e a localização da instalação de carregamento na qual um utilizador está atualmente localizado. Recolhemos informações como o endereço IP, ID do dispositivo e geolocalização. Os utilizadores de Aplicações Móveis podem optar por utilizar as Aplicações Móveis anonimamente ou iniciar sessão como utilizadores identificados, caso em que os dados pessoais fornecidos após o registo podem ser utilizados.

Para utilizadores das Aplicações Móveis, podemos pedir permissão para aceder a determinadas informações do seu dispositivo móvel, incluindo a sua lista de contactos, fotos e vídeos, microfone e câmara. É opcional que nos forneça acesso a estas informações. No entanto, determinadas funcionalidades das Aplicações Móveis podem não funcionar de forma ideal se decidir não nos fornecer permissão.

Web Beacons. As páginas dos nossos Websites e os nossos e-mails podem conter pequenos ficheiros eletrónicos conhecidos como web beacons (também referidos como clear gifs, pixel tags e single-pixel gifs) que nos permitem, por exemplo, contar os utilizadores que visitaram essas páginas ou abriram um e-mail e para outras estatísticas relacionadas com o website (por exemplo, registar a popularidade de determinado conteúdo do website e verificar a integridade do sistema e do servidor).

Pixéis de Rastreamento. Para além de utilizar cookies, os Websites podem empregar “pixéis de rastreamento”. Os pixéis de rastreamento envolvem a utilização de pixel tags que não são visíveis para o utilizador e consistem em algumas linhas de código informático. Os pixéis de rastreamento medem a eficácia dos anúncios e compilam estatísticas de utilização agregadas e específicas. Podemos aceder a estas pixel tags para identificar atividades e interesses que nos possam permitir corresponder melhor aos nossos Produtos, Serviços e ofertas com os seus interesses e necessidades. Por exemplo, se visitar os nossos Websites a partir de um anúncio em outro Website, o pixel tag permitirá ao anunciante rastrear se o seu anúncio conduziu o utilizador para os Websites. Se visitar os nossos Websites e o ligarmos a outro Website, também poderemos determinar que o utilizador foi direcionado para e/ou realizou uma transação com um website de terceiros.

GIF. Podemos utilizar imagens minúsculas conhecidas como clear GIFs para rastrear o comportamento dos utilizadores, incluindo estatísticas sobre quem abre os nossos e-mails.

Endereço IP. Os nossos servidores (ou os dos nossos prestadores de serviços) registam automaticamente determinadas informações de ficheiros de registo comunicadas a partir do seu navegador quando acede aos Websites. Estes registos de servidor podem incluir informações como as páginas dos Websites que visitou, o seu endereço de protocolo de Internet (“IP”), tipo de navegador e outras informações sobre como interage com os Websites. Estes ficheiros de registo são geralmente eliminados periodicamente.

Métricas e análises de terceiros. Métricas e análises de terceiros, em determinadas páginas ou funcionalidades dos Serviços, para nos ajudar a compreender e analisar o tráfego de visitantes, medir a eficácia promocional e a eficácia das nossas funcionalidades, ofertas e campanhas de marketing. Também utilizamos estas ferramentas para identificar perigos, deficiências e áreas das nossas operações que necessitam de melhoria, e para visualizar o desempenho geral e a classificação da nossa presença online. Estas ferramentas podem armazenar cookies no seu dispositivo a seu critério.

AVISO E POLÍTICA DE COOKIES

As tecnologias que utilizamos para a recolha automática de dados também incluem cookies, conforme descrito abaixo.

Cookies do navegador

Os cookies do navegador são pequenos ficheiros colocados no disco rígido do seu computador ou dispositivo móvel. Podem conter determinados dados, incluindo, entre outros, o nome do servidor que o colocou lá, um identificador sob a forma de um número único e uma data de validade (apenas alguns cookies). Os cookies do navegador são geridos pelo navegador Web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, etc.) no seu computador ou dispositivo móvel. Os diferentes tipos de cookies os quais têm finalidades diferentes são utilizados nos nossos Websites.

Cookies essenciais

Os cookies essenciais são essenciais para lhe permitir navegar nos nossos Websites e utilizar as suas funções. Sem estes, serviços como cestos de compras e faturação eletrónica não funcionariam.

Cookies de desempenho

Os cookies de desempenho recolhem informações sobre a utilização dos nossos Websites, tais como quais as páginas que são consultadas com maior frequência. Estas informações permitem-nos otimizar os nossos Websites e simplificar a navegação. Os cookies de desempenho também permitem que as nossas afiliadas e parceiros descubram se acedeu a uma das páginas do nosso Website a partir do seu site e se a sua visita levou à utilização ou compra de um Produto ou Serviço nos nossos Websites, incluindo as referências para o Produto ou Serviço adquirido. Todas as informações recolhidas pelos cookies de desempenho são agregadas e, portanto, anónimas.

Cookies de funcionalidade

Os cookies de funcionalidade permitem que os nossos Websites se lembrem das escolhas que fez ao navegar. Por exemplo, podemos armazenar a sua localização geográfica num cookie para que os Websites correspondentes à sua área sejam apresentados. Também nos podemos lembrar das suas preferências, tais como o tamanho do texto, tipo de letra e outros aspetos personalizáveis dos Websites. Os cookies de funcionalidade também podem ser capazes de acompanhar os produtos ou vídeos consultados para evitar repetição. As informações recolhidas por estes cookies não podem ser utilizadas para o identificar e não podem monitorizar a sua atividade de navegação em websites que não nos pertencem. Os cookies de funcionalidade permitem-nos apresentar publicidade personalizada ao utilizador nos nossos Websites, para compreender que partes do nosso conteúdo lhe interessam mais e que categorias de Produtos ou Serviços solicita. Alguns dos nossos prestadores de serviços estão autorizados a colocar cookies nos nossos Websites. Essas empresas também podem fornecer-lhe a opção de impedir a utilização de cookies no futuro.

Em qualquer altura, pode impedir ou cancelar a utilização futura de determinados cookies ativando a definição adequada no seu navegador para recusar aceitar cookies do navegador. No entanto, se o fizer, a sua experiência nos nossos Websites pode ser afetada; por exemplo, pode não conseguir aceder a determinadas partes dos nossos Websites. A menos que tenha ajustado as definições do seu navegador para que este recuse cookies, o nosso sistema emitirá cookies quando direcionar o seu navegador para os nossos Websites.

Cookies de armazenamento local

Determinadas funcionalidades dos nossos Websites podem utilizar objetos armazenados localmente (para recolher e armazenar informações sobre as suas preferências e navegação para, de e nos nossos Websites. Os cookies de armazenamento local não são geridos pelas mesmas definições do navegador que são utilizadas para cookies do navegador.

Também podemos combinar as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos de si fora dos nossos Websites ou Serviços com Informações Pessoais que são recolhidas através dos nossos Websites ou Serviços ou por outros meios, conforme descrito acima.

1.5 INFORMAÇÕES SOBRE DISPOSITIVOS, REDES, GEOLOCALIZAÇÃO E VE
--------------------------------------------------------------

Quando visita ou sai dos nossos Websites ou Serviços clicando numa hiperligação ou visualizando um plug-in num Website de terceiros, recebemos automaticamente o URL do Website a partir do qual veio ou aquele para o qual foi direcionado. Além disso, os anunciantes recebem o URL da página em que está quando clica em qualquer anúncio que possa aparecer nos nossos Serviços. Também recebemos o endereço de protocolo de Internet (“IP”) do seu computador ou servidor proxy que utiliza para aceder à Internet, aos detalhes do sistema operativo do seu computador, ao seu tipo de navegador de Internet, ao seu dispositivo móvel (incluindo o identificador do seu dispositivo móvel fornecido pelo seu sistema operativo do dispositivo móvel), ao seu sistema operativo móvel (se estiver a aceder aos nossos websites ou serviços utilizando um dispositivo móvel) e ao nome do seu ISP (Internet Service Provider \[Prestador de Serviços de Internet\]) ou da sua operadora móvel.

1.6 INQUÉRITOS
--------------

Nós ou partes não afiliadas podemos realizar inquéritos aos utilizadores relativamente aos nossos Serviços. Algumas partes não afiliadas podem direcionar anúncios ou promoções para o utilizador com base nas suas respostas ao inquérito. Nós ou partes não afiliadas desenvolvemos novos programas ou produtos com base nas informações que o utilizador partilha nos inquéritos. Podemos utilizar partes não afiliadas para oferecer ao utilizador incentivos financeiros ou outros incentivos para participar em inquéritos. Se a oferta de incentivos exigir as informações de contacto do utilizador, poderá ser pedido ao utilizador que forneça Informações Pessoais à parte não afiliada que cumpre a oferta de incentivo, a qual será utilizada apenas com a finalidade de fornecer os incentivos prometidos e verificar as informações de contacto do utilizador. Cabe ao utilizador decidir se fornece estas informações ou se pretende tirar partido de uma oferta de incentivo. O consentimento do utilizador para a utilização de quaisquer Informações Pessoais para os fins definidos no inquérito será explicitamente solicitado pela parte não afiliada que as conduz. Para optar por não participar nos nossos inquéritos, o utilizador pode enviar-nos o seu pedido utilizando as informações de contacto abaixo.

2\. NATUREZA E FINALIDADE DO TRATAMENTO DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS
===============================================================

Utilizamos as informações que recolhemos sobre si ou que nos fornece, incluindo quaisquer Informações Pessoais, para uma ou mais das seguintes finalidades:

* Para lhe apresentar os nossos Websites e aplicações móveis e o seu conteúdo.
* Para lhe fornecer informações e responder às suas perguntas sobre Produtos ou Serviços que nos solicite e informações sobre novos produtos e serviços, descontos, promoções especiais ou eventos futuros, e funcionalidades ou ofertas que acreditamos serem do seu interesse ou relativamente a uma promoção, concurso ou sorteio no qual tenha participado
* Para processar informações de conta e pagamentos de transações, incluindo, mas não se limitando a, taxas de Produtos e/ou Serviços, e pagamentos e reembolsos de quaisquer Produtos ou Serviços adquiridos (embora não recebamos o seu número de cartão de crédito ou débito completo).
* Para processar descontos, ofertas, recompensas de fidelidade e/ou pedidos de descontos, formulários e aplicações e coordenar com o fabricante, revendedor e/ou grossista.
* Para lhe fornecer notificações sobre a sua conta, incluindo notificações de expiração e renovação.
* Para notificá-lo sobre informações ou alterações aos nossos Websites, às nossas políticas, termos ou a quaisquer Produtos ou Serviços que oferecemos ou fornecemos, ou sobre a sua conta.
* Para tratar Informações Pessoais ou outras informações que nos envie.
* Para permitir que participe em funcionalidades interativas nos nossos Websites.
* Para melhorar os nossos Produtos e Serviços e desenvolver novos Produtos e Serviços, por exemplo, analisando as tendências do utilizador e medindo os dados demográficos e interesses.
* Para o funcionamento interno do Website, Serviço e sistema, administração, manutenção, auditorias internas e revisões, diagnóstico de problemas técnicos e manutenção da segurança.
* Para investigar qualquer violação dos nossos Termos de Utilização ou da presente Política de Privacidade.
* Para acompanhar potenciais problemas e tendências com a utilização dos nossos Websites e Serviços por parte dos utilizadores e personalizar o nosso apoio para melhor o servir.
* Para fornecer estatísticas sobre os níveis de utilização dos Websites e outras informações relacionadas aos nossos Prestadores de Serviços.
* Para notificá-lo de incidentes de privacidade de dados ou fornecer-lhe informações legalmente exigidas.
* Para solicitar a sua participação em classificações, avaliações, inquéritos, grupos especializados ou outras iniciativas que nos ajudam a reunir informações utilizadas para desenvolver e melhorar os nossos Produtos e Serviços.
* Para cumprir qualquer outra finalidade para a qual forneça Informações Pessoais.
* De qualquer outra forma que possamos descrever e para a qual obtemos o seu consentimento quando fornece as informações.

Utilizamos cookies, clear gifs e informações do ficheiro de registo para: (a) lembrar informações para que não tenha de as reintroduzir durante a sua visita ou da próxima vez que visitar os Websites; (b) fornecer serviços personalizados, conteúdo e informações personalizados; (c) monitorizar a eficácia dos nossos Serviços; (d) monitorizar métricas agregadas, tais como o número total de visitantes, tráfego, e padrões demográficos; (e) diagnosticar ou corrigir problemas de tecnologia comunicados pelos nossos utilizadores ou engenheiros associados a determinados endereços IP; e/ou, (f) ajudá-lo a aceder eficientemente às suas informações depois de iniciar sessão.

Os dados estatísticos que recolhemos automaticamente ajudam-nos a melhorar os nossos Websites e a fornecer Produtos e Serviços melhores e mais personalizados, incluindo, mas não se limitando a, permitindo-nos: estimar o tamanho do nosso público/visitante e padrões de utilização, armazenar informações sobre as suas preferências, permitir-nos personalizar e melhorar os nossos Websites, acelerar as suas pesquisas e/ou reconhecê-lo quando regressa aos nossos Websites.

Podemos recolher e utilizar as informações da sua sessão de carregamento de VE (por exemplo, tempo de carregamento, consumo de energia, propriedade da estação e dados, etc.) e a marca, modelo e ano do seu veículo para administrar a sua conta, como para distinguir entre vários veículos ou utilizadores que partilham uma única conta e para fins analíticos.

Na medida em que não consinta as práticas de tratamento de informações aqui estabelecidas, pode ter o direito de optar por não as utilizar. Todos os pedidos de autoexclusão devem ser dirigidos para [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Na medida em que os pedidos de exclusão sejam honrados, terão efeito no tratamento futuro e não no tratamento que ocorreu com base no consentimento prévio.

2.1 TOMADA DE DECISÕES AUTOMATIZADAS
------------------------------------

Podemos utilizar as suas Informações Pessoais que nos fornece e que obtemos de outras fontes para compreender melhor os seus interesses, para que possamos tentar prever em que outros Produtos, Serviços e informações pode estar mais interessado. Esta prática envolve tomar decisões automatizadas sobre si com base nestas informações para nos permitir melhor adaptar as nossas interações consigo para torná-las mais relevantes e interessantes. Pode opor-se a que o façamos, a qualquer momento, ou pedir-nos mais informações sobre a metodologia aplicada nos nossos processos de tomada de decisões automatizadas, contactando-nos (consulte a Secção 12 abaixo).

2.2 MENSAGENS DE TEXTO
----------------------

Os nossos Serviços podem incluir o envio de mensagens do Serviço de Mensagens Curtas (Short Message Service“SMS”), que pode enviar até duas mensagens por dia para o seu dispositivo sem fios (a menos que comunique mais connosco), mas a frequência das mensagens pode variar.  Quando consente expressamente em receber mensagens de texto nossas e fornecer um número de telemóvel, está a consentir expressamente em receber mensagens de texto informativas e transacionais recorrentes de ou em nosso nome para o número que forneceu. Ao consentir expressamente em receber mensagens SMS da nossa parte e ao fornecer um número de telemóvel, garante e declara que é o proprietário do número de telemóvel que nos fornece. Podemos utilizar as suas informações para o contactar sobre a sua utilização, compras, devoluções (se disponíveis), atualizações do Website, realização de inquéritos ou comunicações informativas e relacionadas com os serviços, incluindo atualizações de segurança importantes. Depois de nos enviar a mensagem SMS “STOP”, enviar-lhe-emos uma mensagem SMS para confirmar que cancelou a sua subscrição. Em alternativa, pode enviar-nos o seu pedido por e-mail, incluindo o endereço de e-mail e o número de telefone que registou connosco, ou por qualquer outro meio razoável. Depois disso, deixará de receber mensagens SMS da nossa parte. Se quiser aderir novamente, basta registar-se como fez na primeira vez e começaremos a enviar-lhe mensagens SMS novamente. Para obter ajuda, responda a uma mensagem de texto com AJUDA. Podem aplicar-se taxas de mensagens e dados, dependendo do seu plano de telemóvel. As transportadoras não são responsáveis por mensagens atrasadas ou não entregues.

2.3 PLUG-INS DE REDES SOCIAIS
-----------------------------

Integramos interfaces ou plug-ins de programas de aplicativos de redes sociais (“Plug-ins”) de redes sociais, incluindo Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest e/ou possivelmente outras empresas, nos Websites. Para se registar como utilizador connosco, poderá ter a opção de iniciar sessão utilizando o seu início de sessão no Facebook ou em outra rede social.

Por exemplo, quando visita os nossos Websites, o plugin cria uma ligação direta entre o seu navegador e o servidor do Facebook. Isto permite ao Facebook receber informações sobre a sua visita aos nossos Websites com o seu endereço IP. Se clicar no botão “Gosto” do Facebook enquanto estiver ligado à sua conta do Facebook, pode associar o conteúdo dos nossos Websites ao seu perfil do Facebook. Isto permite ao Facebook atribuir a sua visita aos nossos Websites à sua conta de utilizador. Tenha em atenção que, como fornecedor dos Websites, não recebemos qualquer notificação sobre o conteúdo dos dados transmitidos ou a sua utilização pelo Facebook. Se não quiser que o Facebook atribua a sua visita aos nossos Websites à sua conta de utilizador do Facebook, termine a sessão na sua conta de utilizador do Facebook.

Se iniciar sessão através de um plug-in de rede social, autoriza-nos a aceder a determinadas informações de conta a partir desse site de redes sociais, como o seu perfil público nas redes sociais (consistente com as suas definições de privacidade no site das redes sociais), o seu endereço de e-mail, interesses, gostos, sexo, aniversário, histórico de educação, relações, interesses, cidade atual, fotos, descrição pessoal, lista de amigos, e informações e fotografias dos seus amigos nas redes sociais que possam ser amigos nas redes sociais com outros utilizadores. Os plug-ins podem transferir informações a seu respeito para a respetiva plataforma sem qualquer ação da sua parte. Estas informações podem incluir o seu número de identificação de utilizador da plataforma, em que website se encontra e muito mais. Interagir com um plug-in transmitirá informações diretamente para a rede social desse plug-in e essas informações poderão ser visíveis a outras pessoas nessa plataforma. Os plug-ins são controlados pela política de privacidade do respetivo site de redes sociais (disponível no seu site), e não pela nossa Política de Privacidade.

3\. COMO DIVULGAMOS INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS A PARTES NÃO AFILIADAS
===============================================================

3.1 TIPOS DE PARTES NÃO AFILIADAS
---------------------------------

Podemos divulgar ou divulgar as suas Informações Pessoais, no todo ou em parte, aos seguintes tipos de partes não afiliadas e para um ou mais dos seguintes fins:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Tipo de Parte Não Afiliada | Finalidade |
| Fornecedores de armazenamento ou alojamento de dados | armazenamento e transmissão seguros dos seus dados |
| Fornecedores de serviços de base de dados e software | gestão e seguimento dos seus dados |
| Consultores jurídicos e de conformidade, como consultores externos, auditores externos ou consultores fiscais | prestação de serviços profissionais |
| Fornecedores de gestão de identidade | fins de autenticação |
| Fornecedores de soluções de pagamento | processamento seguro de pagamentos que nos fornece |
| Fabricantes, retalhistas e grossistas | envio, processamento e gestão de abatimentos, descontos, ofertas, prémios de fidelização e similares |
| Fornecedores de serviços de entrega e envio | cumprimento e entrega de Produtos, Serviços e mercadorias |
| Prestadores de inquéritos e investigação | realização estudos em nosso nome |
| Parceiros publicitários, incluindo fornecedores de redes sociais | apresentação de anúncios direcionados |

Para qualquer transferência de Informações Pessoais que não seja razoavelmente necessária para alcançar as finalidades para as quais está a envolver-se com a PlugShare (como para fins de marketing ou inquéritos), tem o direito de optar por não participar desse tratamento. Para exercer o seu direito de autoexclusão, contacte-nos através do e-mail [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 PRESTADORES DE SERVIÇOS, PARCEIROS COMERCIAIS E SUBCONTRATADOS
------------------------------------------------------------------

 Podemos partilhar as suas Informações Pessoais com Prestadores de Serviços que prestam serviços em nosso nome, conforme discutido acima. Estes Prestadores de Serviços podem ter acesso às suas Informações Pessoais para nos prestar estes serviços ou em nosso nome. Se contratarmos Prestadores de Serviços para qualquer das situações anteriores, a utilização das suas Informações Pessoais estará vinculada a obrigações de confidencialidade e a sua utilização das Informações Pessoais será restrita à prestação dos seus serviços. Podemos armazenar Informações Pessoais em locais fora do nosso controlo direto (por exemplo, em servidores ou bases de dados localizados ou co-localizados com Prestadores de Serviços de alojamento de dados).  

3.3 PUBLICIDADE COMPORTAMENTAL DE CONTEXTO CRUZADO
--------------------------------------------------

Somos obrigados a divulgar se partilhamos Informações Pessoais com terceiros que estejam envolvidos em publicidade comportamental (direcionada) de contexto cruzado. Nos doze (12) meses anteriores, divulgámos ou podemos ter divulgado as seguintes categorias de Informações Pessoais num contexto que pode, ao abrigo de determinadas leis (por exemplo, , “CPRA” (California Privacy Rights Act, Lei do Direito à Privacidade da Califórnia) da Califórnia, RGPD ou RGPD do Reino Unido) ser considerado uma venda:

* Identificadores
* Atividade na Internet ou outra atividade de rede semelhante
* Dados de geolocalização

Pode optar por não participar nesta partilha clicando nas indicações de não participação que aparecerão no aviso que lhe é enviado quando visitar as nossas aplicações móveis ou Websites pela primeira vez.

3.4 TRANSFERÊNCIAS EMPRESARIAIS
-------------------------------

Reconhece (e não se oporá) à nossa divulgação ou transferência das suas Informações Pessoais, Informações Pessoais Não Identificadas, e outras informações que nos forneça, bem como os direitos que concedeu ou reconheceu na presente Política de Privacidade (coletivamente, “Informação Transferida”) para um comprador ou adquirente potencial ou real da nossa empresa ou outro sucessor com a finalidade de considerar ou de se submeter a uma fusão, alienação, reestruturação, reorganização, dissolução, alteração no controlo, ou transferência de alguns ou todos os nossos ativos (cada um dos anteriores referidos como uma “Transferência”), quer seja como empresa em atividade ou como parte da falência, liquidação ou outro processo judicial, nos quais as Informações Pessoais detidas por nós detidas estão entre os ativos transferidos, e concorda em não se opor a tal divulgação e/ou transferência. Não podemos fazer quaisquer declarações relativamente à utilização ou transferência de Informações Transferidas que possamos ter em caso de falência, reorganização, insolvência, liquidação ou uma cessão para benefício dos credores. Além disso, exceto conforme exigido por lei, não somos nem seremos responsáveis por qualquer violação de segurança por parte de quaisquer partes não afiliadas ou por quaisquer ações de quaisquer partes não afiliadas que recebam qualquer Informação Transferida que nos seja divulgada.

3.5 DIVULGAÇÕES NECESSÁRIAS; PROTEÇÃO DE DIREITOS; SEGURANÇA
------------------------------------------------------------

Salvo se descrito em contrário na presente Política de Privacidade, não divulgaremos as suas Informações Pessoais a qualquer parte não afiliada, a menos que tal seja exigido por lei, ordem judicial, processo legal (por exemplo, intimação), incluindo, mas não limitado a, para responder a qualquer pedido do governo, regulamentar, ou de licenciamento, ou se acreditarmos que tal ação é necessária para: (a) cumprir a lei, cumprir o processo legal que nos foi interposto ou às nossas afiliadas, subsidiárias, fornecedores contratados, ou parceiros de afinidade, ou investigar, prevenir, ou tomar medidas relativamente a atividades ilegais suspeitas ou reais; (b) aplicar os nossos Termos ou contrato de cliente (incluindo para fins de faturação e cobrança); (c) tomar precauções contra a responsabilidade; (d) investigar e defender-nos contra quaisquer reivindicações ou alegações de terceiros; (e) auxiliar agências governamentais de aplicação da lei ou para cumprir requisitos de segurança nacionais ou outros; (f) para proteger a segurança ou integridade dos nossos Websites, nosso, Serviços, e aplicações móveis; ou, (g) exercer ou proteger os direitos, propriedade, ou a nossa segurança pessoal, os nossos utilizadores ou outros. 

Tentaremos notificá-lo, quando praticável, sobre estes pedidos, a menos que: (i) o fornecimento de notificação seja proibido pelo próprio processo legal, por ordem judicial que recebemos, ou pela lei aplicável, ou (ii) acreditemos que o fornecimento de notificação seria fútil, ineficaz, crie um risco de lesão ou danos corporais ou outros danos a um indivíduo ou grupo, ou crie ou aumente um risco de fraude sobre nós, os nossos utilizadores, os nossos Websites, Serviços ou aplicações móveis. Nos casos em que cumprimos pedidos legais sem aviso prévio por estes motivos, tentaremos notificar esse utilizador sobre o pedido após o facto de determinarmos de boa-fé que já não estamos legalmente proibidos de o fazer e que não se aplicam quaisquer cenários de risco descritos neste parágrafo.

3.6 DIVULGAÇÃO DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS NÃO IDENTIFICADAS
--------------------------------------------------------

Podemos partilhar Informações Pessoais Não Identificadas (incluindo, mas não limitado a, dados de utilização anónimos, páginas de referência/saída e URL, endereço IP, tipos de plataforma, número de cliques, etc.) com partes não afiliadas de qualquer forma que escolhamos e para qualquer finalidade, como para administração do sistema e para monitorizar a utilização dos Websites; para medir o número de visitas aos nossos Websites, tempo médio gasto, número de páginas visualizadas; e monitorizar várias outras estatísticas do Website para melhorar o conteúdo.

4\.  PEDIDOS “DO NOT TRACK” (NÃO RASTREAR)
==========================================

Alguns navegadores Web (incluindo Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox e Chrome) incorporam uma funcionalidade “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) ou semelhante que sinaliza aos websites que um utilizador não quer que a sua atividade e comportamento online sejam monitorizados. Se um website que responde a um sinal DNT específico receber o sinal DNT, o navegador pode bloquear esse website para o mesmo que não recolha determinadas informações sobre o utilizador do navegador. Nem todos os navegadores oferecem uma opção DNT e os sinais DNT ainda não são uniformes. Por este motivo, muitos operadores de websites, incluindo a PlugShare, não respondem a sinais DNT.

5\. COMUNICAÇÕES, PREFERÊNCIAS E AUTOEXCLUSÃO DA PLUGSHARE
==========================================================

Ao facultar-nos o seu endereço de e-mail, autoriza a nossa utilização do endereço de e-mail para lhe enviar notificações relacionadas com o Serviço por e-mail, incluindo, mas não se limitando a, quaisquer notificações exigidas por lei (por exemplo, notificação de incidentes de privacidade ou segurança de dados), em vez da comunicação por correio postal. Concorda também que podemos enviar-lhe notificações de atividade relativamente aos nossos Produtos, Serviços, Websites, aplicações móveis, as suas Informações Pessoais ou qualquer aspeto da nossa relação, para o endereço de e-mail que nos fornece, de acordo com quaisquer definições de privacidade aplicáveis. Poderemos utilizar o seu endereço de e-mail para lhe enviar outras mensagens ou conteúdo, tais como, mas não se limitando a, newsletters, adições ou alterações a funcionalidades do Serviço, ou ofertas especiais. Se não quiser receber essas mensagens de e-mail, pode optar por não receber clicando em Cancelar subscrição, quando disponível. A exclusão pode impedir que receba mensagens de e-mail relativas a atualizações, melhorias, funcionalidades especiais, anúncios ou ofertas. Não pode optar por não receber e-mails relacionados com o Serviço. Se optou por não nos fornecer um e-mail ou outro endereço, poderá não receber os nossos e-mails relacionados com o Serviço.

Através da página de definições da sua conta de utilizador, pode aceder e, em alguns casos, editar ou eliminar determinadas informações que nos forneceu, tais como nome e palavra-passe, endereço de e-mail, endereço, informações de perfil de utilizador, etc. As informações que pode ver, atualizar e eliminar podem mudar à medida que os Produtos, Websites, Serviços ou as nossas práticas mudam. Se tiver alguma dúvida sobre a visualização ou atualização das informações que temos em arquivo sobre si, entre em contacto connosco. No entanto, quando atualiza informações, poderemos manter uma cópia das informações não revistas nos nossos registos. Pode solicitar a eliminação da sua conta enviando-nos um e-mail. É da sua responsabilidade manter o seu endereço de e-mail atual connosco. Dependendo do estado ou país em que reside, poderá ter direitos adicionais. Consulte abaixo para obter mais informações.

6\. PROGRAMADORES QUE UTILIZAM SERVIÇOS DE PLATAFORMA DA PLUGSHARE
==================================================================

Colaboramos e permitimos que terceiros utilizem a plataforma de programadores da PlugShare para oferecer serviços e funcionalidades em conjunto com a PlugShare. Estes programadores terceiros negociaram um acordo para utilizar a tecnologia da plataforma da PlugShare ou concordaram com as nossas Interfaces de Programação de Aplicações (Application Programming Interfaces) (“API”) e termos de Plug-In para criar aplicações de plataforma de software (“Aplicações de Plataforma”). Tanto os acordos negociados como a nossa API e termos de utilização de Plug-In contêm restrições sobre como terceiros podem aceder, armazenar e utilizar as Informações Pessoais que fornece à PlugShare. Se optar por utilizar uma Aplicação de Plataforma, ser-lhe-á pedido que confirme a aceitação da política de privacidade e do acordo de utilizador do programador de terceiros. Para revogar a permissão concedida a uma Aplicação de Plataforma, visite as suas definições. No entanto, tenha em atenção que, mesmo que revogue a permissão concedida a uma Aplicação da Plataforma, as suas ligações podem continuar a utilizar a Aplicação da Plataforma, pelo que a Aplicação da Plataforma pode ainda ter acesso a determinadas informações sobre si, tal como as suas ligações.

7\. RETENÇÃO DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS
====================================

O período de tempo durante o qual conservamos as suas Informações Pessoais depende das finalidades para as quais as utilizamos. Conservaremos as suas Informações Pessoais enquanto a sua conta estiver ativa, ou enquanto for um titular de conta registado ou utilizador dos nossos Serviços ou enquanto tivermos outro objetivo comercial para o fazer (como, por exemplo, mas não limitado a, negócios, assuntos fiscais, ou para fins legais) e, depois disso, por um período não superior ao exigido ou permitido por lei, ou a nossa política de retenção de registos, razoavelmente necessário para fins internos de relatório e reconciliação, ou para lhe fornecer feedback ou informações que possa solicitar. Este período de retenção está sujeito à nossa revisão e alteração. Podemos reter Informações Pessoais Não Identificadas durante o tempo que considerarmos apropriado.

Após a cessação ou desativação da sua conta de utilizador, podemos reter as suas informações de perfil e todas as informações publicadas em áreas públicas dos Websites. Após a cessação ou desativação da sua conta de utilizador, podemos reter as suas Informações Pessoais e outros dados, mas iremos mantê-los confidenciais de acordo com os Termos, a presente Política de Privacidade e conforme exigido pela lei aplicável. Temos o direito de eliminar todas as suas Informações Pessoais e outros dados após o encerramento da sua conta de utilizador sem aviso prévio.

8\. RECOLHA NÃO INTENCIONAL DE DADOS DE CRIANÇAS
================================================

Não recolhemos, solicitamos ou mantemos intencionalmente Informações Pessoais de qualquer utilizador com idade inferior a 18 anos ou permitimos conscientemente que tais utilizadores se registem ou utilizem os nossos Serviços. Se tiver menos de 18 anos, não nos envie quaisquer Informações Pessoais. Caso tenhamos conhecimento de que recolhemos Informações Pessoais de uma criança com idade inferior a 18 anos sem verificação do consentimento parental, envidaremos esforços comercialmente razoáveis para eliminar essas informações da nossa base de dados.

9\. QUANDO AS INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS SÃO TRATADAS E ARMAZENADAS; LEGISLAÇÃO APLICÁVEL
===================================================================================

Temos a nossa sede nos Estados Unidos. As Informações Pessoais que nós ou os nossos Prestadores de Serviços recolhemos podem ser armazenadas e tratadas em servidores dentro ou fora dos Estados Unidos e onde quer que nós e os nossos Prestadores de Serviços tenhamos instalações em todo o mundo, e determinadas informações podem ser acessíveis por pessoas ou empresas fora dos Estados Unidos que nos prestam serviços. O utilizador autoriza a transmissão e/ou transferência das suas Informações Pessoais, por nós e pelos nossos Prestadores de Serviços para, ou o acesso às mesmas, jurisdições que podem não proporcionar níveis equivalentes de proteção de dados à sua jurisdição nacional. Tomaremos medidas razoáveis para garantir que as suas Informações Pessoais recebem um nível adequado de proteção nas jurisdições em que as tratamos.

As leis dos EUA aplicam-se na medida em que seja residente nos Estados Unidos. Caso contrário, a presente Política de Privacidade e todas as outras questões serão interpretadas e interpretadas de acordo com as leis da província/estado e federais da jurisdição em que reside. As jurisdições fora da sua residência podem ter leis de privacidade diferentes das que constam da sua, incluindo o direito de aplicação da lei e autoridades governamentais a aceder às Informações Pessoais.  Na medida em que tratamos dados fora do seu país, realizamos uma avaliação de impacto na privacidade para determinar que os nossos Prestadores de Serviços podem oferecer substancialmente o mesmo nível de proteção exigido na sua jurisdição e celebramos contratos para reforçar ainda mais as obrigações para tratar adequadamente as suas Informações Pessoais.

10\. SEGURANÇA
==============

Implementámos salvaguardas de segurança técnicas e organizacionais concebidas para proteger as suas Informações Pessoais contra perda acidental e contra acesso, utilização, destruição, alteração e divulgação não autorizados. No entanto, tenha em mente que a Internet não é um ambiente 100% seguro. É da sua responsabilidade proteger a segurança das suas informações de início de sessão, ter cuidado ao transmitir quaisquer Informações Pessoais através de e-mails, mensagens instantâneas e meios de comunicação semelhantes e manter boas práticas de segurança da Internet. Nunca lhe enviaremos um e-mail a pedir a sua palavra-passe ou outras informações de início de sessão da conta. Se receber um e-mail com esse pedido, envie-nos o mesmo para que possamos investigar.

11\. DIREITOS ADICIONAIS DOS TITULARES DE DADOS PARA RESIDENTES EM DETERMINADAS JURISDIÇÕES DESCRITAS NOS AVISOS DE PRIVACIDADE SUPLEMENTARES
=============================================================================================================================================

O seguinte explica cada direito de titular de dados descrito nas Notificações Suplementares de Privacidade:

* Direito a receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade: Tem o direito de receber determinadas informações legalmente exigidas no momento ou antes do momento da recolha ou em resposta ao seu pedido.
* Direito à eliminação: Pode solicitar que eliminemos quaisquer Informações Pessoais sobre si que recolhemos de si, sujeito a determinadas exceções.
* Direito de correção: Pode solicitar que corrijamos quaisquer Informações Pessoais incorretas que mantenhamos sobre si.
* Direito a saber: Pode solicitar que lhe forneçamos informações específicas sobre como tratámos as suas Informações Pessoais, o que inclui fornecer-lhe uma cópia das partes específicas de Informações Pessoais que recolhemos sobre si num formato portátil.
* Direito à não discriminação: Tem o direito de não ser discriminado por exercer os seus direitos enquanto titular dos dados. Isto significa não recusar bens ou serviços ao utilizador, cobrar preços ou taxas diferentes ou fornecer um nível diferente de qualidade para produtos ou serviços em resultado do exercício dos direitos do titular dos dados.
* Direitos de exclusão: Pode solicitar a exclusão da Venda e Partilha das suas Informações Pessoais, publicidade comportamental ou direcionada em contexto cruzado, tomada de decisões automatizada ou definição de perfis, na medida em que tais atividades sejam definidas e restritas ao abrigo das leis aplicáveis.
* Direito de Restrição ou Oposição ao Tratamento: Pode pedir-nos para suprimir ou cessar o tratamento de algumas das suas Informações Pessoais, mas podemos ainda assim armazenar as suas Informações Pessoais.  
* Direito de limitar a utilização das suas Informações Pessoais Sensíveis: Pode solicitar a limitação da utilização das suas Informações Pessoais Sensíveis apenas para os fins autorizados pelas leis aplicáveis.
* Direito de Apresentar uma Reclamação: Tem o direito de apresentar uma reclamação junto da sua autoridade local de proteção de dados se considerar que o tratamento de Informações Pessoais relacionadas consigo infringe os seus direitos.
* Direito de retirar o consentimento: Na medida em que o nosso tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais se baseie unicamente no seu consentimento, pode retirar esse consentimento a qualquer momento.

12\. INFORMAÇÕES DE CONTACTO
============================

A PlugShare designou um Encarregado de Proteção de Dados como o indivíduo que supervisionará a conformidade com os requisitos de privacidade. O Encarregado de Proteção de Dados da PlugShare pode ser contactado no endereço abaixo, em relação a quaisquer questões relacionadas com a política de privacidade.

Se tiver alguma dúvida ou comentário sobre esta Política de Privacidade ou sobre as nossas práticas de privacidade, contacte-nos através de: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 EUA; A/C: Encarregado de Proteção de Dados; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

AVISO DE PRIVACIDADE PARA RESIDENTES DE DETERMINADOS ESTADOS DOS EUA
====================================================================

Se residir na Califórnia, Virgínia, Colorado, Utah ou Connecticut (ocasionalmente referido como “Consumidor”), as leis estatais conferem-lhe direitos adicionais relativamente à nossa utilização das suas Informações Pessoais.

LEI “SHINE THE LIGHT” DA CALIFÓRNIA
-----------------------------------

A Secção 1798.83 do Código Civil da Califórnia, conhecida como a lei “Shine The Light”, permite que quaisquer utilizadores residentes na Califórnia solicitem e obtenham de nós uma lista das Informações Pessoais (se existentes) que divulgamos a terceiros para fins de marketing direto no ano civil anterior e os nomes e endereços desses terceiros. Os pedidos podem ser feitos apenas uma vez por ano e são gratuitos.

LEI DE PROTEÇÃO DE PRIVACIDADE ONLINE DA CALIFÓRNIA (“CALOPPA”; CALIF. NEG. e PROF. CÓDIGO § 22575-22578, DISPONÍVEL [AQUI](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D))
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

A CalOPPA aplica-se apenas a empresas que recolhem Informações Pessoais de residentes na Califórnia.

1. COMO RESPONDEMOS PARA NÃO RASTREAR SINAIS.

Alguns navegadores Web transmitem sinais de “não rastrear” (DNT/GPC) para os sites e outros serviços online com os quais o seu navegador Web comunica. Atualmente, não há nenhuma norma que governe aquilo que os sites devem fazer, se for caso disso, quando recebem estes sinais; no entanto, dispomos atualmente de medidas para agir em resposta a estes sinais.

2. ACOMPANHAMENTO COMPORTAMENTAL DE TERCEIROS

Também podemos utilizar estas tecnologias para recolher informações sobre as suas atividades online ao longo do tempo e em websites de terceiros ou outros serviços online, ou para associar Informações Pessoais a outras informações recolhidas desta forma. Podemos utilizar Informações Pessoais para seguir os padrões de clique e navegação dos utilizadores.

LEI DE PRIVACIDADE DO CONSUMIDOR DA CALIFÓRNIA DE 2018 (“CCPA”, DISPONÍVEL [AQUI](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) E SEU SUCESSOR, A LEI DE DIREITOS DE PRIVACIDADE DA CALIFÓRNIA DE 2020 (“CPRA”, DISPONÍVEL [AQUI](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)).
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

A tabela abaixo detalha como divulgamos as informações pessoais que recolhemos sobre si:

| Categoria | Categorias de terceiros não afiliados a quem divulgamos informações pessoais | Categorias de terceiros não afiliados a quem vendemos ou partilhamos informações pessoais |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificadores | Fornecedores de armazenamento ou alojamento de dados<br><br>Fornecedores de gestão de identidade<br><br>Fornecedores de soluções de pagamento<br><br>Prestadores de inquéritos e investigação<br><br>Parceiros publicitários, incluindo fornecedores de redes sociais | n/a |
| Demografia | Prestadores de inquéritos e investigação | n/a |
| Informações comerciais | n/a | n/a |
| Atividade na Internet ou outra rede eletrónica; informações do dispositivo | Fornecedores de armazenamento ou alojamento de dados<br><br>Fornecedores de serviços de base de dados e software<br><br>Fornecedores de gestão de identidade<br><br>Parceiros publicitários, incluindo fornecedores de redes sociais | n/a |
| Geolocalização | Fornecedores de armazenamento ou alojamento de dados<br><br>Fornecedores de serviços de base de dados e software<br><br>Parceiros publicitários, incluindo fornecedores de redes sociais | n/a |
| Outro | Fornecedores de armazenamento ou alojamento de dados<br><br>Fornecedores de serviços de base de dados e software<br><br>Prestadores de inquéritos e investigação<br><br>Parceiros publicitários, incluindo fornecedores de redes sociais | Fabricantes, retalhistas e grossistas |

Pode contactar-nos para exercer os seguintes direitos ao abrigo da CCPA e da CPRA (consulte a secção 11 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal para descrições destes direitos):

1. Direito a receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade.
2. Direito de saber o seguinte:

* As categorias de Informações Pessoais que recolhemos sobre si.
* As categorias de fontes para as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos sobre si.
* O nosso objetivo comercial ou comercial para recolher essas Informações Pessoais.
* As categorias de terceiros com quem partilhamos essas Informações Pessoais.
* As partes específicas das Informações Pessoais que recolhemos sobre si (também designadas por pedido de portabilidade de dados) e que lhe fornecemos uma cópia em formato eletrónico ou em papel.
* Se divulgarmos as suas Informações Pessoais para fins comerciais, uma lista que divulga divulgações para fins comerciais, identificando as categorias de Informações Pessoais que cada categoria de destinatário obteve.

3. Direito à eliminação.
4. Direito à correção.
5. Direito de exclusão de publicidade comportamental em contexto cruzado, venda ou partilha de Informações Pessoais, tratamento de Informações Pessoais para definição de perfis e tomada de decisões automatizada.
6. Direito de limitar a utilização das suas Informações Pessoais Sensíveis. Queira assinalar que não usamos Informações Pessoais Sensíveis sobre si para fins não autorizados pela CCPA e pela CPRA.

LEI DE PROTEÇÃO DE DADOS DO CONSUMIDOR DA VIRGÍNIA (VCDPA), LEI DE PRIVACIDADE DO COLORADO (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), LEI DE PRIVACIDADE DO CONSUMIDOR DO UTAH (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) E LEI DE PRIVACIDADE DE DADOS DO CONNECTICUT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Pode contactar-nos para exercer os seguintes direitos ao abrigo destas leis específicas do estado:

1. Direito a receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade.
2. Direito de saber.
3. Direito à eliminação.
4. Direito à correção.
5. Direito de exclusão de publicidade direcionada ou da venda de informações Pessoais.
6. Direito de exclusão da definição de perfis (processamento automatizado de informações pessoais para fins de análise ou previsão das características de um indivíduo ou do seu comportamento futuro, resultando em decisões que afetam os direitos substantivos de uma pessoa).  
7. Os consumidores da Virgínia, Colorado e Connecticut também têm o direito de recorrer das nossas decisões sobre os seus pedidos de titulares de dados, contactando-nos através do mesmo método para enviar um pedido. Envie uma cópia ou refira especificamente a nossa decisão sobre o seu pedido de titular de dados, para que possamos abordar adequadamente o seu recurso. Responderemos ao seu recurso de acordo com a lei aplicável.

NEVADA
------

Conforme descrito acima, podemos vender os seus identificadores ou outras informações de identificação que recolhemos dos nossos Websites e Serviços online a partes não afiliadas para fins de monitorização de comportamento entre contextos, na aceção da lei do Nevada. Tem o direito de optar por não vender ou licenciar essas categorias de informações pessoais sobre si a partes não afiliadas.

EXERCER DIREITOS
----------------

Para exercer os direitos de acesso, correção, portabilidade de dados e eliminação descritos acima, envie-nos um pedido usando o nosso formulário disponível [aqui](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Apenas você ou uma pessoa que tenha autorizado a agir em seu nome pode fazer um pedido relacionado com as suas informações pessoais. Também pode fazer um pedido em nome do seu filho menor. Se recebermos um pedido de uma pessoa para exercer o direito em seu nome, solicitaremos uma cópia da sua permissão assinada na qual autoriza o envio de tais pedidos em seu nome e entraremos em contacto consigo para confirmar diretamente essa autorização. Só pode efetuar um pedido de acesso ou portabilidade de dados duas vezes num período de 12 meses. O pedido verificável do Consumidor tem de:

* Fornecer informações suficientes que nos permitam verificar razoavelmente se é a pessoa sobre quem recolhemos Informações Pessoais ou que um representante autorizado fez o pedido.
* Descreva o seu pedido com detalhes suficientes que nos permitam compreender, avaliar e responder adequadamente ao mesmo.

Não podemos responder ao seu pedido ou fornecer-lhe Informações Pessoais se não pudermos verificar a sua identidade ou autoridade para fazer o pedido e confirmar que as Informações Pessoais estão relacionadas consigo. A apresentação de um pedido não obriga a criar uma conta connosco. Apenas utilizaremos as Informações Pessoais fornecidas num pedido para verificar a identidade ou autoridade do requerente para fazer o pedido.

Para exercer os direitos de exclusão da publicidade comportamental em contexto cruzado, da publicidade direcionada ou da partilha de Informações Pessoais conforme descrito acima, a exclusão terá de ser efetuada com base na plataforma em que está.  Queira assinalar que o seu pedido de exclusão é específico para o dispositivo e plataforma em que o pedido é apresentado, pelo que poderá ter de enviar vários pedidos caso pretenda autoexcluir-se destas atividades de tratamento específicas no que se refere a vários dispositivos e plataformas. Clique:

* aqui para desativar o Plugshare.com (plataforma da Web)
* aqui para desativar a aplicação Plugshare para iOS
* aqui para desativar a aplicação Plugshare para Android

### Processo de verificação

Após receber um pedido de acesso, correção, portabilidade de dados ou eliminação de dados, enviar-lhe-emos um e-mail no prazo de 10 dias úteis para o endereço de e-mail que temos em seu nome. O e-mail irá pedir-lhe que responda para verificar a sua qualidade como Consumidor que faz o pedido. Após a receção da sua verificação, iremos fazer corresponder as suas informações com as que temos no nosso ficheiro. Após a verificação da sua identidade, prosseguiremos para processar o seu pedido e responder no prazo de 45 dias de calendário, a menos que (a) não possamos verificar o seu pedido, (b) se não conseguirmos fazer corresponder-lhe informações na nossa base de dados, ou (c) se existir uma exceção ao abrigo da lei que nos isente do cumprimento do seu pedido. Se precisarmos de mais tempo (até um período adicional de quarenta e cinco (45) dias de calendário), informá-lo-emos do motivo e do período de extensão por escrito.

Se não pudermos atender ao seu pedido, a resposta que fornecermos explicará os motivos para tal. Para pedidos de portabilidade de dados, selecionaremos um formato para fornecer as suas Informações Pessoais que seja prontamente utilizável e que lhe permita transmitir as informações de uma entidade para outra entidade sem obstáculos.

Não cobramos uma taxa para processar ou responder ao seu pedido verificável do Consumidor, a menos que seja excessivo, repetitivo ou manifestamente infundado. Se determinarmos que o pedido justifica uma taxa, informá-lo-emos do motivo pelo qual tomámos essa decisão e fornecer-lhe-emos uma estimativa de custos antes de concluir o seu pedido.

* * *

AVISOS DE PRIVACIDADE PARA DETERMINADOS PAÍSES FORA DOS EUA
===========================================================

INFORMAÇÕES GERAIS
------------------

1. ### O SEU CONSENTIMENTO ESPECÍFICO PARA O TRATAMENTO DE CATEGORIAS “SENSÍVEIS” OU “ESPECIAIS” DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS

Ao abrigo das leis de privacidade de alguns países, determinados tipos de Informação Pessoal são considerados categorias de informação “sensíveis” ou “especiais”. Raramente tratamos categorias de dados sensíveis ou especiais, a menos que seja no seu interesse vital ou no de outra pessoa que o fazemos. Para todas as outras circunstâncias, consente especificamente na nossa recolha, tratamento e retenção de categorias sensíveis ou especiais de Informações Pessoais, conforme descrito na Secção 1.2 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal e, de outra forma, consente no tratamento de Informações Pessoais de acordo com o presente Aviso de Privacidade.  

2. ### OS NOSSOS FUNDAMENTOS JURÍDICOS PARA O TRATAMENTO DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS

As nossas bases legais para a recolha e utilização das Informações Pessoais descritas acima dependerão das Informações Pessoais em questão e do contexto específico no qual as recolhemos. De um modo geral, iremos recolher e tratar as suas Informações Pessoais apenas quando precisarmos das Informações Pessoais para lhe prestar Serviços, para os quais nos contratou, ou quando o tratamento for do nosso interesse legítimo e não for anulado pelos seus interesses de proteção de dados ou direitos e liberdades fundamentais, basear-nos-emos no seu consentimento quando formos legalmente obrigados a fazê-lo. Em alguns casos, também podemos ter uma obrigação legal de recolher Informações Pessoais suas ou podemos precisar das Informações Pessoais para proteger os seus interesses vitais ou os de outra pessoa.

BASE DE INTERESSE LEGÍTIMO PARA A RECOLHA DE INFORMAÇÕES PESSOAIS: A recolha e tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais pode ser necessária para os fins dos nossos interesses legítimos. Tais fins de interesse legítimo podem incluir:

* prevenção de fraude
* garantir a segurança da rede e da informação
* indicar possíveis atos criminosos ou ameaças à segurança pública, incluindo melhorar a proteção da nossa comunidade contra spam, assédio, violação de propriedade intelectual, crime e riscos de segurança de todos os tipos, e aplicar ações judiciais, incluindo investigação de potenciais violações dos nossos Termos de Utilização
* quando estamos a cumprir obrigações legais
* tratar dados de funcionários ou visitantes, membros, participantes ou inscritos
* desempenhar a função ou serviço que nos solicitou
* prestar-lhe os nossos Serviços e a sua funcionalidade quando tal tratamento for necessário para os fins dos interesses legítimos perseguidos por nós ou pelos nossos prestadores de serviços relacionados com os Serviços
* marketing direto
* a relação relevante e adequada que temos consigo
* análise, por exemplo, avaliar o número de visitantes, visualizações de páginas, utilização dos Websites, etc., para compreender como os nossos Websites, Produtos e Serviços estão a ser utilizados, para otimizar os Websites e/ou comunicações futuras, e para desenvolver novos serviços e funcionalidades do Website 
* atualizar as suas informações e preferências
* oferecer e melhorar os nossos Websites, Produtos e Serviços
* aplicar ações judiciais, incluindo investigação de potenciais violações dos nossos Termos

Além das informações fornecidas acima, as secções seguintes aplicam-se apenas aos residentes ou cidadãos do país ou região em questão. Para efeitos das secções seguintes, a menos que especificamente mencionado, a definição de “Informações Pessoais”, conforme utilizada acima, terá a definição de informações pessoais, dados pessoais ou termo semelhante, conforme aplicável ao abrigo das leis de privacidade de dados desse país ou região. Em caso de, e na medida de um conflito entre as secções abaixo e as secções acima, prevalecerão as secções abaixo.

RGPD – AVISO DE PRIVACIDADE PARA RESIDENTES DO ESPAÇO ECONÓMICO EUROPEU (EEE), REINO UNIDO E SUÍÇA
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### VISÃO GERAL

As seguintes disposições aplicam-se apenas se residir no EEE, Reino Unido ou Suíça (referido nesta Secção por conveniência como a “Região da UE”).

Para esses residentes, todo o tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais é realizado de acordo com os direitos e regulamentos de privacidade, em particular, (UE) 2016/679 do Parlamento Europeu e do Conselho, de 27 de abril de 2016, conhecido como o Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados ou o Regulamento Geral de Proteção de Dados do Reino Unido para residentes do Reino Unido (coletivamente, “RGPD”), e o nosso tratamento terá lugar de acordo com o RGPD. Para efeitos do RGPD, seremos o “responsável pelo tratamento de dados” das Informações Pessoais (referidas e definidas no RGPD (disponível [aqui](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/)) como “dados pessoais”) que recolhemos, a menos que recolhamos essas informações em nome de um “responsável pelo tratamento de dados”, caso em que seremos um “subcontratante”. Esta Política de Privacidade não se aplica a websites, aplicações ou serviços que não apresentem ou tenham uma ligação para esta Política de Privacidade ou que apresentem ou tenham uma ligação para uma política de privacidade diferente. Apenas para residentes e cidadãos da Região da UE, na medida em que qualquer definição na presente Política de Privacidade entre em conflito com uma definição ao abrigo do RGPD, a definição do RGPD prevalecerá.

Fornecemos proteção adequada para a transferência de Informações Pessoais para países fora da Região da UE através de um ou mais dos seguintes métodos: (a) uma série de acordos interempresas com base em ou incorporando as Cláusulas Contratuais-Tipo, (b) podemos basear-nos nas decisões de adequação da Comissão Europeias obre determinados países, conforme aplicável, (c) podemos obter o seu consentimento para estas transferências de dados da Região da UE para os Estados Unidos e para outros países, (d) podemos adotar regras empresariais vinculativas, ou (e) na medida do aplicável, podemos basear-nos em derrogações, conforme estabelecido no Artigo 49.º do RGPD, para a transferência e continuação da transferência de Informações Pessoais recolhidas de indivíduos na Região da UE para os Estados Unidos e outros países que a Região da UE considere não fornecer proteção de dados adequada. Relativamente ao método (e), podemos transferir Informações Pessoais para um terceiro para executar um contrato consigo, com o seu consentimento explícito ou de uma forma que não supere os seus direitos e liberdades. Se estas Informações Pessoais não forem tratadas e transferidas, não poderemos executar o contrato consigo ou não terá acesso a nenhum ou todos os benefícios e funcionalidades associados à sua transação.

Também podemos precisar de transferir as suas informações para outras empresas do grupo ou prestadores de serviços em países fora da Região da UE. Isto pode acontecer se os nossos servidores ou fornecedores e prestadores de serviços estiverem sediados fora da Região da UE, ou se utilizar os nossos Produtos e/ou Serviços ao visitar países fora destas áreas.

Os nossos fundamentos jurídicos para a recolha das suas Informações Pessoais são discutidos.

2. ### OS SEUS DIREITOS DE DADOS AO ABRIGO DO RGPD.

Se estiver sujeito ao RGPD, os seus direitos incluem o direito de:

* Direito de saber.
* Direito à correção.
* Direito à eliminação.
* Direito de Restrição ou Oposição ao Tratamento. Tem o direito de se opor às suas Informações Pessoais utilizadas das seguintes formas: (a) tratamento baseado em interesses legítimos ou no desempenho de uma tarefa no interesse público/exercício de autoridade oficial (incluindo definição de perfis); (b) marketing direto (incluindo definição de perfis); e, (c) tratamento para fins de investigação científica/histórica e estatísticas. Consulte abaixo para obter mais informações.
* Direito de exclusão. Tem o direito de não estar sujeito a uma decisão baseada unicamente no tratamento automatizado, incluindo a definição de perfis, que produza efeitos legais sobre si ou que o afete significativamente de forma semelhante, exceto as exceções aplicáveis ao abrigo das leis de proteção de dados relevantes.
* Direito de Apresentar uma Reclamação. Se residir no EEE, pode encontrar uma lista das Autoridades Nacionais de Proteção de Dados [aqui](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Se residir no Reino Unido, pode contactar o Gabinete do Comissário de Informação [aqui.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Direito de retirar o consentimento.

AVISOS A RESIDENTES DE DETERMINADOS OUTROS (NÃO EUA) PAÍSES
-----------------------------------------------------------

O seguinte nesta Secção é adicional às informações discutidas na nossa Política de Privacidade principal.

Iremos honrar os seguintes direitos de titular de dados para todos os residentes fora dos EUA:

* Direito a receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade:

* A nossa identidade e informações de contacto,
* A finalidade específica do nosso tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais,
* A forma e duração do nosso tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais,
* Informações sobre a nossa partilha e finalidade de partilhar as suas Informações Pessoais,
* As responsabilidades de quaisquer terceiros que tratem as suas Informações Pessoais, e,
* Informações relativas a quaisquer entidades legais públicas e privadas com as quais partilhámos as suas Informações Pessoais.  

* Direito a saber:

* Decisões tomadas exclusivamente com base no tratamento automatizado de Informações Pessoais.
* Aceder a informações sobre as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos.  

* Direito à correção.
* Direito de Restrição ou Oposição ao Tratamento.
* Direito de retirar o consentimento.

Qualquer tradução da presente Política de Privacidade para outro idioma que não o inglês é fornecida apenas para fins informativos. Em caso de discrepâncias, a única versão legalmente válida e vinculativa será a versão inglesa deste documento.

1. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DA ARGENTINA

As medidas de segurança técnicas e organizacionais implementadas pela PlugShare também apoiariam regras na Lei de Proteção de Dados Pessoais (PDPA) 25.326 da Argentina, como a proibição de qualquer uso secundário de dados pessoais de um titular de dados e a proibição contra a transferência de dados pessoais para países que não ofereçam um nível adequado de proteção. A PlugShare utiliza um acordo de transferência/tratamento de dados para ajudar na conformidade com a Disposição PDPA 60-E/2016, que regula a transferência transfronteiriça de dados pessoais.

Os residentes na Argentina têm (a) o Direito de Conhecer informações sobre a existência e finalidade de tais Informações Pessoais, e (b) o Direito à Correção e o Direito de Restringir ou Opor-se ao Tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais se forem falsas, imprecisas ou discriminatórias.

2. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DA AUSTRÁLIA

Podemos usar e divulgar as suas Informações Pessoais (conforme definido pela lei australiana) a terceiros sediados fora da Austrália, principalmente nos Estados Unidos, conforme descrito na Secção 9 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal. Concorda e reconhece que os destinatários estrangeiros estarão sujeitos à lei de privacidade da sua jurisdição local e não podem estar sujeitos a quaisquer obrigações de privacidade ou a quaisquer princípios semelhantes aos Princípios de Privacidade Australianos. Também estarão sujeitos a uma lei estrangeira que poderia obrigar à divulgação de Informações Pessoais a terceiros, como uma autoridade estrangeira. A menos que nos notifique por escrito em contrário, será considerado que consentiu a divulgação de Informações Pessoais a destinatários estrangeiros por nós. Tem a opção de permanecer anónimo ao lidar connosco, ou de não nos divulgar determinadas Informações Pessoais. No entanto, isto pode significar que podemos ser impedidos de lhe fornecer os nossos Serviços.

Para os residentes da Austrália, as atualizações à presente Política de Privacidade entram em vigor se obtivermos o seu consentimento expresso ou se fornecermos uma opção de exclusão quando forem anunciadas alterações materiais (por exemplo, nos nossos Websites ou por e-mail).

3. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DO BRASIL

Os residentes no Brasil têm o Direito de Conhecer as seguintes informações: se o seu fornecimento das suas Informações Pessoais é um requisito contratual, ou se houver alguma consequência em não fornecer tais dados (a resposta é não para ambos), informações sobre qualquer tomada de decisão automatizada (incluindo definição de perfis) que façamos (consulte a Secção 2.1 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal), tem o direito de retirar o consentimento para o tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais, e, os seus direitos de acesso de titular de dados (ver abaixo).

Os residentes do Brasil também têm o direito de: (a) Direito de Saber, incluindo obter uma cópia de tais informações; (b) Direito de Correção; (c) Direito de Restrição ou Oposição ao Tratamento; (d) Direito de Eliminação; (e) Direito de Receber Informações sobre Práticas de Privacidade sobre as entidades públicas e privadas com as quais as suas Informações Pessoais foram partilhadas; e, (f) Direito de Apresentar uma Reclamação junto da autoridade de supervisão de dados brasileira (a ANPD).

4. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DO CANADÁ (INCLUINDO QUEBEC)

A nossa Política de Privacidade e as nossas práticas gerais foram concebidas para cumprir as leis de privacidade canadianas, incluindo a Lei de Proteção de Informações Pessoais e Documentos Eletrónicos (PIPEDA) e, quando aplicável, a lei de privacidade do setor privado do Quebeque, a Proteção de Informações Pessoais no Setor Privado (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Para quaisquer práticas de tratamento de informações que não estejam razoavelmente ligadas às finalidades para as quais contactou a PlugShare, tem o direito de optar por não participar em tais práticas de tratamento de informações (incluindo marketing, definição de perfis, publicidade comportamental, partilha com terceiros que não sejam prestadores de serviços).  

Os residentes no Canadá têm o direito de recusar a nossa utilização de Informações Pessoais para fins de marketing direto e outro tratamento que não seja razoavelmente necessário para responder ao que nos contratou.

5. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DE HONG KONG

Utilizamos as suas Informações Pessoais para os seguintes fins de marketing direto: (a) para comunicar consigo sobre os nossos produtos e serviços e os das nossas afiliadas; e, (b) para lhe enviar mais avisos, promoções ou outros materiais de marketing relativos aos nossos Websites, Produtos e Serviços e aos das nossas afiliadas. O seu consentimento para esta finalidade ser-nos-á solicitado no momento da sua submissão de Informações Pessoais (por exemplo, na criação da conta, registo no evento, etc.).

6. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DO MÉXICO

Além das informações apresentadas acima, os residentes do México têm o direito de receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade, incluindo (a) se o seu fornecimento das suas Informações Pessoais é um requisito contratual ou se existe qualquer consequência em não fornecer tais dados (a resposta é não para ambos), (b) informação relativa a qualquer tomada de decisão automatizada (incluindo definição de perfis) que façamos (que é discutida na Secção 2.1 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal), (c) durante quanto tempo é realizada (consulte a Secção 7 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal), (d) o direito de retirar o consentimento para o tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais, e, (e) os seus direitos de acesso ao titular dos dados (ver abaixo). Também tem o direito de saber a indicação expressa das Informações Pessoais sensíveis a serem tratadas.

Os residentes do México também têm: (a) Direito a conhecer as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos, incluindo ser informados sobre as entidades públicas e privadas com quem as suas Informações Pessoais foram partilhadas e obter uma cópia dessas informações; (b) Direito à correção; (c) Direito a restringir ou opor-se ao tratamento; e (d) Direito à eliminação.

7. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DE SINGAPURA

Entre outros direitos, se tivermos presença em Singapura, tem o direito de que as suas Informações Pessoais que possuímos sejam transmitidas para outra organização.

As pessoas ou empresas a quem divulgamos e transferimos as suas Informações Pessoais podem estar localizadas fora de Singapura. Garantiremos que os destinatários das Informações Pessoais transferidas possam fornecer às Informações Pessoais transferidas um padrão de proteção comparável aos padrões de proteção estabelecidos pela lei de privacidade de Singapura através da utilização de acordos de transferência de dados escritos (para transferências para terceiros) ou regras empresariais vinculativas (para transferências para as nossas afiliadas e outras entidades relacionadas connosco).

8. ### AVISO AOS RESIDENTES DE TAIWAN

Os residentes de Taiwan têm o direito de receber informações sobre práticas de privacidade.

Os residentes de Taiwan também têm: (a) direito de saber sobre as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos, incluindo ser informados sobre as entidades públicas e privadas com quem as suas Informações Pessoais foram partilhadas e obter uma cópia dessas informações; (b) direito de correção; (c) direito de restringir ou opor-se ao processamento; e (d) direito de eliminação.

Além das informações apresentadas acima, os residentes de Taiwan têm o direito de conhecer determinadas informações sobre as Informações Pessoais que recolhemos, incluindo (a) se o seu fornecimento das suas Informações Pessoais é um requisito contratual ou se existe qualquer consequência em não fornecer tais dados (a resposta é não para ambos), (b) informação relativa a qualquer tomada de decisão automatizada (incluindo definição de perfis) que façamos (que é discutida na Secção 2.1 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal), (c) durante quanto tempo é realizada (consulte a Secção 7 da nossa Política de Privacidade principal), (d) o direito de retirar o consentimento para o tratamento das suas Informações Pessoais, e, (e) os seus direitos de acesso ao titular dos dados (ver abaixo). Também tem o direito de conhecer a indicação expressa das Informações Pessoais sensíveis a serem tratadas (não recolhemos informações “sensíveis”).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) A Lei de Privacidade do Colorado entra em vigor a 1 de julho de 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) A Lei de Privacidade do Consumidor do Utah entra em vigor em 31 de dezembro de 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) A Lei de Privacidade de Dados do Connecticut entra em vigor a 1 de julho de 2023.

POLITICA DE CONFIDENȚIALITATE PLUGSHARE
=======================================

DATA INTRĂRII ÎN VIGOARE: 10 iulie 2023
---------------------------------------

PlugShare, LLC („PlugShare” „noi”, „nouă” sau „al nostru”) are scopul de a crea o comunitate de sprijin pentru utilizatorii de vehicule electrice („EV”) și de a furniza informații de încărcare de top în industrie și o gamă largă de produse și servicii inovatoare care să ne ajute să facem experiența de conducere EV cât mai ușoară și mai satisfăcătoare posibil. Această Politică de confidențialitate stabilește politicile noastre privind colectarea, utilizarea, divulgarea, păstrarea și transferul Informațiilor cu caracter personal (definite mai jos) pe care le colectăm despre dvs. („dvs.” sau „al dvs.”) prin interacțiunile noastre cu dvs. prin intermediul Site-urilor noastre ([www.PlugShare.com](http://www.plugshare.com/); sau [www.pluginsights.com](http://www.pluginsights.com/); denumite în continuare împreună „Site-urile”), serviciile corespunzătoare și aplicațiile noastre mobile (denumite în continuare împreună „Serviciile”), precum și prin interacțiuni cu părțile neafiliate, cum ar fi furnizorii noștri care colaborează cu noi pentru a vă furniza Serviciile noastre.

Vă rugăm să citiți cu atenție această Politică de confidențialitate. Dacă nu doriți să prelucrăm Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, vă rugăm să nu ne furnizați nicio informație; cu toate acestea, este posibil să nu puteți beneficia de anumite caracteristici ale Serviciilor noastre.

Utilizarea de către dvs. a Site-ului și a Serviciilor noastre este în orice moment supusă și Termenilor noștri de utilizare (disponibili la adresa [https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html](https://company.plugshare.com/terms.html) și actualizați periodic („Termenii”)).

Această Politică de confidențialitate nu se aplică niciunui site sau serviciu neafiliat legat de sau de pe Site-urile sau Serviciile noastre, cu excepția celor ale Furnizorilor noștri de servicii, canalelor sau platformelor noastre de socializare care le găzduiesc sau oricărui site sau serviciu recomandat sau menționat de Site-urile sau Serviciile noastre sau de personalul nostru.

Rezidenții din California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah și Connecticut: Vă rugăm să consultați [.](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html)[Notificarea noastră suplimentară privind confidențialitatea pentru Rezidenții anumitor state din S.U.A.](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html) cu privire la informațiile suplimentare despre prelucrarea de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal.

Rezidenții din alte țări: Dacă sunteți un rezident într-o altă țară decât Statele Unite, vă rugăm să consultați pagina Site-ului nostru Notificări suplimentare privind confidențialitatea pentru anumite țări din afara SUA pentru informații suplimentare despre prelucrarea de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal.

Depunem eforturi constante pentru a ne îmbunătăți Serviciile și este posibil să fie necesar să modificăm periodic această Politică de confidențialitate. Politica noastră de confidențialitate actuală va fi disponibilă întotdeauna pe Site-urile noastre. Vă rugăm să observați data intrării în vigoare a acestei Politici de confidențialitate și să vă asigurați că reveniți periodic pentru actualizări.

1\. CE INFORMAȚII CU CARACTER PERSONAL COLECTĂM
===============================================

1.1 CE SUNT INFORMAȚIILE CU CARACTER PERSONAL
---------------------------------------------

Această Politică de confidențialitate acoperă tratamentul nostru al informațiilor dvs. de identificare personală. „Informații cu caracter personal” înseamnă, în general, orice informații necriptate care identifică, se referă la, descriu, pot fi asociate în mod rezonabil cu sau ar putea fi legate în mod rezonabil de o anumită persoană, cum ar fi, dar fără a se limita la, numele, adresa poștală, adresa de e-mail, numărul dvs. de telefon etc.

Informațiile cu caracter personal nu includ Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal care au fost dezidentificate, anonimizate sau agregate în moduri necesare conform legilor aplicabile, astfel încât informațiile să nu mai poată fi utilizate direct sau prin alte mijloace disponibile în mod rezonabil pentru a identifica o persoană (denumite în continuare împreună „Informațiile cu caracter personal dezidentificate”).

1.2 CATEGORIILE DE INFORMAȚII CU CARACTER PERSONAL PE CARE LE COLECTĂM ȘI PRELUCRĂM
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Colectăm mai multe categorii de Informații cu caracter personal de la dvs. și despre dvs., astfel cum este rezumat în tabelul următor:

| Categorie | Informații cu caracter personal specifice |
| --- | --- |
| Identificatori | * prenumele și numele de familie<br>* numele de utilizator (care poate include prenumele și numele de familie)<br>* adresa de e-mail<br>* codul poștal<br>* sexul, genul<br>* identificatorul personal unic, de ex., numele sau numărul clientului sau al contului, numărul de telefon, identificatorul dispozitivului mobil |
| Date demografice | * țara de reședință |
| Informații comerciale | * istoricul și tendințele achizițiilor de produse/servicii |
| Activitatea pe Internet sau pe alte rețele electronice; informații despre dispozitiv | * tipul și producătorul dispozitivului și ID-ul/UDID-ul acestuia sau un cod similar specific dispozitivului<br>* sistemul de operare și platforma<br>* rezoluția ecranului<br>* numele furnizorului de servicii de internet sau al operatorului de telefonie mobilă, viteza conexiunii și tipul de conexiune<br>* Informații despre adresa, protocolul și secvența de Internet Protocol (sau IP)<br>* modulele cookie<br>* etichetele pixel<br>* Adresa Media Access Control (MAC) a paginilor pe care le-ați vizitat<br>* identificatorul de publicitate pentru dispozitivul mobil<br>* tipul, limba și versiunea browserului<br>* Navigarea, sesiunea, interacțiunea și istoricul căutărilor pe Site-uri, materialele și paginile vizualizate, ora și data accesului la Site-uri, numărul de octeți transferați, numărul de clicuri per vizită, timpul petrecut pe o pagină, datele privind clicurile și fluxul de clicuri, solicitările efectuate, rezultatele căutării selectate, comentariile făcute<br>* marcajul datei și URL-ul ultimei pagini web vizitate înainte de a vizita Site-urile noastre și URL-ul primei pagini vizitate după părăsirea Site-urilor noastre<br>* tipul de Serviciu solicitat<br>* anteturile protocolului de transfer hipertext, bannere de client și server de aplicații |
| Geolocație | * locația fizică și/sau deplasările |
| Altele | * Datele de încărcare, marca, modelul și anul vehiculului electronic<br>* Informațiile oferite voluntar de dvs. ca parte a unui răspuns de feedback sau a unei alte interogări generale efectuate prin intermediul Site-urilor noastre<br>* Concluziile obținute din oricare dintre informațiile enumerate pentru a crea un profil despre un consumator care reflectă preferințele, caracteristicile, tendințele psihologice, predispozițiile, comportamentul, atitudinile, inteligența, abilitățile sau aptitudinile consumatorului |

1.3 UNDE COLECTĂM INFORMAȚIILE CU CARACTER PERSONAL
---------------------------------------------------

Putem colecta Informații cu caracter personal direct de la dvs. prin intermediul Serviciilor noastre atunci când:

* Furnizați informații cu caracter personal prin completarea de formulare web pe Site-urile noastre sau prin tranzacționarea în magazine (mărci ale societății mamă, filialelor și afiliaților). Acestea includ informațiile furnizate atunci când creați un cont online, când achiziționați Serviciile noastre, când vă abonați la buletinele noastre informative electronice sau la alte comunicări, când solicitați informații de la noi, când trimiteți sau postați materiale (în cazul în care acest lucru este permis) pe forumurile noastre sau când interacționați cu serviciul de asistență sau service pentru clienți, când raportați o problemă legată de Site-urile, aplicațiile mobile sau Serviciile noastre sau când comunicați în alt mod cu noi.
* Contactați-ne. Acestea includ toate înregistrările și copiile corespondenței dvs. cu noi, cum ar fi cu birourile noastre sau serviciul de asistență/service pentru clienți sau expedierea prin poștă a unui cec.
* Vă înregistrați pentru un eveniment sau ne informați cu privire la orice solicitare de acces sau de găzduire.
* Răspundeți la sondajele pe care noi sau Furnizorii noștri de servicii v-ar putea solicita să le completați în scopuri de cercetare.
* Efectuați căutări pe Site-uri.
* Participați la programe de loialitate/recompense.
* Solicitați un loc de muncă.
* Utilizați dispozitive și rețele pentru a accesa Serviciile noastre, cum ar fi sincronizarea EV cu Serviciile noastre.
* Utilizați anumite caracteristici de pe Site-urile și aplicațiile noastre mobile. Deși utilizatorii pot accesa caracteristici limitate fără a-și divulga Informațiile cu caracter personal, cum ar fi navigarea în stațiile publice de încărcare fără un cont, colectăm Informații cu caracter personal atunci când utilizatorii înregistrează un cont. Utilizatorii pot alege să utilizeze doar adresa de e-mail și parola lor pentru a căuta încărcătoare pentru acasă. De asemenea, utilizatorii pot alege să profite de capacitățile îmbunătățite prin postarea, comentarea, publicarea sau partajarea cu comunitatea a unor Informații cu caracter personal suplimentare. În general, Utilizatorii aleg câte informații doresc să afișeze despre ei înșiși și pot renunța în orice moment.

De asemenea, putem colecta Informații cu caracter personal de la părți neafiliate, inclusiv:

* Furnizori de date (de ex., companii care furnizează date demografice și alte informații cu privire la consumatori)
* În aplicațiile mobile (mărcile societății mamă, filialelor și afiliaților)
* Parteneri comuni de marketing
* Companii sau platforme de publicitate online (cum ar fi dacă vă legați sau conectați în mod voluntar profilul de pe rețelele de socializare la Serviciile noastre)
* Furnizori de servicii de îndeplinire și livrare
* Companii de socializare
* Alți Furnizori de servicii
* Răspunsul la oportunitățile de angajare
* Acțiuni ale utilizatorilor pe site/formularul web sau aplicații
* Furnizori de investigare sau de verificare a antecedentelor pentru scopuri de angajare
* Permiteți, prin intermediul setărilor dispozitivului dvs. sau al serviciilor terțe, să primim date privind geolocația pentru a afișa informații locale (de exemplu, o stație de încărcare locală) pe aplicațiile noastre mobile.

1.4 INFORMAȚIILE COLECTATE PRIN TEHNOLOGIILE AUTOMATE
-----------------------------------------------------

Pe măsură ce navigați pe și interacționați cu Serviciile noastre, putem utiliza, de asemenea, tehnologii automate de colectare a datelor pentru a colecta anumite informații de pe dispozitivul, browserul dvs. sau alte activități din rețea, conform descrierii din Politica noastră privind modulele cookie, disponibilă la [https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html).

Informațiile despre vizita pe Site și despre dispozitiv. Colectăm detalii despre vizitele dvs. pe Site-urile noastre și despre utilizarea Aplicațiilor noastre mobile, inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, date privind traficul, date privind geolocația, jurnale și alte date de comunicare și resursele pe care le accesați și utilizați pe Site-uri. Colectăm informații despre computerul, dispozitivul mobil și conexiunea dvs. la internet, inclusiv adresa IP, sistemul de operare, tipul de browser, tiparele dvs. privind fluxul de clicuri (adică, pe ce faceți clic pe un site), adresa URL a celui mai recent site pe care l-ați vizitat înainte de a accesa Site-urile noastre, timpul petrecut pe Site-urile noastre și paginile pe care le-ați vizualizat în timp ce navigați pe Site-urile noastre. Este posibil să obținem o estimare aproximativă a locației dvs. pe baza adresei dvs. IP atunci când vizitați Site-urile noastre. Pentru utilizatorii Aplicațiilor noastre mobile, putem colecta și păstra un istoric al informațiilor dvs. exacte despre locație folosind tehnologiile Wi-Fi și/sau Bluetooth, precum și identificatorii dispozitivului dvs. și coordonatele GPS (de ex., latitudine/longitudine). Dacă doriți să împiedicați colectarea informațiilor despre locația dvs., vă rugăm să ajustați setările dispozitivului dvs. mobil pentru a limita accesul Aplicației mobile la informațiile despre locația dvs.

Când utilizați site-ul nostru web, împărtășim informațiile pe care le colectăm de la dvs., cum ar fi e-mailul dvs. (în formă hashing), adresa IP sau informații despre browser sau sistemul dvs. de operare, cu partenerii noștri de identitate/furnizorii de servicii. Acești parteneri returnează un cod de identificare online pe care îl putem stoca în cookie-ul nostru primar pentru a-l folosi în publicitate online, în aplicație și pe mai multe canale și poate fi împărtășit cu companiile de publicitate pentru a permite publicitate orientată și bazată pe interese. Pentru a renunța la această utilizare, faceți clic aici ([https://liveramp.com/opt\_out/](https://liveramp.com/opt_out/)).

Urmărirea comportamentului. De asemenea, putem utiliza aceste tehnologii pentru a colecta informații despre activitățile dvs. online în timp și pe site-uri terțe sau alte servicii online sau pentru a asocia Informațiile cu caracter personal cu alte informații colectate în acest mod.

Location Analytics: Aplicațiile noastre mobile și Site-urile noastre cu browser mobil includ funcții (de ex., pentru trimiterea unei analize privind șoferul în legătură cu o unitate de încărcare) care ne permit să identificăm locația unui șofer și locația unității de încărcare la care se află în prezent un utilizator. Colectăm informații precum adresa IP, ID-ul dispozitivului și locația geografică. Utilizatorii Aplicațiilor mobile pot alege să utilizeze Aplicațiile mobile în mod anonim sau să se conecteze ca utilizator identificat, caz în care pot fi utilizate datele cu caracter personal furnizate la înregistrare.

Pentru utilizatorii Aplicațiilor mobile, putem solicita permisiunea de a accesa anumite informații de pe dispozitivul dvs. mobil, inclusiv lista dvs. de contacte, fotografii și videoclipuri, microfon și cameră. Este opțional să ne furnizați accesul la aceste informații. Cu toate acestea, este posibil ca anumite caracteristici ale Aplicațiilor mobile să nu funcționeze optim dacă decideți să nu ne acordați permisiunea.

Semnalizatoare web. Paginile Site-urilor noastre și e-mailurile noastre pot conține mici fișiere electronice cunoscute sub numele de semnalizatoare web (denumite și gif-uri clare, etichete pixel și gif-uri cu un singur pixel) care ne permit, de exemplu, să numărăm utilizatorii care au vizitat paginile respective sau au deschis un e-mail și pentru alte statistici legate de site (de exemplu, înregistrarea popularității anumitor conținuturi ale site-ului și verificarea integrității sistemului și serverului).

Pixelii de urmărire. Pe lângă utilizarea modulelor cookie, Site-urile pot utiliza „pixeli de urmărire”. Pixelii de urmărire implică utilizarea de etichete pixel care nu sunt vizibile pentru utilizator și constau din câteva linii de cod de computer. Prin pixelii de urmărire se măsoară eficiența reclamelor și se compilează statistici agregate și specifice de utilizare. Putem accesa aceste etichete pixel pentru a identifica activitatea și interesele care ne pot permit să potrivim mai bine Produsele, Serviciile și ofertele noastre cu interesele și nevoile dvs. De exemplu, dacă vizitați Site-urile noastre dintr-o reclamă de pe un alt site, eticheta pixel va permite agenției de publicitate să urmărească faptul că publicitatea sa v-a adus pe Site-uri. Dacă vizitați Site-urile noastre și vă conectăm la un alt site, este posibil, de asemenea, să putem stabili că ați fost trimis către și/sau ați tranzacționat cu un site terț.

GIF. Putem utiliza imagini minuscule cunoscute sub denumirea de GIF-uri transparente pentru a urmări comportamentul utilizatorilor, inclusiv statistici despre cine deschide e-mailurile noastre.

Adresa IP. Serverele noastre (sau cele ale furnizorilor noștri de servicii) înregistrează automat anumite informații din fișierele jurnal raportate din browserul dvs. atunci când accesați Site-urile. Aceste jurnale de server pot include informații precum paginile de pe Site-urile pe care le-ați vizitat, adresa protocolului dvs. de internet („IP”), tipul de browser și alte informații despre modul în care interacționați cu Site-urile. În general, aceste fișiere jurnal sunt șterse periodic.

Valori și analize terțe. Valorile și analizele terțe, pe anumite pagini sau caracteristici ale Serviciilor, pentru a ne ajuta să înțelegem și să analizăm traficul de vizitatori, măsoară eficacitatea promoțională și eficiența caracteristicilor, ofertelor și campaniilor noastre de marketing. De asemenea, utilizăm aceste instrumente pentru a identifica capcanele, deficiențele și domeniile operațiunilor noastre care au nevoie de îmbunătățire și pentru a vizualiza performanța generală și poziția noastră în ceea ce privește prezența online. Aceste instrumente pot stoca module cookie pe dispozitivul dvs. la discreția lor.

NOTIFICAREA ȘI POLITICA PRIVIND MODULELE COOKIE

Tehnologiile pe care le utilizăm pentru colectarea automată a datelor includ, de asemenea, module cookie, conform descrierii de mai jos.

Modulele cookie pentru browser

Modulele cookie pentru browser sunt fișiere mici plasate pe hard disk-ul computerului sau al dispozitivului dvs. mobil. Acestea pot conține anumite date, inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, numele serverului care le-a plasat acolo, un identificator sub forma unui număr unic și o dată de expirare (numai pentru anumite module cookie). Modulele cookie pentru browser sunt gestionate de browserul web (Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome etc.) pe computerul sau dispozitivul dvs. mobil. Pe Site-urile noastre sunt utilizate diferite tipuri de module cookie care au scopuri diferite.

Modulele cookie esențiale

Modulele cookie esențiale sunt esențiale pentru a vă permite să navigați pe Site-urile noastre și să utilizați funcțiile acestora. Fără acestea, serviciile precum coșurile de cumpărături și facturarea electronică nu ar putea funcționa.

Modulele cookie de performanță

Modulele cookie de performanță colectează informații despre utilizarea Site-urilor noastre, cum ar fi paginile care sunt consultate cel mai des. Aceste informații ne permit să ne optimizăm Site-urile și să simplificăm navigarea. Modulele cookie de performanță permit, de asemenea, afiliaților și partenerilor noștri să afle dacă ați accesat una dintre paginile Site-ului nostru de pe site-ul lor și dacă vizita dvs. a dus la utilizarea sau achiziționarea unui Produs sau Serviciu de pe Site-urile noastre, inclusiv referințele pentru Produsul sau Serviciul achiziționat. Toate informațiile colectate de modulele cookie de performanță sunt agregate și, prin urmare, anonime.

Modulele cookie funcționale

Modulele cookie funcționale permit Site-urilor noastre să rețină alegerile pe care le-ați făcut în timpul navigării. De exemplu, putem stoca locația dvs. geografică într-un modul cookie, astfel încât să fie afișate Site-urile corespunzătoare zonei dvs. De asemenea, putem reține preferințele dvs., cum ar fi dimensiunea textului, fontul și alte aspecte personalizabile ale Site-urilor. De asemenea, modulele cookie funcționale pot ține evidența produselor sau videoclipurilor consultate pentru a evita repetarea acestora. Informațiile colectate de aceste module cookie nu pot fi utilizate pentru a vă identifica și nu pot monitoriza activitatea dvs. de navigare pe site-uri care nu ne aparțin. Modulele cookie funcționale ne permit să afișăm reclame adaptate dvs. pe Site-urile noastre, pentru a înțelege care părți ale conținutului nostru vă interesează cel mai mult și ce categorii de Produse sau Servicii solicitați. Unii dintre furnizorii noștri de servicii au permisiunea de a plasa module cookie pe Site-urile noastre. De asemenea, aceste companii vă pot oferi opțiunea de a împiedica utilizarea modulelor cookie în viitor.

În orice moment, puteți împiedica sau renunța la utilizarea viitoare a anumitor module cookie prin activarea setării corespunzătoare din browserul dvs. pentru a refuza acceptarea modulelor cookie din browser. Cu toate acestea, dacă faceți acest lucru, este posibil ca experiența dvs. pe Site-urile noastre să fie afectată; de exemplu, este posibil să nu puteți accesa anumite părți ale Site-urilor. Cu excepția cazului în care ați ajustat setarea browserului dvs. astfel încât să refuze modulele cookie, sistemul nostru va emite module cookie atunci când vă direcționați browserul către Site-urile noastre.

Modulele cookie de stocare locală

Anumite caracteristici ale Site-urilor noastre pot utiliza obiecte stocate local (pentru a colecta și a stoca informații despre preferințele dvs. și navigarea către, de la și pe Site-urile noastre. Modulele cookie de stocare locală nu sunt gestionate de aceleași setări ale browserului ca cele utilizate pentru modulele cookie pentru browser.

De asemenea, putem combina Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm de la dvs. în afara Site-urilor sau Serviciilor noastre cu Informațiile cu caracter personal colectate prin intermediul Site-urilor sau al Serviciilor noastre sau prin alte mijloace, conform descrierii de mai sus.

1.5 INFORMAȚII DESPRE DISPOZITIV, REȚEA, LOCAȚIE GEOGRAFICĂ ȘI EV
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Atunci când vizitați sau părăsiți Site-urile sau Serviciile noastre făcând clic pe un hyperlink sau vizualizați un plugin pe un site terț, primim automat URL-ul site-ului de la care ați venit sau al celui către care sunteți direcționat. De asemenea, agențiile de publicitate primesc URL-ul paginii pe care vă aflați atunci când faceți clic pe orice reclamă care poate apărea în Serviciile noastre. De asemenea, primim adresa protocolului de internet („IP”) a computerului dvs. sau a serverului proxy pe care îl utilizați pentru a accesa internetul, detaliile sistemului de operare al computerului dvs., tipul dvs. de browser web, dispozitivul dvs. mobil (inclusiv identificatorul dispozitivului dvs. mobil furnizat de sistemul dvs. de operare al dispozitivului dvs. mobil), sistemul dvs. mobil de operare (dacă accesați site-urile sau serviciile noastre folosind un dispozitiv mobil) și numele ISP sau al operatorului dvs. mobil.

1.6 SONDAJE
-----------

Noi sau părțile neafiliate putem efectua sondaje pentru utilizatori cu privire la Serviciile noastre. Unele părți neafiliate vă pot direcționa reclame sau promoții pe baza răspunsurilor dvs. la sondaj. Noi sau părțile neafiliate dezvoltăm noi programe sau produse pe baza informațiilor pe care le partajați în sondaje. Putem folosi părți neafiliate pentru a vă oferi stimulente financiare sau de altă natură pentru a participa la sondaje. Dacă furnizarea stimulentelor necesită informațiile dvs. de contact, este posibil să vi se solicite să furnizați Informații cu caracter personal părții neafiliate care îndeplinește oferta de stimulente, care va fi utilizată numai în scopul furnizării stimulentelor promise și al verificării informațiilor dvs. de contact. Depinde de dvs. dacă furnizați aceste informații sau dacă doriți să profitați de o ofertă de stimulente. Consimțământul dvs. pentru utilizarea oricăror Informații cu caracter personal în scopurile stabilite în sondaj va fi solicitat în mod explicit de partea neafiliată care îl efectuează. Pentru a renunța la sondajele noastre, ne puteți trimite solicitarea dvs. utilizând informațiile de contact de mai jos.

2\. NATURA ȘI SCOPUL PRELUCRĂRII INFORMAȚIILOR CU CARACTER PERSONAL
===================================================================

Utilizăm informațiile pe care le colectăm despre dvs. sau pe care ni le furnizați, inclusiv orice Informații cu caracter personal, pentru unul sau mai multe dintre următoarele scopuri:

* Pentru a vă prezenta Site-urile și aplicațiile noastre mobile și conținutul acestora.
* Pentru a vă furniza informații și a răspunde la întrebările dvs. privind Produsele sau Serviciile pe care le solicitați de la noi și informații despre produse și servicii noi, reduceri, promoții speciale sau evenimente viitoare și caracteristici sau oferte care credem că vă vor interesa sau cu privire la o promoție, un concurs sau o tombolă la care ați participat
* Pentru a procesa informațiile contului și plățile tranzacțiilor, inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, taxele pentru Produse și/sau Servicii și plățile și rambursările pentru orice Produse sau Servicii achiziționate (deși nu primim numărul complet al cardului dvs. de credit sau de debit).
* Pentru a procesa reduceri, oferte, recompense de loialitate și/sau solicitări de reduceri, formulare și aplicații și pentru a coordona cu producătorul, comerciantul cu amănuntul și/sau angrosistul.
* Pentru a vă trimite notificări despre contul dvs., inclusiv notificări de expirare și reînnoire.
* Pentru a vă notifica cu privire la informații referitoare la Site-urile noastre sau la modificările acestora, politicile noastre, termenii noștri sau orice Produse ori Servicii pe care le oferim sau le furnizăm ori cu privire la contul dvs.
* Pentru a prelucra Date cu caracter personal sau alte date pe care ni le transmiteți prin intermediul nostru.
* Pentru a vă permite să participați la funcțiile interactive de pe Site-urile noastre.
* Pentru a îmbunătăți Produsele și Serviciile noastre și pentru a dezvolta unele noi, de exemplu, prin analizarea tendințelor utilizatorilor și măsurarea datelor demografice și a intereselor.
* Pentru funcționarea, administrarea, întreținerea Site-ului, Serviciilor și sistemului intern, audituri și analize interne, diagnosticarea problemelor tehnice și menținerea securității.
* Pentru a investiga orice încălcare a Termenilor noștri de utilizare sau a acestei Politici de confidențialitate.
* Pentru a urmări potențialele probleme și tendințe privind utilizarea de către Utilizatori a Site-urilor și Serviciilor noastre și pentru a personaliza asistența noastră pentru a vă oferi servicii mai bune.
* Pentru a pune la dispoziție Furnizorilor noștri de servicii statistici cu privire la nivelurile de utilizare a Site-urilor și alte informații conexe.
* Pentru a vă notifica cu privire la incidentele privind confidențialitatea datelor sau pentru a vă furniza informațiile necesare din punct de vedere legal.
* Pentru a solicita participarea dvs. la evaluări, recenzii, sondaje, grupuri de lucru sau alte inițiative care ne ajută să colectăm informațiile utilizate pentru a dezvolta și a îmbunătăți Produsele și Serviciile noastre.
* Pentru a îndeplini orice alt scop pentru care furnizați Informații cu caracter personal.
* În orice alt mod pe care este posibil să îl descriem și pentru care obținem consimțământul dvs. atunci când furnizați informațiile.

Utilizăm module cookie, GIF-uri clare și informații despre fișierele jurnal pentru: (a) a reține informații, astfel încât să nu fie nevoie să le reintroduceți în timpul vizitei dvs. sau data următoare când vizitați Site-urile; (b) a furniza conținut și informații personalizate; (c) a monitoriza eficacitatea Serviciilor noastre; (d) a monitoriza valorile agregate, cum ar fi numărul total de vizitatori, traficul și tiparele demografice; (e) a diagnostica sau a remedia problemele tehnologice raportate de utilizatorii sau inginerii noștri care sunt asociate cu anumite adrese IP și/sau (f) a vă ajută să vă accesați eficient informațiile după ce vă conectați.

Datele statistice pe care le colectăm ne ajută automat să ne îmbunătățim Site-urile și să furnizăm Produse și Servicii mai bune și mai personalizate, inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, permițându-ne: să estimăm publicul/dimensiunea vizitatorilor și tiparele de utilizare, să stocăm informații despre preferințele dvs., să ne permitem să personalizăm și să îmbunătățim Site-urile, să accelerăm căutările dvs. și/sau să vă recunoaștem atunci când reveniți pe Site-urile noastre.

Putem colecta și utiliza informațiile despre sesiunea dvs. de încărcare EV (de exemplu, timpul de încărcare, consumul de energie, proprietatea stației și datele etc.) și marca, modelul și anul vehiculului dvs. pentru a vă administra contul, cum ar fi pentru a face diferența între mai multe vehicule sau utilizatori care partajează un singur cont și în scopuri analitice.

În măsura în care nu sunteți de acord cu practicile de gestionare a informațiilor prevăzute în prezentul document, puteți avea dreptul de a refuza astfel de practici. Toate solicitările de renunțare trebuie adresate către [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). În măsura în care solicitările de renunțare sunt onorate, acestea vor avea efect asupra prelucrării viitoare și nu asupra prelucrării care a avut loc pe baza consimțământului prealabil.

2.1 LUAREA AUTOMATĂ A DECIZIILOR
--------------------------------

Putem utiliza Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pe care ni le furnizați și pe care le obținem din alte surse pentru a înțelege mai bine interesele dvs., astfel încât să putem încerca să anticipăm ce alte Produse, Servicii și informații v-ar putea interesa. Această practică implică luarea de decizii automate în legătură cu dvs., pe baza acestor informații, pentru a ne permite să ne adaptăm mai bine interacțiunile cu dvs., astfel încât acestea să devină mai relevante și mai interesante. Vă puteți opune în orice moment acestui lucru sau ne puteți solicita mai multe informații despre metodologia aplicată în procesele noastre decizionale automatizate, contactându-ne (a se vedea Secțiunea 12 de mai jos).

2.2 MESAJE TEXT
---------------

Serviciile noastre pot include trimiterea de mesaje către dvs. prin Serviciul de mesaje scurte („SMS”), care pot transmite până la două mesaje pe zi către dispozitivul dvs. wireless (cu excepția cazului în care comunicați mai departe cu noi), însă frecvența mesajelor poate varia.  Atunci când consimțiți în mod expres să primiți mesaje text de la noi și să furnizați un număr de telefon mobil, consimțiți în mod expres să primiți texte informative și tranzacționale recurente de la sau în numele nostru la numărul pe care l-ați furnizat. Prin acordarea în mod expres a consimțământului de a primi mesaje SMS de la noi și furnizarea unui număr de telefon mobil, garantați și declarați că sunteți proprietarul numărului de telefon mobil pe care ni-l furnizați. Putem utiliza informațiile dvs. pentru a vă contacta cu privire la utilizarea, achizițiile, retururile dvs. (dacă sunt disponibile), actualizările Site-urilor, desfășurarea sondajelor sau comunicările informaționale și legate de servicii, inclusiv actualizările importante de securitate. După ce ne trimiteți mesajul SMS „STOP”, vă vom trimite un mesaj SMS pentru a confirma că v-ați dezabonat. Alternativ, ne puteți trimite solicitarea dvs. prin e-mail, inclusiv adresa de e-mail și numărul de telefon pe care le-ați înregistrat la noi sau prin orice mijloace rezonabile. După aceasta, nu veți mai primi mesaje SMS de la noi. Dacă doriți să vă înscrieți din nou, înregistrați-vă așa cum ați făcut prima dată și vom începe să vă trimitem din nou mesaje SMS. Pentru ajutor, vă rugăm să răspundeți la un text cu AJUTOR. Se pot aplica tarife pentru mesaje și date, în funcție de abonamentul dvs. pentru telefonul mobil. Transportatorii nu sunt responsabili pentru mesajele întârziate sau nelivrate.

2.3 PLUGIN-URI PENTRU REȚELELE DE SOCIALIZARE
---------------------------------------------

Integrăm interfețe sau plug-in-uri pentru programe de aplicații pe rețelele de socializare („Plug-in\-uri”) de pe rețelele de socializare, inclusiv Facebook, Google+, LinkedIn, Xing, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr, Pinterest și/sau posibil alte companii, pe Site-urile noastre. Pentru a vă înregistra ca utilizator la noi, este posibil să aveți opțiunea de a vă autentifica folosind contul dvs. de Facebook sau alte site-uri de socializare.

De exemplu, atunci când vizitați Site-urile noastre, plugin-ul creează o conexiune directă între browserul dvs. și serverul Facebook. Acest lucru permite ca Facebook să primească informații despre vizita dvs. pe Site-urile noastre cu adresa dvs. IP. Dacă faceți clic pe butonul „Like” de pe Facebook în timp ce sunteți conectat la contul dvs. de Facebook, puteți conecta conținutul Site-urilor noastre la profilul dvs. de Facebook. Acest lucru permite ca Facebook să aloce vizita dvs. pe Site-urile noastre contului dvs. de utilizator. Vă rugăm să rețineți că, în calitate de furnizor al Site-urilor, nu primim nicio notificare cu privire la conținutul datelor transmise sau la utilizarea acestora de către Facebook. Dacă nu doriți ca Facebook să aloce vizita dvs. pe Site-urile noastre contului dvs. de utilizator Facebook, vă rugăm să vă deconectați din contul dvs. de utilizator Facebook.

Dacă vă conectați printr-un plug-in de pe rețelele de socializare, ne autorizați să accesăm anumite informații despre cont de pe site-ul de socializare respectiv, cum ar fi profilul dvs. public de pe rețelele de socializare (în conformitate cu setările dvs. de confidențialitate de pe site-ul de socializare), adresa dvs. de e-mail, interesele, aprecierile, sexul, ziua de naștere, istoricul educației, relațiile, interesele, orașul actual, fotografiile, descrierea personală, lista de prieteni și informații despre și fotografii ale prietenilor de pe site-ul dvs. de socializare care ar putea fi prieteni de pe site-ul de socializare cu alți utilizatori. Plug-in-urile pot transfera informații despre dvs. pe platforma Plug-in-ului respectiv fără a fi acționate de dvs. Aceste informații pot include numărul dvs. de identificare ca utilizator al platformei, site-ul pe care vă aflați și multe altele. Interacțiunea cu un Plug-in va transmite informații direct către rețeaua de socializare a acelui Plug-in, iar informațiile respective pot fi vizibile de alte persoane de pe platforma respectivă. Plug-inurile sunt controlate de politica de confidențialitate a site-ului respectiv de socializare (disponibilă pe site-ul respectiv) și nu de Politica noastră de confidențialitate.

3\. MODUL ÎN CARE DIVULGĂM INFORMAȚII CU CARACTER PERSONAL PĂRȚILOR NEAFILIATE
==============================================================================

3.1 TIPURI DE PĂRȚI NEAFILIATE
------------------------------

Putem sau divulgăm Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, integral sau parțial, următoarelor tipuri de părți neafiliate și în unul sau mai multe dintre următoarele scopuri:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Tipul de parte neafiliată | Scop |
| Furnizori de stocare sau găzduire a datelor | stocarea și transmiterea în siguranță a datelor dvs. |
| Furnizori de servicii pentru baze de date și software | gestionarea și urmărirea datelor dvs. |
| Consultanți juridici și de conformitate, cum ar fi consilieri externi, auditori externi sau consultanți fiscali | Furnizarea de servicii profesionale pentru noi |
| Furnizori de gestionare a identității | scopuri de autentificare |
| Furnizori de soluții de plată | procesarea în siguranță a plăților pe care ni le furnizați |
| Producători, comercianți cu amănuntul și angrosiști | depunerea, procesarea și gestionarea reducerilor, ofertelor, recompenselor de loialitate și altele asemenea |
| Furnizori de servicii de îndeplinire și expediere | furnizarea și livrarea Produselor, Serviciilor și mărfurilor |
| Furnizori de sondaje și cercetări | efectuarea de studii în numele nostru |
| Parteneri de publicitate, inclusiv furnizori de rețele de socializare | furnizarea de reclame direcționate |

Pentru orice transfer de Informații cu caracter personal care nu este necesar în mod rezonabil pentru a îndeplini scopurile pentru care interacționați cu PlugShare (cum ar fi în scopuri de marketing sau sondaj), aveți dreptul de a renunța la o astfel de prelucrare. Pentru a vă exercita dreptul de renunțare, vă rugăm să ne contactați la [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

3.2 FURNIZORI DE SERVICII, PARTENERI DE AFACERI ȘI SUBCONTRACTANȚI
------------------------------------------------------------------

 Putem partaja Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal cu Furnizorii de servicii care prestează servicii în numele nostru, după cum s-a discutat mai sus. Acești Furnizori de servicii pot avea acces la Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pentru a ne furniza aceste servicii nouă sau în numele nostru. Dacă angajăm Furnizori de servicii pentru oricare dintre cele de mai sus, utilizarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal se va supune obligațiilor de confidențialitate, iar utilizarea de către aceștia a Informațiilor cu caracter personal va fi restricționată la furnizarea serviciilor lor către noi. Putem stoca Informații cu caracter personal în locații care nu se află sub controlul nostru direct (de exemplu, pe servere sau baze de date situate sau co-localizate cu furnizori de servicii de găzduire a datelor).  

3.3 PUBLICITATE COMPORTAMENTALĂ ÎN CONTEXT ÎNCRUCIȘAT
-----------------------------------------------------

Suntem obligați să divulgăm dacă partajăm Informații cu caracter personal cu o terță parte care este implicată în publicitate comportamentală (direcționată) în context încrucișat. În ultimele douăsprezece (12) luni, am divulgat sau este posibil să fi divulgat următoarele categorii de date cu caracter personal într-un context care, în anumite legi (de ex., CPRA, RGPD sau RGPD din Regatul Unit) poate fi considerat o vânzare:

* Identificatori
* Internet sau altă activitate similară în rețea
* Date de geolocalizare

Aveți posibilitatea de a vă dezabona de la această partajare făcând clic pe solicitările de dezabonare care vor apărea în notificarea care vă este comunicată la prima vizită a aplicațiilor noastre mobile sau a Site-urilor noastre.

3.4 TRANSFERURI ALE ACTIVITĂȚII
-------------------------------

Confirmați (și nu vă veți opune) divulgării sau transferului de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal, a Informațiilor cu caracter personal dezidentificate și a altor informații pe care ni le furnizați, precum și a drepturilor pe care le-ați acordat sau confirmat în această Politică de confidențialitate (denumite în continuare împreună „Informațiile transferate”) către un cumpărător sau achizitor potențial sau real al companiei noastre sau alt succesor în scopul analizării sau realizării unei fuziuni, cesiuni, restructurări, reorganizări, dizolvări, modificări a controlului sau transfer al unora din sau al tuturor activelor noastre (fiecare dintre cele de mai sus fiind denumită „Transferul”), fie ca o continuare a activității, fie ca parte a unei proceduri de faliment, lichidare sau a altei proceduri judiciare, în care Informațiile cu caracter personal deținute de noi se numără printre activele transferate, și sunteți de acord să nu vă opuneți unei astfel de divulgări și/sau transfer. Nu putem face nicio declarație cu privire la utilizarea sau transferul Informațiilor transferate pe care le putem deține în caz de faliment, reorganizare, insolvență, administrare judiciară sau cesiune în beneficiul creditorilor. În plus, cu excepția cazurilor impuse de lege, nu suntem și nu vom fi responsabili pentru nicio încălcare a securității de către nicio parte neafiliată sau pentru nicio acțiune a oricărei părți neafiliate care primește oricare dintre Informațiile transferate care ne sunt divulgate.

3.5 DIVULGĂRILE NECESARE; PROTEJAREA DREPTURILOR; SIGURANȚA
-----------------------------------------------------------

Cu excepția cazului în care se descrie altfel în această Politică de confidențialitate, nu vom divulga Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal niciunei părți neafiliate, cu excepția cazului în care acest lucru este impus prin lege, ordin judecătoresc, proces juridic (de ex., citație), inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, pentru a răspunde oricărui guvern, autoritate de reglementare sau cerere de licențiere, sau în cazul în care considerăm că o astfel de acțiune este necesară pentru: (a) a respecta legea, a respecta procesul juridic aplicat nouă sau afiliaților, filialelor, furnizorilor contractați sau parteneri lor noștri de afinitate, sau a investiga, preveni sau a lua măsuri cu privire la activități ilegale suspectate sau efective; (b) a pune în aplicare Termenii noștri sau contractul cu clienții (inclusiv în scopuri de facturare și colectare); (c) a lua măsuri de precauție împotriva răspunderii; (d) a investiga și a ne apăra împotriva oricăror pretenții sau acuzații ale terților; (e) a asista agențiile guvernamentale de aplicare a legii sau a îndeplini cerințele naționale sau alte cerințe de securitate guvernamentale; (f) a proteja securitatea sau integritatea Site-urilor noastre, integritatea noastră, integritatea Serviciilor și aplicațiilor noastre mobile sau, (g) a exercita sau a proteja drepturile, proprietatea sau siguranța personală a noastră, a utilizatorilor noștri sau a altor persoane. 

Vom încerca să vă notificăm, acolo unde este posibil, cu privire la aceste solicitări, cu excepția cazului în care: (i) furnizarea notificării este interzisă prin procesul legal în sine, prin ordinul judecătoresc pe care îl primim sau prin legislația aplicabilă sau (ii) considerăm că furnizarea notificării ar fi inutilă, ineficientă, ar crea un risc de vătămare corporală sau alte vătămări corporale ale unei persoane sau ale unui grup sau ar crea sau crește riscul de fraudă asupra noastră, a utilizatorilor noștri, a Site-urilor, Serviciilor sau aplicațiilor noastre mobile. În cazurile în care ne conformăm solicitărilor legale fără notificare din aceste motive, vom încerca să notificăm utilizatorul respectiv cu privire la solicitare după ce stabilim cu bună-credință că nu ne mai este interzis prin lege să facem acest lucru și că nu se aplică niciun scenariu de risc descris la acest alineat.

3.6 DIVULGAREA INFORMAȚIILOR CU CARACTER PERSONAL DEZIDENTIFICATE
-----------------------------------------------------------------

Putem partaja Informații cu caracter personal dezidentificate (inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, date de utilizare anonime, pagini și URL-uri de referință/ieșire, adresa IP, tipuri de platforme, numărul de clicuri etc.) cu părți neafiliate în orice mod și în orice scop, cum ar fi pentru administrarea sistemului și pentru monitorizarea utilizării Site-urilor; pentru măsurarea numărului de vizite pe Site-urile noastre, a timpului mediu petrecut, a numărului de pagini vizualizate și pentru monitorizarea diverselor alte statistici ale Site-urilor pentru a îmbunătăți conținutul.

4\.  SOLICITĂRILE DE „DO NOT TRACK”
===================================

Unele browsere web (inclusiv Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox și Chrome) includ o caracteristică „Do Not Track” („DNT”) sau o caracteristică similară care semnalează site-urilor că un utilizator nu dorește să îi fie urmărite activitatea și comportamentul online. Dacă un site care răspunde la un anumit semnal DNT recepționează semnalul DNT, browserul poate bloca acel site de la colectarea anumitor informații despre utilizatorul browserului. Nu toate browserele oferă o opțiune DNT, iar semnalele DNT nu sunt încă uniforme. Din acest motiv, mulți operatori de site-uri, inclusiv PlugShare, nu răspund la semnalele DNT.

5\. COMUNICĂRI, PREFERINȚE ȘI RENUNȚARE PLUGSHARE
=================================================

Prin furnizarea adresei dvs. de e-mail, sunteți de acord ca noi să utilizăm adresa de e-mail pentru a vă trimite notificări legate de servicii prin e-mail, inclusiv, dar fără a se limita la, orice notificări impuse de lege (de exemplu, notificări privind confidențialitatea datelor sau incidente de securitate), în locul comunicării prin poștă. De asemenea, sunteți de acord că vă putem trimite notificări privind activitatea cu privire la Produsele, Serviciile, Site-urile, aplicațiile noastre mobile, Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal sau orice aspect al relației noastre, la adresa de e-mail pe care ne-o furnizați, în conformitate cu orice setări de confidențialitate aplicabile. Putem utiliza adresa dvs. de e-mail pentru a vă trimite alte mesaje sau conținut, cum ar fi, dar fără a se limita la, buletine informative, completări sau modificări ale caracteristicilor Serviciului sau oferte speciale. Dacă nu doriți să primiți astfel de mesaje de e-mail, puteți renunța făcând clic pe Dezabonare, dacă este disponibil. Renunțarea vă poate împiedica să primiți mesaje e-mail cu privire la actualizări, îmbunătățiri, caracteristici speciale, anunțuri sau oferte. Nu aveți dreptul să renunțați la e-mailurile legate de Serviciu. Dacă ați ales să nu ne furnizați un e-mail sau o altă adresă, este posibil să nu primiți e-mailurile noastre legate de Serviciu.

Prin intermediul paginii de setări a contului dvs. de utilizator, puteți accesa și, în unele cazuri, puteți edita sau șterge anumite informații pe care ni le-ați furnizat, cum ar fi numele și parola, adresa de e-mail, adresa, informațiile profilului de utilizator etc. Informațiile pe care le puteți vizualiza, actualiza și șterge se pot modifica pe măsură ce Produsele, Site-urile, Serviciile sau practicile noastre se modifică. Dacă aveți întrebări despre vizualizarea sau actualizarea informațiilor pe care le avem la dosar despre dvs., vă rugăm să ne contactați. Cu toate acestea, atunci când actualizați informațiile, putem păstra o copie a informațiilor nerevizuite în evidențele noastre. Puteți solicita ștergerea contului dvs. trimițându-ne un e-mail. Este responsabilitatea dvs. să păstrați adresa de e-mail actuală la noi. În funcție de statul sau țara în care locuiți, puteți avea drepturi suplimentare. Vă rugăm să consultați mai jos mai multe informații.

6\. DEZVOLTATORII CARE UTILIZEAZĂ SERVICIILE PLATFORMEI PLUGSHARE
=================================================================

Colaborăm cu terții și le permitem acestora să utilizeze platforma de dezvoltare PlugShare pentru a oferi servicii și funcționalități împreună cu PlugShare. Acești dezvoltatori terți fie au negociat un acord de utilizare a platformei PlugShare, fie au fost de acord cu interfețele noastre de programare aplicații cu autoservire („API”) și termenii plug-in-ului pentru a construi aplicații pentru platforma software („Aplicații platformă”). Atât contractele negociate, cât și API-ul nostru și termenii de utilizare a plug-in-ului conțin restricții privind modul în care terții pot accesa, stoca și utiliza Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le furnizați către PlugShare. Dacă alegeți să utilizați o Aplicație pentru platformă, vi se va solicita să confirmați acceptarea politicii de confidențialitate și acordul utilizatorului al dezvoltatorului terț. Pentru a revoca permisiunea acordată unei Aplicații pentru platformă, vă rugăm să vizitați setările dvs. Rețineți, totuși, că, chiar dacă revocați permisiunea acordată unei Aplicații pentru platformă, este posibil ca conexiunile dvs. să utilizeze în continuare Aplicația pentru platformă, astfel încât Aplicația pentru platformă să poată avea în continuare acces la anumite informații despre dvs., la fel ca și conexiunile dvs.

7\. PĂSTRAREA INFORMAȚIILOR CU CARACTER PERSONAL
================================================

Perioada de timp pentru care păstrăm Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal depinde de scopurile pentru care le utilizăm. Vom păstra Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal atât timp cât contul dvs. este activ, sau atâta timp cât sunteți titular de cont înregistrat sau utilizator al Serviciilor noastre sau atât timp cât avem un alt scop de afaceri în acest sens (cum ar fi, dar fără a se limita la, pentru afaceri, impozit, sau în scopuri legale) și ulterior, nu mai mult decât este impus sau permis de lege, sau politica noastră de păstrare a înregistrărilor, necesare în mod rezonabil în scopuri de raportare și reconciliere internă, sau pentru a vă oferi feedback sau informații pe care le-ați putea solicita. Această perioadă de păstrare este supusă evaluării și modificării de către noi. Putem păstra Informațiile cu caracter personal dezidentificate atât timp cât considerăm că este adecvat.

În urma închiderii sau dezactivării contului dvs. de utilizator, putem păstra informațiile dvs. de profil și toate informațiile postate în zonele publice ale Site-urilor. În urma închiderii sau dezactivării contului dvs. de utilizator, putem păstra Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și alte date, dar le vom păstra în condiții de confidențialitate, în conformitate cu Termenii, această Politică de confidențialitate și după cum impune legislația aplicabilă. Avem dreptul de a șterge toate Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și alte date după închiderea contului dvs. de utilizator, fără a vă notifica.

8\. NICIO COLECTARE INTENȚIONATĂ A DATELOR COPIILOR
===================================================

Nu colectăm, nu solicităm sau nu păstrăm cu bună știință Informații cu caracter personal de la nicio persoană cu vârsta sub 18 ani și nu permitem acestor persoane să se înregistreze sau să utilizeze Serviciile noastre. Dacă aveți vârsta sub 18 ani, vă rugăm să nu ne trimiteți nicio Informație cu caracter personal. În cazul în care luăm cunoștință despre faptul că am colectat Informații cu caracter personal de la un copil cu vârsta sub 18 ani fără verificarea consimțământului parental, vom depune eforturi rezonabile din punct de vedere comercial pentru a șterge aceste informații din baza noastră de date.

9\. UNDE SUNT PRELUCRATE ȘI STOCATE INFORMAȚIILE CU CARACTER PERSONAL; LEGISLAȚIA APLICABILĂ
============================================================================================

Avem sediul central în Statele Unite. Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care noi sau Furnizorii noștri de servicii le colectăm pot fi stocate și prelucrate pe servere din interiorul sau din afara Statelor Unite și oriunde noi și Furnizorii noștri de servicii avem sedii în întreaga lume, iar anumite informații pot fi accesibile persoanelor sau companiilor din afara Statelor Unite care ne furnizează servicii. Sunteți de acord ca Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal să fie transmise și/sau transferate de noi și de Furnizorii noștri de servicii către, sau să fie accesate în, jurisdicții care ar putea să nu ofere niveluri de protecție a datelor echivalente cu cele din jurisdicția dvs. de origine. Vom lua măsuri rezonabile pentru a ne asigura că Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal beneficiază de un nivel adecvat de protecție în jurisdicțiile în care le prelucrăm.

Legile SUA se aplică în măsura în care sunteți un rezident al Statelor Unite. În caz contrar, această Politică de confidențialitate și toate celelalte aspecte vor fi interpretate în conformitate cu legile provinciale/statale și federale ale jurisdicției în care locuiți. Jurisdicțiile din afara reședinței dvs. pot avea legi privind confidențialitatea diferite de cele din jurisdicția dvs., inclusiv dreptul autorităților de aplicare a legii și guvernamentale de a accesa Informațiile cu caracter personal.  În măsura în care prelucrăm date în afara țării dvs., efectuăm o evaluare a impactului asupra confidențialității pentru a stabili că Furnizorii noștri de servicii pot oferi în mod substanțial același nivel de protecție ca cel impus în jurisdicția dvs. și că pot încheia contracte pentru a consolida și mai mult obligațiile de a prelucra în mod adecvat Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal.

10\. SECURITATE
===============

Am implementat măsuri de securitate tehnice și organizatorice menite să protejeze Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal împotriva pierderii accidentale și împotriva accesului, utilizării, distrugerii, modificării și divulgării neautorizate. Cu toate acestea, vă rugăm să rețineți că internetul nu este un mediu 100% sigur. Este responsabilitatea dvs. să protejați securitatea informațiilor dvs. de conectare, să fiți precaut atunci când transmiteți orice Informații cu caracter personal prin e-mailuri, mesagerie instantanee și mijloace similare de comunicare și să mențineți bune practici de securitate pe internet. Nu vă vom trimite niciodată un e-mail pentru a vă solicita parola sau alte informații de conectare la cont. Dacă primiți un astfel de e-mail, vă rugăm să ni-l trimiteți pentru a putea investiga.

11\. DREPTURI SUPLIMENTARE ALE PERSOANELOR VIZATE PENTRU REZIDENȚII DIN ANUMITE JURISDICȚII DESCRISE ÎN NOTIFICĂRILE SUPLIMENTARE PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA
============================================================================================================================================================

Mai jos sunt explicate drepturile fiecărei persoane vizate descrise în Notificările suplimentare privind confidențialitatea:

* Dreptul de a primi informații privind practicile de confidențialitate: Aveți dreptul de a primi anumite informații obligatorii din punct de vedere legal la sau înainte de momentul colectării sau ca răspuns la solicitarea dvs.
* Dreptul la ștergere: Puteți solicita să ștergem orice Informații cu caracter personal despre dvs. pe care le-am colectat de la dvs., sub rezerva anumitor excepții.
* Dreptul la corectare: Puteți solicita corectarea oricăror Informații cu caracter personal incorecte pe care le păstrăm despre dvs.
* Dreptul de a cunoaște: Puteți solicita să vă furnizăm informații specifice despre modul în care am gestionat informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, inclusiv să vă furnizăm o copie a informațiilor cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat despre dvs. într-un format portabil.
* Dreptul la nediscriminare: Aveți dreptul de a nu fi discriminat pentru exercitarea drepturilor dvs. de persoană vizată. Aceasta înseamnă să nu refuzați bunuri sau servicii, să nu vă percepeți prețuri sau tarife diferite sau să nu oferiți un nivel diferit de calitate pentru produse sau servicii ca urmare a exercitării de către dvs. a drepturilor dvs. de persoană vizată.
* Drepturi de renunțare: Puteți solicita să renunțați la vânzarea și partajarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal, publicitatea comportamentală sau direcționată în context încrucișat, luarea automată a deciziilor sau crearea de profiluri, în măsura în care astfel de activități sunt definite și restricționate în conformitate cu legile aplicabile.
* Dreptul de a restricționa sau a se opune prelucrării: Ne puteți solicita să suprimăm sau să încetăm prelucrarea unora dintre Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal, dar putem stoca în continuare Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal.  
* Dreptul de a limita utilizarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal sensibile: Puteți solicita limitarea utilizării Informațiilor dvs. sensibile cu caracter personal numai în scopurile autorizate de legile aplicabile.
* Dreptul de a depune o plângere: Aveți dreptul de a depune o plângere la autoritatea locală pentru protecția datelor, în cazul în care considerați că prelucrarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal care vă vizează încalcă drepturile dvs.
* Dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul: În măsura în care prelucrarea de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal se bazează exclusiv pe consimțământul dvs., vă puteți retrage consimțământul în orice moment.

12\. INFORMAȚII DE CONTACT
==========================

PlugShare a desemnat un Responsabil cu protecția datelor ca persoană care va supraveghea respectarea cerințelor de confidențialitate. Responsabilul cu protecția datelor din cadrul PlugShare poate fi contactat la adresa de mai jos cu privire la orice probleme legate de politica de confidențialitate.

Dacă aveți întrebări sau comentarii despre această Politică de confidențialitate sau despre practicile noastre de confidențialitate, vă rugăm să ne contactați la: PlugShare, LLC, 2231 Campus Drive, El Segundo, California 90245 SUA; În atenția: Responsabilului cu protecția datelor; [\[email protected\]](https://company.plugshare.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

NOTIFICARE DE CONFIDENȚIALITATE PENTRU REZIDENȚII ANUMITOR STATE DIN SUA
========================================================================

Dacă sunteți un rezident din California, Virginia, Colorado, Utah sau Connecticut (denumit ocazional „Consumator”), legile statale vă oferă drepturi suplimentare cu privire la utilizarea de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal.

LEGEA „SHINE THE LIGHT” DIN CALIFORNIA
--------------------------------------

Secțiunea 1798.83 a Codului Civil din California, cunoscută sub denumirea de legea „Shine The Light”, permite utilizatorilor care sunt rezidenți ai statului California să solicite și să obțină de la noi o listă a Informațiilor cu caracter personal (dacă există) pe care le-am divulgat terților în scopuri de marketing direct în anul calendaristic precedent și numele și adresele acestor terți. Solicitările pot fi făcute o singură dată pe an și sunt gratuite.

LEGEA PRIVIND PROTECȚIA CONFIDENȚIALITĂȚII ONLINE DIN CALIFORNIA („CALOPPA”; CALIF. BUS. & PROF. CODE § 22575-22578, DISPONIBILĂ [AICI](http://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?lawCode%3DBPC%26division%3D8.%26title%3D%26part%3D%26chapter%3D22.%26article%3D))
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

CalOPPA se aplică numai companiilor care colectează Informații cu caracter personal ale rezidenților din California.

1. MODUL ÎN CARE RĂSPUNDEM LA SEMNALELE DO NOT TRACK.

Unele browsere web transmit semnale „do not track” (DNT/GPC) către site-urile și alte servicii online cu care comunică browser-ul dvs. web. În prezent nu există niciun standard care să reglementeze ce anume trebuie să facă site-urile, dacă este cazul să ia vreo măsură, atunci când primesc aceste semnale; cu toate acestea, avem în prezent în vigoare măsuri pentru a acționa ca răspuns la aceste semnale.

2. URMĂRIREA COMPORTAMENTULUI TERȚILOR

De asemenea, putem utiliza aceste tehnologii pentru a colecta informații despre activitățile dvs. online în timp și pe site-uri terțe sau alte servicii online sau pentru a asocia Informațiile cu caracter personal cu alte informații colectate în acest mod. Putem utiliza Informațiile cu caracter personal pentru a urmări tiparele de clic și navigare ale utilizatorilor.

LEGEA PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA CONSUMATORILOR DIN CALIFORNIA DIN 2018 („CCPA”, DISPONIBILĂ [AICI](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/codes_displayText.xhtml?division%3D3.%26part%3D4.%26lawCode%3DCIV%26title%3D1.81.5.)) ȘI SUCCESOAREA ACESTEIA, LEGEA PRIVIND DREPTURILE DE CONFIDENȚIALITATE DIN CALIFORNIA DIN 2020 („CPRA”, DISPONIBILĂ [AICI](https://oag.ca.gov/system/files/initiatives/pdfs/19-0021A1%2520%2528Consumer%2520Privacy%2520-%2520Version%25203%2529_1.pdf)). 
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* * *

Tabelul de mai jos detaliază modul în care divulgăm Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat despre dvs.:

| Categorie | Categorii de terțe părți neafiliate cărora le divulgăm Informații cu caracter personal | Categorii de părți terțe neafiliate cărora le vindem sau partajăm Informații cu caracter personal |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identificatori | Furnizori de stocare sau găzduire a datelor<br><br>Furnizori de gestionare a identității<br><br>Furnizori de soluții de plată<br><br>Furnizori de sondaje și cercetări<br><br>Parteneri de publicitate, inclusiv furnizori de rețele de socializare | n/a |
| Date demografice | Furnizori de sondaje și cercetări | n/a |
| Informații comerciale | n/a | n/a |
| Informații despre activitatea pe Internet sau altă rețea electronică; informații despre dispozitiv | Furnizori de stocare sau găzduire a datelor<br><br>Furnizori de servicii pentru baze de date și software<br><br>Furnizori de gestionare a identității<br><br>Parteneri de publicitate, inclusiv furnizori de rețele de socializare | n/a |
| Geolocație | Furnizori de stocare sau găzduire a datelor<br><br>Furnizori de servicii pentru baze de date și software<br><br>Parteneri de publicitate, inclusiv furnizori de rețele de socializare | n/a |
| Altele | Furnizori de stocare sau găzduire a datelor<br><br>Furnizori de servicii pentru baze de date și software<br><br>Furnizori de sondaje și cercetări<br><br>Parteneri de publicitate, inclusiv furnizori de rețele de socializare | Producători, comercianți cu amănuntul și angrosiști |

Ne puteți contacta pentru a vă exercita următoarele drepturi în temeiul CCPA și CPRA (vă rugăm să consultați secțiunea 11 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate pentru descrieri ale acestor drepturi):

1. Dreptul de a primi informații privind practicile de confidențialitate.
2. Dreptul de a cunoaște următoarele:

* Categoriile de Informații cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat despre dvs.
* Categoriile de surse pentru Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat despre dvs.
* Scopul nostru comercial sau de afaceri pentru colectarea respectivelor Informații cu caracter personal.
* Categoriile de terțe părți cu care partajăm respectivele Informații cu caracter personal.
* Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le-am colectat despre dvs. (denumită și o solicitare de portabilitate a datelor) și vă oferim o copie în format electronic sau pe hârtie.
* Dacă am divulgat Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pentru un scop de afaceri, vă oferim o listă care indică divulgările pentru un scop de afaceri, identificând categoriile de Informații cu caracter personal pe care le-a obținut fiecare categorie de destinatari.

3. Dreptul la ștergere.
4. Dreptul la corectare.
5. Dreptul de a renunța la publicitatea comportamentală în context încrucișat, vânzarea sau partajarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal, prelucrarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal pentru crearea de profiluri și luarea automată a deciziilor.
6. Dreptul de a limita utilizarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal sensibile. Vă rugăm să rețineți că nu utilizăm Informații sensibile cu caracter personal despre dvs. în scopuri care nu sunt autorizate de CCPA și CPRA.

LEGEA PRIVIND PROTECȚIA DATELOR CONSUMATORILOR DIN VIRGINIA (VCDPA), LEGEA PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA DIN COLORADO (CPA)[\[1\]](#ftnt1), LEGEA PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA CONSUMATORILOR DIN UTAH (UCPA)[\[2\]](#ftnt2) ȘI LEGEA PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA DATELOR DIN CONNECTICUT (CDPA)[\[3\]](#ftnt3).  
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Ne puteți contacta pentru a vă exercita următoarele drepturi în temeiul acestor legi specifice statelor:

1. Dreptul de a primi informații privind practicile de confidențialitate.
2. Dreptul de a cunoaște.
3. Dreptul la ștergere.
4. Dreptul la corectare.
5. Dreptul de a renunța la publicitatea direcționată sau vânzarea de Informații cu caracter personal.
6. Dreptul de a renunța la crearea de profiluri (prelucrarea automată a informațiilor cu caracter personal în scopul analizării sau anticipării caracteristicilor sau comportamentelor viitoare ale unui individ, rezultând în decizii care afectează drepturile fundamentale ale unei persoane).  
7. Consumatorii din Virginia, Colorado și Connecticut au, de asemenea, dreptul de a contesta deciziile noastre cu privire la solicitările în calitate de persoană vizată, contactându-ne prin aceeași metodă de transmitere a unei solicitări. Vă rugăm să anexați o copie a sau altfel să faceți referire la decizia noastră privind solicitarea dvs. în calitate de persoană vizată, astfel încât să putem soluționa în mod adecvat contestația dvs. Vom răspunde la contestația dvs. în conformitate cu legislația aplicabilă.

NEVADA
------

După cum s-a descris mai sus, putem vinde identificatorii dvs. sau alte informații de identificare pe care le colectăm de pe Site-urile și Serviciile noastre online către părți neafiliate, în scopuri de urmărire a comportamentului în context încrucișat, în sensul legislației din Nevada. Aveți dreptul de a renunța la vânzarea sau licențierea acelor categorii de informații cu caracter personal despre dvs. către părți neafiliate.

EXERCITAREA DREPTURILOR
-----------------------

Pentru a vă exercita drepturile de acces, corectare, portabilitate a datelor și ștergere descrise mai sus, vă rugăm să transmiteți o solicitare către noi folosind formularul nostru online disponibil [aici](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy-notice.html#data-form). Doar dvs. sau o persoană pe care ați autorizat-o să acționeze în numele dvs. puteți face o solicitare legată de Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal. De asemenea, puteți face o solicitare în numele copilului dvs. minor. Dacă primim un formular de solicitare de la o persoană pentru exercitarea unui drept în numele dvs., vom solicita o copie a permisiunii dvs. semnată, prin care îi acordați autorizarea de a transmite asemenea solicitări în numele dvs. și vă vom contacta pentru a confirma în mod direct autorizarea respectivă. Puteți face o solicitare pentru accesul la sau portabilitatea datelor doar de două ori într-o perioadă de 12 luni. Este necesar ca solicitarea verificabilă a Consumatorului:

* Să furnizeze suficiente informații care să ne permită să verificăm în mod rezonabil dacă sunteți persoana despre care am colectat Informații cu caracter personal sau dacă un reprezentant autorizat a formulat solicitarea.
* Să descrie solicitarea dvs. cu suficiente detalii care să ne permită să înțelegem, să evaluăm și să răspundem în mod corespunzător.

Nu putem răspunde solicitării dvs. sau nu vă putem furniza Informații cu caracter personal dacă nu vă putem verifica identitatea sau autoritatea de a formula solicitarea și de a confirma că Informațiile cu caracter personal au legătură cu dvs. Efectuarea unei solicitări nu necesită crearea unui cont la noi. Vom utiliza Informațiile cu caracter personal furnizate într-o solicitare numai pentru a verifica identitatea sau autoritatea solicitantului de a formula solicitarea.

Pentru a vă exercita drepturile de a renunța la publicitatea comportamentală în context încrucișat, dreptul de a renunța la publicitatea direcționată sau partajarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal, după cum este descris mai sus, va trebui să renunțați în funcție de platforma pe care vă aflați.  Rețineți că solicitarea dvs. de a renunța este specifică dispozitivului și platformei pe care transmiteți solicitarea respectivă, așadar este posibil să fie nevoie să înaintați mai multe solicitări dacă intenționați să renunțați la aceste activități de prelucrare specifice pentru mai multe dispozitive și platforme. Vă rugăm să faceți clic:

* aici pentru a renunța la Plugshare.com (Platforma web)
* aici pentru a renunța la aplicația Plugshare pe iOS
* aici pentru a renunța la aplicația Plugshare pe Android

### Procesul de verificare

La primirea unei solicitări de accesare a datelor, corectare, portabilitate a datelor sau ștergere de la dvs., vă vom trimite un e-mail în termen de 10 zile lucrătoare la adresa de e-mail pe care o avem înregistrată pentru dvs. la dosar. E-mailul vă va solicita să răspundeți pentru a vă verifica în calitate de Consumator care face solicitarea. La primirea verificării dvs., vom corela informațiile dvs. cu cele din dosarul nostru. După verificarea identității dvs., vom continua să prelucrăm solicitarea dvs. și vom răspunde în termen de 45 de zile calendaristice, cu excepția cazului în care (a) nu putem verifica solicitarea dvs., (b) nu putem să vă corelăm cu informațiile din baza noastră de date sau (c) există o excepție în temeiul legii care ne scutește să îndeplinim solicitarea dvs. Dacă avem nevoie de mai mult timp (până la patruzeci și cinci (45) de zile calendaristice suplimentare), vă vom informa în scris despre motivul și perioada de prelungire.

Dacă nu suntem în măsură să vă onorăm solicitarea, răspunsul pe care vi-l furnizăm va explica motivele corespunzătoare. Pentru solicitările de portabilitate a datelor, vom selecta un format pentru a furniza Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal care este ușor de utilizat și ar trebui să vă permită să transmiteți informațiile de la o entitate la alta fără obstacole.

Nu percepem o taxă pentru a prelucra sau a răspunde la solicitarea dvs. verificabilă a Consumatorului, cu excepția cazului în care este excesivă, repetitivă sau nefondată în mod evident. Dacă stabilim că solicitarea necesită o taxă, vă vom informa de ce am luat decizia respectivă și vă vom furniza o estimare a costurilor înainte de a finaliza solicitarea.

* * *

NOTIFICĂRI PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA PENTRU ANUMITE ȚĂRI DIN AFARA SUA
=======================================================================

INFORMAȚII GENERALE
-------------------

1. ### CONSIMȚĂMÂNTUL DVS. SPECIFIC PENTRU PRELUCRAREA CATEGORIILOR „SENSIBILE” SAU „SPECIALE” DE INFORMAȚII CU CARACTER PERSONAL

Conform legislației privind confidențialitatea din unele țări, anumite tipuri de Informații cu caracter personal sunt considerate categorii „sensibile” sau „speciale” de informații. Prelucrăm rar categorii sensibile sau speciale de date, cu excepția cazului în care acest lucru este în interesul dvs. vital sau al altei persoane. Pentru toate celelalte circumstanțe, vă dați în mod specific consimțământul pentru colectarea, prelucrarea și păstrarea de către noi a categoriilor sensibile sau speciale de Informații cu caracter personal, conform descrierii din Secțiunea 1.2 a Politicii noastre principale de confidențialitate și, de asemenea, pentru prelucrarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal în conformitate cu această Notificare privind confidențialitatea.  

2. ### TEMEIURILE NOASTRE JURIDICE PENTRU PRELUCRAREA INFORMAȚIILOR CU CARACTER PERSONAL

Temeiurile noastre juridice pentru colectarea și utilizarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal descrise mai sus vor depinde de Informațiile cu caracter personal în cauză și de contextul specific în care le colectăm. În general, vom colecta și prelucra Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal numai în cazul în care avem nevoie de Informațiile cu caracter personal pentru a vă furniza Serviciile pentru care ați încheiat un contract cu noi sau, în cazul în care prelucrarea este în interesul nostru legitim și nu este anulată de interesele dvs. privind protecția datelor sau de drepturile și libertățile dvs. fundamentale, ne vom baza pe consimțământul dvs. în cazul în care avem obligația legală de a face acest lucru. În unele cazuri, este posibil să avem, de asemenea, obligația legală de a colecta Informații cu caracter personal de la dvs. sau este posibil să avem nevoie de Informațiile cu caracter personal pentru a vă proteja interesele vitale sau pe cele ale unei alte persoane.

TEMEIUL INTERESULUI LEGITIM PENTRU COLECTAREA INFORMAȚIILOR CU CARACTER PERSONAL: Colectarea și prelucrarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal pot fi necesare în scopurile intereselor noastre legitime. Astfel de scopuri ale intereselor legitime pot include:

* prevenirea fraudei
* asigurarea securității rețelei și a informațiilor
* indicarea posibilelor acte penale sau amenințări privind securitatea publică, inclusiv îmbunătățirea protecției comunității noastre împotriva spamurilor, hărțuirii, încălcării proprietății intelectuale, infracțiunilor și riscurilor de securitate de orice fel și punerea în aplicare a revendicărilor legale, inclusiv investigarea potențialelor încălcări ale Termenilor noștri de utilizare
* îndeplinirea obligațiilor noastre legale
* prelucrarea datelor despre angajat sau vizitator, membru, participant sau înregistrator
* îndeplinirea funcției sau a serviciului pe care ni l-ați solicitat
* furnizarea Serviciilor noastre și a funcționalității acestora către dvs. în cazul în care o astfel de prelucrare este necesară în scopul intereselor legitime urmărite de noi sau de furnizorii noștri de servicii în legătură cu Serviciile
* marketing direct
* relația relevantă și adecvată pe care o avem cu dvs.
* analize, de ex., evaluarea numărului de vizitatori, vizualizările paginilor, utilizarea Site-urilor etc., pentru a înțelege modul în care sunt utilizate Site-urile, Produsele și Serviciile noastre, pentru a optimiza Site-urile și/sau comunicările viitoare și pentru a dezvolta noi servicii și caracteristici ale Site-urilor
* actualizarea informațiilor și preferințelor dvs.
* oferirea și îmbunătățirea Site-urilor, Produselor și Serviciilor noastre
* executarea cererilor legale, inclusiv investigarea potențialelor încălcări ale Termenilor noștri

În plus față de informațiile furnizate mai sus, următoarele secțiuni se aplică numai rezidenților sau cetățenilor țării sau regiunii discutate. În scopurile următoarelor secțiuni, cu excepția cazului în care se menționează în mod specific, definiția „Informațiilor cu caracter personal” așa cum este utilizată mai sus va reprezenta definiția informațiilor cu caracter personal, a datelor cu caracter personal sau a unui termen similar aplicabilă în temeiul legilor privind confidențialitatea datelor din țara sau regiunea respectivă. În cazul unui conflict între secțiunile de mai jos și cele de mai sus, vor prevala secțiunile de mai jos.

RGPD – NOTIFICARE PRIVIND CONFIDENȚIALITATEA PENTRU REZIDENȚII DIN SPAȚIUL ECONOMIC EUROPEAN (SEE), REGATUL UNIT ȘI ELVEȚIA
---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. ### PREZENTARE GENERALĂ

Următoarele prevederi se aplică numai dacă sunteți un rezident din SEE, Regatul Unit sau Elveția (denumite în această Secțiune „Regiunea UE”).

Pentru acești rezidenți, toate prelucrările Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal sunt efectuate în conformitate cu drepturile și reglementările privind confidențialitatea, în special Regulamentul (UE) 2016/679 al Parlamentului European și al Consiliului din 27 aprilie 2016, cunoscut sub denumirea de Regulamentul general privind protecția datelor sau Regulamentul general privind protecția datelor din Regatul Unit pentru rezidenții din Regatul Unit (denumite în continuare împreună „RGPD”), iar prelucrarea noastră va fi efectuată în conformitate cu RGPD. În sensul RGPD, vom fi „operatorul de date” al Informațiilor cu caracter personal (denumite și definite în RGPD (disponibil [aici](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-4-gdpr/-fws_PydAsXAe)) „date cu caracter personal”) pe care le colectăm, cu excepția cazului în care colectăm astfel de informații în numele unui „operator de date”, caz în care vom fi „persoana împuternicită de operatorul de date”. Această Politică de confidențialitate nu se aplică site-urilor, aplicațiilor sau serviciilor care nu afișează sau nu fac trimitere la această Politică de confidențialitate sau care afișează sau fac trimitere la o altă politică de confidențialitate. Numai pentru rezidenții și cetățenii din Regiunea UE, în măsura în care orice definiție din această Politică de confidențialitate intră în conflict cu o definiție în temeiul RGPD, definiția RGPD va prevala.

Oferim o protecție adecvată transferului Informațiilor cu caracter personal către țări din afara Regiunii UE, prin una sau mai multe din următoarele metode: (a) o serie de acorduri inter-companii bazate pe sau care încorporează Clauzele contractuale standard, (b) ne putem baza pe deciziile de adecvare ale Comisiei Europene cu privire la anumite țări, după caz, (c) putem obține consimțământul dvs. pentru aceste transferuri de date din Regiunea UE către Statele Unite ale Americii și alte țări, (d) putem adopta reguli corporative obligatorii, sau (e) în măsura aplicabilă, ne putem baza pe derogări prevăzute de Articolul 49 din RGPD pentru transferul și transferul ulterior al Informațiilor cu caracter personal colectate de la persoane fizice din Regiunea UE către Statele Unite și alte țări despre care Regiunea UE consideră că nu oferă o protecție adecvată a datelor. În ceea ce privește metoda (e), putem transfera Informații cu caracter personal către o terță parte pentru a îndeplini un contract încheiat cu dvs., cu consimțământul dvs. explicit sau într-un mod care să nu anuleze drepturile și libertățile dvs. Dacă aceste Informații cu caracter personal nu sunt prelucrate și transferate, nu vom putea îndeplini contractul încheiat cu dvs. sau nu veți avea acces la niciunul sau toate beneficiile și caracteristicile asociate tranzacției dvs.

De asemenea, este posibil să fie necesar să transferăm informațiile dvs. către alte companii din grup sau furnizori de servicii din țări din afara Regiunii UE. Acest lucru se poate întâmpla dacă serverele sau furnizorii și prestatorii noștri de servicii se află în afara Regiunii UE sau dacă utilizați Produsele și/sau Serviciile noastre în timp ce vizitați țări din afara acestor zone.

Temeiurile noastre juridice pentru colectarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal sunt discutate .

2. ### DREPTURILE DVS. PRIVIND DATELE ÎN CONFORMITATE CU RGPD.

Dacă sunteți supus RGPD, drepturile dvs. includ următoarele drepturi:

* Dreptul de a cunoaște.
* Dreptul la corectare.
* Dreptul la ștergere.
* Dreptul de a restricționa sau de a vă opune prelucrării. Aveți dreptul de a vă opune Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal utilizate în următoarele moduri: (a) prelucrarea bazată pe interese legitime sau efectuarea unei sarcini în interesul public/exercitarea unei autorități oficiale (inclusiv crearea de profiluri); (b) marketingul direct (inclusiv crearea de profiluri); și (c) prelucrarea în scopuri de cercetare științifică/istorică și statistici. Consultați mai jos pentru mai multe informații.
* Dreptul de a renunța. Aveți dreptul de a nu vă supune unei decizii bazate exclusiv pe prelucrarea automată, inclusiv crearea de profiluri, care produce efecte juridice care vă privesc sau vă afectează semnificativ în mod similar, în afară de excepțiile aplicabile în temeiul legilor relevante privind protecția datelor.
* Dreptul de a depune o plângere. Dacă sunteți un rezident din SEE, o listă a Autorităților naționale pentru protecția datelor poate fi găsită [aici](https://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). Dacă sunteți un rezident din Regatul Unit, puteți contacta Biroul Comisarului pentru Informații [aici.](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)
* Dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul.

NOTIFICĂRI CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN ALTE ȚĂRI (ÎN AFARA SUA)
--------------------------------------------------------

Următoarele informații din această Secțiune se adaugă informațiilor discutate în Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate.

Vom respecta următoarele drepturi ale persoanelor vizate pentru toți rezidenții din afara SUA:

* Dreptul de a primi informații privind practicile de confidențialitate:

* Identitatea și informațiile noastre de contact,
* Scopul specific al prelucrării de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal,
* Formularul și durata prelucrării de către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal,
* Informații despre partajarea de către noi și scopul partajării Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal,
* Responsabilitățile oricăror terți care prelucrează Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și
* Informații cu privire la orice entități juridice publice și private cu care am partajat Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal.  

* Dreptul de a cunoaște:

* Decizii luate exclusiv pe baza prelucrării automate a Informațiilor cu caracter personal.
* Informații de acces despre Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm.  

* Dreptul la corectare.
* Dreptul de a restricționa sau de a vă opune prelucrării.
* Dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul.

Orice traducere a acestei Politici de confidențialitate într-o altă limbă decât limba engleză este furnizată exclusiv în scop informativ. În cazul oricăror discrepanțe, singura versiune validă și obligatorie din punct de vedere juridic va fi versiunea în limba engleză a acestui document.

1. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN ARGENTINA

Măsurile tehnice și organizatorice de securitate implementate de PlugShare ar susține, de asemenea, regulile din Legea privind protecția datelor cu caracter personal din Argentina (PDPA) 25.326, cum ar fi interzicerea oricărei utilizări secundare a datelor cu caracter personal ale unei persoane vizate și interzicerea transferului de date cu caracter personal către țări care nu oferă un nivel adecvat de protecție. PlugShare utilizează un acord de transfer/prelucrare a datelor pentru a ajuta la respectarea Prevederilor PDPA 60-E/2016, care reglementează transferul transfrontalier de date cu caracter personal.

Rezidenții din Argentina au (a) dreptul de a cunoaște informații despre existența și scopul acestor Informații cu caracter personal și (b) dreptul la corectare și dreptul de a restricționa sau a se opune prelucrării Informațiilor cu caracter personal dacă acestea sunt false, inexacte sau discriminatorii.

2. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN AUSTRALIA

Putem utiliza și divulga Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal (astfel cum sunt definite de legislația din Australia) către terțe părți cu sediul în afara Australiei, în principal în Statele Unite, așa cum este descris la Secțiunea 9 a Politicii noastre principale de confidențialitate. Sunteți de acord și confirmați că destinatarii din străinătate vor fi supuși legislației privind confidențialitatea din jurisdicția lor locală și nu pot fi supuși niciunei obligații de confidențialitate sau niciunui principiu similar cu Principiile de confidențialitate din Australia. De asemenea, aceștia vor fi supuși unei legislații străine care ar putea impune divulgarea Informațiilor cu caracter personal către o terță parte, cum ar fi o autoritate străină. Cu excepția cazului în care ne notificați în scris contrariul, se va considera că ați consimțit la divulgarea de către noi a Informațiilor cu caracter personal către destinatari din străinătate. Aveți opțiunea de a vă păstra anonimatul atunci când interacționați cu noi sau de a nu ne divulga anumite Informații cu caracter personal. Totuși, acest lucru poate însemna că este posibil să nu vă putem furniza Serviciile noastre.

Pentru rezidenții din Australia, actualizările la această Politică de confidențialitate intră în vigoare dacă obținem consimțământul dvs. expres sau dacă oferim o opțiune de renunțare atunci când sunt anunțate modificări semnificative (de exemplu, pe Site-urile noastre sau prin e-mail).

3. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN BRAZILIA

Rezidenții din Brazilia au dreptul de a cunoaște următoarele informații: dacă furnizarea de către dvs. către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal este o cerință contractuală sau dacă există vreo consecință a nefurnizării unor astfel de date (răspunsul este nu pentru ambele cazuri), informații cu privire la orice proces decizional automatizat (inclusiv crearea de profiluri) al nostru (consultați Secțiunea 2.1 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate), aveți dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul pentru prelucrarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal și drepturile dvs. de acces în calitate de persoană vizată (a se vedea mai jos).

Rezidenții din Brazilia au, de asemenea, următoarele drepturi: (a) dreptul de a cunoaște, inclusiv de a obține o copie a acestor informații; (b) dreptul la corectare; (c) dreptul de a restricționa sau a se opune prelucrării; (d) dreptul la ștergere; (e) dreptul de a primi informații despre practicile de confidențialitate cu privire la entitățile publice și private cu care au fost partajate Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și (f) dreptul de a depune o plângere la autoritatea de supraveghere a datelor din Brazilia (ANPD).

4. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN CANADA (INCLUSIV QUEBEC)

Politica noastră de confidențialitate și practicile noastre generale sunt concepute pentru a respecta legile canadiene privind confidențialitatea, inclusiv Legea privind protecția informațiilor cu caracter personal și a documentelor electronice (PIPEDA) și, dacă este cazul, Legea privind confidențialitatea în sectorul privat din Quebec, Protecția informațiilor cu caracter personal în sectorul privat (RSQ, c. P-39.1). Pentru orice practici de gestionare a informațiilor care nu sunt legate în mod rezonabil de scopurile pentru care ați contactat PlugShare, aveți dreptul de a renunța la astfel de practici de gestionare a informațiilor (inclusiv marketing, crearea de profiluri, publicitate comportamentală, partajarea cu o terță parte care nu este un furnizor de servicii).  

Rezidenții din Canada au dreptul de a renunța la utilizarea de către noi a Informațiilor cu caracter personal în scopuri de marketing direct și alte prelucrări care nu sunt necesare în mod rezonabil pentru a răspunde scopurilor pentru care ne-ați angajat.

5. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN HONG KONG

Utilizăm Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal în următoarele scopuri de marketing direct: (a) pentru a comunica cu dvs. despre produsele și serviciile noastre și ale afiliaților noștri și (b) pentru a vă trimite notificări, promoții suplimentare sau alte materiale de marketing cu privire la Site-urile, Produsele și Serviciile noastre și cele ale afiliaților noștri. Consimțământul dvs. în acest scop va fi solicitat la momentul transmiterii de către dvs. a Informațiilor cu caracter personal (de exemplu, la crearea contului, înregistrarea la evenimente etc.) către noi.

6. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN MEXIC

În plus față de informațiile prezentate mai sus, rezidenții din Mexic au dreptul de a primi Informații privind practicile de confidențialitate, inclusiv (a) dacă furnizarea de către dvs. către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal este o cerință contractuală sau dacă există vreo consecință a nefurnizării acestor date (răspunsul este nu pentru ambele cazuri), (b) informații cu privire la orice proces decizional automatizat (inclusiv crearea de profiluri) al nostru (care este discutat la Secțiunea 2.1 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate), (c) durata păstrării (consultați Secțiunea 7 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate), (d) dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul pentru prelucrarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal și (e) drepturile dvs. de acces în calitate de persoană vizată (a se vedea mai jos). Aveți, de asemenea, dreptul de a cunoaște indicarea expresă a Informațiilor sensibile cu caracter personal care vor fi prelucrate.

Rezidenții din Mexic au, de asemenea, următoarele drepturi: (a) dreptul de a cunoaște Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm, inclusiv de a fi informați cu privire la entitățile publice și private cu care au fost partajate Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și de a obține o copie a acestor informații; (b) dreptul la corectare; (c) dreptul de a restricționa sau de a se opune prelucrării și (d) dreptul la ștergere.

7. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN SINGAPORE

Printre alte drepturi, dacă ne desfășurăm activitatea în Singapore, aveți dreptul ca Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pe care le deținem să fie transmise unei alte organizații.

Persoanele sau companiile cărora le divulgăm și transferăm Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal pot fi situate în afara Singapore. Ne vom asigura că destinatarii Informațiilor cu caracter personal transferate pot oferi Informațiilor cu caracter personal transferate un standard de protecție comparabil cu standardele de protecție prevăzute de legislația din Singapore privind confidențialitatea, prin utilizarea acordurilor scrise privind transferul datelor (pentru transferuri către terțe părți) sau a regulilor corporative obligatorii (pentru transferuri către afiliații noștri și alte entități care au legătură cu noi).

8. ### NOTIFICARE CĂTRE REZIDENȚII DIN TAIWAN

Rezidenții din Taiwan au dreptul de a primi informații privind practicile de confidențialitate.

Rezidenții din Taiwan au, de asemenea, următoarele drepturi: (a) dreptul de a cunoaște Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm, inclusiv de a fi informați cu privire la entitățile publice și private cu care au fost partajate Informațiile dvs. cu caracter personal și de a obține o copie a acestor informații; (b) dreptul la corectare; (c) dreptul de a restricționa sau de a se opune prelucrării și (d) dreptul la ștergere.

În plus față de informațiile prezentate mai sus, rezidenții din Taiwan au dreptul de a cunoaște anumite informații despre Informațiile cu caracter personal pe care le colectăm, inclusiv (a) dacă furnizarea de către dvs. către noi a Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal este o cerință contractuală sau dacă există vreo consecință a nefurnizării acestor date (răspunsul este nu pentru ambele cazuri), (b) informații cu privire la orice proces decizional automatizat (inclusiv crearea de profiluri) al nostru (care este discutat la Secțiunea 2.1 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate), (c) durata păstrării (consultați Secțiunea 7 din Politica noastră principală de confidențialitate), (d) dreptul de a vă retrage consimțământul pentru prelucrarea Informațiilor dvs. cu caracter personal și (e) drepturile dvs. de acces în calitate de persoană vizată (a se vedea mai jos). De asemenea, aveți dreptul de a cunoaște indicarea expresă a Informațiilor sensibile cu caracter personal care urmează să fie prelucrate (nu colectăm informații „sensibile”).

* * *

[\[1\]](#ftnt_ref1) Legea privind confidențialitatea din Colorado intră în vigoare la 1 iulie 2023.

[\[2\]](#ftnt_ref2) Legea privind confidențialitatea consumatorilor din Utah intră în vigoare la 31 decembrie 2023.

[\[3\]](#ftnt_ref3) Legea privind confidențialitatea datelor din Connecticut intră în vigoare la 1 iulie 2023.

© 2024 PlugShare LLC. All rights reserved.

PlugShare.com uses [Cookies](https://company.plugshare.com/cookies.html) to help us understand how our features are used. We've recently updated our [Privacy Policy](https://company.plugshare.com/privacy.html). Accept
